Everybody
I went to ifo with the with the with unity Technologies a couple weeks
Go like right before Thanksgiving and
Friend of mine gray cotton
He had an HTC Vive and I played with oculus app raided the gear VR play with a bunch of these things and
K cool but I never played an HTC Vive and as soon as he got it out
As soon as he showed me those like boxes
I realized htc-vive is where the future of VR is
I feel really bad that I'm like a year behind the times now but
It just totally blew my mind when I was able to play space pirate trainer and it just work now is the coolest thing
The fact that
This thing knows where it is in 3D space is just so cool and
But I think it's also really cool is
The way in which it knows where it is and that's one of the things I just decided as soon as I get my hands on this thing
By the way I didn't actually buy all of big thanks to Unity Technologies for financing most of the purchase
This product for
For myhabit hacking fun
But I
I wanted to be able to hack this be able to find out where was and all the other details in a way that was
Actually open source
And there are some projects but they're under the lgpl and they're
You're not quite there either so that's that one of the big things that the name
He realize I wanted to do a lot of packing was there are some other project like
Libre osvr Vive
But the problem was this project to do it it's not
It's not ready or not that Fuller complete or anyting
I started trying to actually get it and trying to get all of the libraries that were necessary for the osvr implementation
And everything else and they needed eigen and opencv and
All of this stuff and I actually ran out of data on my cell phone plan
And I decided this is just ridiculous
Somebody needs to write an HTC Vive thing that is a reasonable size will be very fast
Hospital
I got it out requires V
VR capable computer I realized
They haven't met me have the wires they wouldn't cuz I'm not really famous or anything but that's okay because I'm going to
If I can get this htc-vive running over the next couple months on this right
I hear my old little touchy-feely Intel i5 gen 1 laptop
Okay
And it totally does not have a TV that you be able to handle it but I don't know I'll just see what happens when
Whatever I'm not
I don't need fast computers to see if it's going to work
There have been a lot of progress in these these these different tools people have been reverse engineering it more and more
Implementations on Lenox and stuff like that
So like this Heroes VR Vive Libre
Call the vibe I kept pronouncing it.
And Viv and all that I don't know why I just thought it was funny so
No it's a mine
Thanks Greg for for fixing that my mind
Any rate these tools that people have been copying off each other for a while have
Various levels of completion but none of them are really all that.
Really this is a matter of being on like I'm like a little midget on the giant Justin shoulders
Because other people have already gone through a great deal of effort figuring out exactly what all of these messages
At the very least how to get them so for instance here under the lighthouse redox
Project under
Neural neural something like that
They have done a lot of reverse engineering on the USB protocol so what the basic
Machines are basic endpoints are devices
So
Lsusd I can see a bunch of these devices from the HTC Vive
They've kind of documented what they were and what kind of devices to stay attached as
So there's a bunch of different properties you can get this thing
Hear Hoops wrong window know what you're going over to the other desktop
Cuz I don't meet you
So
Hope you're going to go over together desktop to
This right here so this is the hmd or I don't even know what the other names for Dar but this
Sing right here has a bunch of documented commands that you can receive from an information about the lens separation
Whether or not this button right here is pressed and whether or not there's a person who's like moving their face
Closer or farther face proximity it says how close their faces this live
Center
Right in there
Actually you can kind of see it flashing a little bit I guess
What's interesting that means that the camera here can actually see a little bit of infrared
I can't quite see the white house so I can't really show you guys
The lighthouse data
Erase this thing's got all these sensors on it and all of that and
Acted by USB to my laptop here
Headset connected through cable
My laptop over including all of
The the light sensors
I guess I should also spend a minute explaining how this whole thing works and why I thought it was so cool so for doing
Room scale kind of telling where you are that's a really really hard problem and you think that you know since 19
Figure out a solvent good
Dave Chapman
David somebody who's working on some of the other parts of this affect the project
So trying to reverse-engineer this last little bit that I'm kind of run into and he's also going to be working on trying to
To do the mathematics use the common filters to figure out based on the IMU updates of the devices
Where they are in 3D space
I also using the system I'm about to go and explain how it works so the reason
That the the HTC Vive is so
Amazing is because the way in which it tells where everything is so
It has these lighthouses that Lighthouse up there
And I want across the room and barely see it over there
For specifically coded. Of time and they sweep a laser this way
Bellator this way and then the other one flashes its lights weeps flashes its lights flashing
The same in between each time
And depending on the amount of time it was between the Flash
And when you see that light sweep passed you that's how you know where you are in this axis Felton
To the lighthouse and how you know where you are in this axis relative to the lighthouse
Give me a second here I'm going to go pull up a video I recorded
I'm probably going to turn into video
Plugging it in here
Define dit
But you know what
Hard time keeping up so I took a video
Admitting light this is with an infrared camera
And I used rolling shutter in order to get a better picture as to what's going on
What happens if there's this field of LEDs visible right here that goes
Goes and does The Flash and these two wheels there and there with your spinning around in a meeting
The beam of light what go and paint the scene
So to speak
I guess why they call them lighthouses cuz they really do like and each one
The little sisters on the Vive
Can pick up exactly when the face
Exactly where it is and the other thing that makes it super cool is it means that you can have a bunch of these devices
They don't make it harder for you to figure out where they all are which is just completely mind-boggling because that's like one of the hugest problem
I never thought I had never heard of this technology it was amazing I have to start playing with it
By the way I'm also playing with the esp32 so
You'll have to wait to see if I actually get far enough to figure out how to make them thicker related
So David over there and Dave has been working
Level
First though so back into what I'm actually here to do today it's kind of now the intro video
I want to know what time the lights Weeps By each one of them
Have the other one I want to know what time the lights we spy
Each one of the sensors on this thing right here so each one of these little dots has little photo center
And there is a processor onboard that operates at 48 make undershirt actually operated much higher but they will
Tell you that within 148 millionth of a second when that being came and hit each one of those little dots
And I want to be able to get that data back now for the headset
That's really easy that's actually already documented and it's documented really really well
Somewhere here like how
I am U button controller
Wireless dongle
Oh where is it it's somewhere here
I'm looking I'm looking
Maybe it wasn't documented here all that well
Hmd display
How cool H&D Brendan says hmd may stand for head-mounted display I didn't know that
What are you guys still watching the chat so I don't okay
So if something comes up tell me that I should stop
Now that's not useful
Okay you know what actually I don't maybe they don't documented maybe that was under the
Osvr Vive here
I can find a different file that they were looking at here it is
VL hid reports.
They have the head-to-head Mount display structures and they tell me what everything is I can file
Find the right one
Give me a second to find it
Not yet
Oh okay
But that's not the point the point where yes
Make that clear
Answer that more clearly okay I will do that after this next section. You guys
I don't have a question about why and I'll get into that this is actually the right that
The right one
Whenever the light passes by or Flash hits it I get information when did that flash happen and
And how long was the Flash and it tells me which sensor on the amount pet gnosis play
It was that actually received the Flash
On the head-mounted display that actually received the Flash and so using the structure I can then parse back and get it
Information about what all is actually going on, the problem is with this
This guy this is not any word near fat
Has all sorts of crazy crazy different protocol from any other part of the system
Tattoos in Wireless mode
The way with parse was just not not quite there so I started to really dig at that
Almond so introduce my project
Live survive so that people with lower end Hardware specifically
So I can survive on my cell phone data plan and be able to get the stuff I need without having
Any rate
To check that out and in here I'm actually starting on everything so under the source Direct
After 8 I have survived USB type-c
So I do note that this is basically a blatant rip-off of everybody else's previous work button
Because of other reasons in constrained I do have to get it written under the mitx
11 license so that is what license is going to be under as I have to rewrite portions which I have written
From the ground-up I may have to specifically right portions in order to maintain that
So you guys are curious why
And and I do want to clarify so it does have to do with with the
Speed and I do believe that the architecture that everybody's using right now which involves
Enormous
The interaction between the hardware to the server to the different pieces of software that
Environment for the virtual reality World in which you're going to be playing is entirely too complicated for
And
I see that those from software point of view because I like to really get into the nuts-and-bolts I would rather
V that have a working product and I know that seems
Dumb but that's its decide might have been able to look at something and see all of the parts but
Because those parts are really big the fact that I needed a copy of eigg in
Decompiled like this and they're not even doing calming filters as far as I can tell in any of the open-source libraries
That was that was pretty painful I mean I kind of big and all of the other pack
Packages that are necessary to operate these and
Hair stuck in object-oriented Haitian land of just
Mountains mountains of abstractions in classes and everything and I'm I'm seguy I want to be able to work with
More concrete objects in concrete
Like simple code that's really kind of my driving Factor behind this I don't want
Going to have client-server relationships and all this other stuff which I'm going to have a limited amount probably
But not for the core environment I want to be able to have a library that you can use and be able to just get the position of all
All of these objects
And maybe I'll have a companion library at some point
Maybe this is all time this guy I've no idea whenever I see going to do any of this stuff but where it would simplify its
Just be a library you include and you can just start writing opengl code
And that's that's where I want to be that's what I want to have I don't want to mess with these levels beefed-up possum instantiate in all the
I just want a really basic Library
It doesn't use very much room and very few dependencies like a right now we're looking at using the potty
Person that transforms which is a pretty small Library we might not even be using that I'm right now I think I'm using zlide
And live USB and pthread switch
Come on most Linux distributions and even if live USB doesn't it's only like a megabyte
I hope that answers everything Brandon his chatton
Going pretty good
Okay by the way I got to inverse phase over there
He has been sick the last couple of days but he's he's feeling better today that's good
So David Chapman's over there he's been helping out like look at the protocol and all that
And Dom and really the last thing that I didn't know how to do it all so when I saw Pro
Problems I want to make sure that I can get the problem whatever it is from this huge nebulous
Whatever into something that I can put into a box and something that I know I can control the inputs in the output
And
Everybody else who's been working on these projects has done an amazing job at making that possible
Be able to get it somewhere that I can have it
But still this thing is the last Bastion so until I can figure out where this thing is flights are I can't even
Begin to figure out
Like where it is cuz I can't decode the light coming past it
So what I can do right now
Power off this guy
And I'm going to go run a copy of
Also stickers on the Waterworks bass get rid of it
I can still build it
Okay
So
Whenever I have a message that comes in from something I don't know what is
It will display their so I can power this thing on
And right now there's no messages
But what I can do
Dwyane Wade normally try to solve these problems with this is I try to control it so
I was able to decode all of the buttons and all of that next week
Python print statement so you guys can see what that looks like
Five data so let's just first look
At the IMU information
And see what that looks like
Okay so you can see here the IMU data so the IMU inside
This guy is based off of a an accelerometer and it has an extra
Hawaii and Izzy bizu XYZ
And a gyro here here in here so if I rotate the thing so it's
So like this is negative
Negative X orientation down and they can see -4000 about 4090
In the First Column if I do it this way
It's about positive 4096 in the First Column and then if I do it this way
Way
You can see that it's about 4000 second column
Cameron diaz
Somewhere here there this way is he down
And then you have the gyro which can tell you
Rotating around that axis for this access or you know whatever axies whatever
Videos that use the siren accelerometer in between frames for sweet
Exactly where you are in a really fast rate that's how you actually can make
Can be tracking you in real-time so let's stop looking at that for a moment
And let's actually just just for the sake of you guys getting a feel for it
I do need to push some updates I had a bit of a sour attitude with
This last night I feel bad for the lighthouse redox people open up a ticket and was a little dress
Castrated sorry I didn't mean to bite you guys anyway
And I kind of
Yeah I shouldn't said that there's a lot of issues with the doc's not know the doctor really good thank you so
Come back here there are there different kinds of commands that can come back from this thing, they're all pass through
The same data buffer and commands can contain things like the buttons or the axies
Likely either trigger Axis or the touch access for right now just so you guys can
I'm not totally kidding you I'm going to just print out the analog access whenever it gets
Stride you can't see if I knew that the analog access whenever I update it
Picotte always on top
So I'm not going to print that out whenever whenever gets updated
So now
Hold on I've got to be
On the bug
So now this this trigger right here is I pull it Tighter and Tighter it goes up higher and higher
So now by looking at this particular command I can see what it's values are if I
Look at a different command like if I print out when I receive something in the the other message
Then whenever I touch the touchpad right here
You can see that it update so that's a very negative
X and Y so actually seeing both
So now if I go over there it's 32,000 there's 31
Negative positive
That's what those numbers mean I do think that there are a lot of
Are these values that nobody really figured out how to parse before it has to do with the way in which these B flags were used
Everly
What does somebody want to know
Flags me go print that out right now
Trigger
I'm going to print out whenever the button mask gets altered
Sue
So now analog trigger but watching I get it really close
When I get it on there it sets the trigger for button mask one
I like to go sit back 20
So when I click it it's what mask one and they use but math for this so that if I like touch this
Like to touch it
It's too if I press hard it sets the button mask for 4
4 + 2 is 6 so if I touch it and
Click
Little bit more
I'm so that's how that works there's also this up here
Kiss me a butt mask of
20 hack
The steam button is 08 hacks
There's the funky thing on the side here that's 10 hacks
Maybe there's another button here that I don't know about I keep finding things I didn't
No Justin
There's any other questions feel free to just say to the chat there's enough people around here watching it that will
Alert me to it
Really big window
People are
Probably or something oh
Okay well I could but it's it's difficult for me to
People around here telling me what the hell you guys are talking about and chat first of all
Get back real quick for the the lightweight portion
By writing everything in see now
It makes it so that you can then use it in more situations
Much more easily where is when you start off with something it's already designed be heavyweight then you might run
Situations where it's not a viable option
And I've run is that a lot
So because you know what I did my Minecraft on an AVR slide and absolute minimum
Porting at any other system was instantaneous very easy basic C code
Very tightly written
Works everywhere I kind of want that for this
What did you say
Maybe
Laptop not be
Okay hold on let me switch that out then
Explanation of
What happens when you start with C + +
How see if it's still
Now
Okay
Okay tell you what I'll do I'll shrink this even smaller and then
Hey it's really small okay yeah this is a pretty slow laptop so that's one of the reasons
Everything good okay
Can you see all of the little
Right here
Is it still visible
Like you as a person camera and slide of the
Okay good good got it
Back to the CC plus plus thing
So the way when I do my engineering if I can and I have the time and I have the wherewithal I was
I want to make everything that I work on as small as possible as tight as possible so that I can be used elsewhere
Absolutely crazy that I would want to plan for this project to be small and lightweight besides the obvious this is a slow computer
Peter and I want to shave off every possible microsecond I can be able to spend those microseconds on other things
Like rendering
I do have some longer-term plans for this project
But those are just pie-in-the-sky plans so I'll just leave that there
I really like the just a personal thing
All of the dependencies the actual reason they got me doing this instead of using one
Existing systems was because I ran out of data on my cell phone plan trying to get all of the
Dependencies of the project for what I needed so this is Tiny that's the way I'm going
No no ASCII okay
Moving on so we had the button masks those worked out
Happy scoot this one over the other workspace to mask the wrong controller
Going all is well
And so I was able to finally get all that figured out I found out some other information about the masks in the way that they were working
In all that I do need to go update those project moving on now
I'm going to go comment out those print statements and I'm going to get to the Crux of what I
Got to make that always on top now going to get to the Crux of what I want to do today
I don't know if I'm going to able to do it but it's my goal
So I can decode everything that I really need right now I don't actually decode all
Old Lighthouse data but I don't think I need it for what I'm working on all of the lights
To come and get the headset but the one thing I can't do and I can't do it as of right now so you guys forgot
Just give it a shot and see if I can make it happen cuz I can't read the light data from the I cried I spent quite a while
I've been complaining to people online I tweeted a little bit earlier today
Symcode these right here which looks like nobody took to trying to see
Figure out what it was of what I'm getting back how weird
This is a closed off some of these extra tabs
So if
Now
I have down here I'm going to display anytime data comes in for this thing that I do
Don't know what it is then I'm going to display a message I'm going to display a little bit of text
So Mandy right now is going to turn on the two lighthouses and we'll see
Nothing started freaking out yet
Lighthouses are coming online
They're online and there's the data complete craziness this is totally
Crazy this thing right here is receiving data from the lighthouses I'm just playing to the screen I have no idea
What any of that mean I spent hours and hours and hours and hours hours okay what like 10 hours
Pouring over it and and I got nowhere
So let's take a look at what some of this looks like and I'll explain to you guys how I started playing with it and
Shrink the font hear some and
Why it's so hard
The most data whenever you're playing with it when you look at their the date of reverse engineering it
You'll start to look for patterns so if I instead of printing this
I just print all data that's coming in
Chanel
What turn the phone off
Nice enough to take this controller and put tape over it over everyone of the
Surfaces so that it it won't receive any when I power it on since it's not receiving light
Like data I can look at this and someone asks you how like you can do basic reverse engineering with this sort of thing right now
I'm streaming through data coming from it and if I click something you'll notice that the code right here
Changes who's I change the analog values that changes so when I change something I speeded the B chain
I know that it had something to do with that end in the same thing for this overtime this
Number here is incrementing and this number here is somewhere else here is incrementing overtime
And being able to kind of see these patterns helps you have an idea as to what's going on Princeton Simon
Well when I hold it like this this column right here reads f-zero but when I do like
Sbcounty read 0f that's kind of interesting and they would look at
Just call him over and they'd find out there's correlation they're here look at that there's correlation and by looking at
Those fields you can kind of figure out how they get used and how each part of that like goes to
Picture has
Question
Okay then if you
If you want to help out here
I'm not really sure of a good way of communicating while I'm live streaming I don't have a s desktop but
There are people here that if you want to go like startup Ascot Elsewhere on the email or something to be really cool
Any rate let's go and look at the light data
I'm done right now are all supposed to cover all of the sensors are covered
Do all of that was just the raw data right now because all of the centers are covered
I thought it didn't update or whenever Hamilton takes recovered do I change the code so that it would dump
All the data that comes in now it's only dumping date of the screen but it doesn't know what to do with
So if I go expose this I right here see that
New data open the I now there's tons of data so
This like data is a little bit harder to figure out what is because instead of it fitting into some sort of nice
My smol like all of the other data well the lines are different lengths but you can see sometimes too
But the lines are this long and sometimes their lifelong
Now there's no B there if I change the orientation. There's more B there so we're clearly
Was it clearly cuz I don't know or really dealing with but it looks like we're dealing with something where these records aren't of stable size
Now there's a little bit of an annoyance in it because the data coming from the all the lighthouses is
Complicated there's the long Paul and there's the streak
Comes by so one thing I tried doing last night was jiggering up the
Little law
Aviall right here with a little LED on it and black
Homelite in pattern that I would be able to see
Concerning I don't know why it's not lit right now
OK Google still working
So what I'm going to do right now is instead of having a situation where I can't control tool
Life is going into the controller because it's coming from the lighthouse over there and up there I'm going to go with her
And then we're going to use Blissful aviar right here in order to actually light up the
Different sensors on this controller
Steamvr Depot
Can he post a link that publicly
Can you pull up for me
What will start reverse engineering this stop and just somebody just you know
Early it anyway I'm going to turn this controller off
And this one on
And now I'm going to use this I'm going to hold it up to the little light right here
So now when I hold it up I can actually see data that is predictable
So now I can control my source
And I can control properties about the source and see how that changes the output
Now I will say that I currently do not know
What's really going on here, as far as what these b mean but until somebody else
Start digging through this
I don't know
Brandon are you on the trail of trying to get the info
Well we have our our people here working on it right now to see if this entire video
We will see
Working on the problem inside here though I have an EGR codes
ER that's running on the floorboard right here and I'm going to edit test. See
By the way as soon as the people who worked on the documentation for this for like of course it's not going to
Lightened up in Plano
Wizards for killing that
I have a VR code and what I do is I turn the LED on
That takes two cycles I subtract one from marker which I believe is a registered this point I'm sets one psycho
Can I turn the port back off and I have a while to go back up which I just now read
Realize it is less than 2 MHz I should probably
Optical
Value
Call make it work better
Chelsea
They actually know that that's the case
Heart
Said that the person who wrote The Firm or for This Guy's in the chat room so if you want to just like string me along a little bit little bit
Not too much would be kind of fun but
Yeah okay
Whatever let's start messing around with this
So that would be zero a that's still a little hot so it is actually 1.8 MHz
By the way do you mind if I, the stuff publicly like
This is going to be about 1.8 megahertz turns out
That's probably better than the two megahertz suggestion from the lighthouse
Redox people
Any rate you can see that now when I take this light right here and I hold it up close to the the thing
Boom after getting the data all is fine and well
Some of the more important things now though is the data doesn't look completely random anymore I'm starting to get a little
More
Information about what's going on you can see that the first value is 0 x 5
The second I use A1
Select a different light like this one right here sensor
For this one
This one this one this one any of these you can see that now I can tell which led or which photodiode it is that is
Being hooked up to
So what's going on
So now I'm going to try to make it longer
Instead of only being on and off for five Cycles which is
908 55 1.8
X
48 MHz
Where's
Should I switch to programming mode
Cono
Out here is
About 85 so I don't know why that's so
Says a one so maybe a one is actually not what I think it is but what I'm going to do is I'm going to make it turn on for a little
Bit longer so one extra cycle on off on off on off
One extra one I'm so to take slightly longer and I'm going to reburn the firmware
So now 3 burning
When I go back over here
Hold it up to the light
Now it says ba
Remember okay
Well I guess I'll make a little chart
Exercise Gerlach's
B3 before something like that
Five says oops
A1 A2
Hue
But the other thing is
One of the things that kind of funny about this
When the light brighter light the actual length of the pulse is
Is increased because
I don't know how Works internally I'm probably wrong and making a fool of myself but the signal from the analog circuitry is going to be going
Edgar pasta threshold earlier and leave it later
If the amplitude of the signal is higher
Today. I'm going to hold it to yourself to say it's about A9
Length of time
For everybody who doesn't know these are just hexadecimal values
They're they're just easier to use in programming more frequently cuz I can say like a
Represents the number 165
And it's easier to see in base
Like the 8-Bit B that we have cuz everything fits into two digits so that's why I use hacks
A lot plus try seven and see what 7 says
B1
C 0
Striate
Anything I need to know from the shop
Washing quick where you create him
Quick Square
Quey swarey quick Square
Please don't dmca me or something
Steve what you're not doing anything with so
Well I mean technically it's their Hardware so
Although I think I do remember how the DMC work for this I think this is actually legal cuz I'm so far black boxing most of it
Must be other docs were from people who didn't blackbox it
Switch case
I promise I'm doing this for the purpose of interoperability instead of marketing new
Products or something
I think I don't remember what are the rules surrounding that
D4
So you're at zero eight says you're xd4 so right now I can see with 7
Indifference
Between 8 and 5
Set 123
And I can say 0xd 4 - 0 x 89
D4 - 89 is to be
And the 2D hacks which is 43
Phase 10 and that means that the code that I'm receiving from the
Controller the thing it says 43 is 43 I'm guessing 48
Millions of a second because everything else inside this thing operates at 48 million for the 2nd
By the way this is a perfect time to plug the esp32 which I'm not getting any special treatment from Express
Estefan
I mean other than keeping me the parts a little early
The esp32 I just found out earlier this week in an example I can pull from up to 16 pin in
Parallel at 40 MHz not 4840
But you know start thinking about that
Charles I sent you a package of firmware has it been mentioned that they just come with steam VR
Can one of you guys open it I can't
Competitive
Okay I don't have I don't I don't really feel comfortable pulling it up on the livestream cuz I can't
Filter
I only have one display so
Mindy you're going to open it okay so somebody is is on opening it
Gmail
Okay so going to be opening that
So consider this might be all for nothing but let's just go through it anyway I'm going to keep going at this until the other stuff
Comes through
So what this says right here the 43 is that when I was running for five psycho
Then this thing thinks it was on for a 19 when I dated thought it was D4
Which means that it was 43 more 48 millionths of a second
Per thing per cycle so I'm probably a higher frequency than I should
We can actually calculate that out
So if it's 43
Switch to decimal
Bye-bye 48 millionths of a second
Education background
I have a regular degree from UMBC and I went back for my masters
In what
Oh I went to school specifically for computer engineering
And then I decided I wanted to do gamedev
So I went back for
A master's in computer science
And I decided I didn't want to do game data so I went back to hardware
That's Story of My Life
Scientific automatic how to do that
.895 9
I really want to watch
Start with USA protocol been Jackson's name
From where
But I already know most of the USB protocol
I'm a little confused by the statement been Jackson's making with regards the USB
Xavier is compression arcane
Not modern well
There can't be very much compression because
I can see a pattern emerging so it can't be
Not much really odd because I don't
They follow pretty clear B pattern
Especially men.
Where Point fired those are his messages from the wireless dongle
Wired USB protocol
Oh no that's been very well-documented and it's
Zero-interest me I specifically want the wireless protocol
The wired one appears to be from what I can tell almost identical to this
As far as what the messages are for the light information I'm pretty sure it's pretty well-documented in the lighthouse redox stuff
I can pull it up
Although if you want to give me some details about with his Arcane compression is that be pretty cool
Pitot tube
I guess they haven't
Time length
Sensor ID so it's almost identical to this I got to just uses 8 b b packets instead of 7 to describe
Dissenters
So I'm not really interested in having this wired all the time
Moving on so maybe in the background you guys will give me the stuff to do the thing
Right now I will keep on showing people how I reverse engineer cuz that's kind of the purpose of this video
So 43 until right now when I'm trying to figure out its what is the actual clock rate of this
Little Flashing LED right here
And so it's going to be 43
Units
And that's 4348 millionths of a second
Which is 89-59 of a wavelength
2.6 MHz that's a little bit too hot
See what happens if I drop it to that
E1
That's weird why would that be faster
Maybe I am running into compression thing
He won the firmware for the controller
I guess
I'll be looking into the VR controller
So this one is now
B5
Okay so I just did the same thing I did up there so
1 - P4 is a total of
194 total of 45
Do iguanas that's a little bit fast let's try 70
Oh that's interesting it's a text that the signal lot further away so totally believe that my frequency was little bit too
U-high
The right now it's a sick
If we bump that up to eight
So it'll make it last longer and we'll see what this second value is right here
Who's that says C
App cbspd
Hello
Set 37 total difference
Picking my division is wrong
1.2 9729
I'm thinking this might not actually be the time I was expecting it what's up let's crafthouse more data points
So you did
Hopefully this thing on a little bit longer let's leave it on for 16 total cycle zero x 10
The state says
Who
That's interesting now it says
So what my guess is but now I realize it's a large enough number that it needs to expand the next digit
Cam so this is this is a little concerning
That means that this is actually a longer string now because that was those different so these are not fixed
Fields
In the string
So let's see here
Are you in the folder
Define Aristo
Xbox One
I need a little bit
Say
Watchmen dongle. Bin
Pi +
I could do this on this laptop
No
Can you make sure that you can you mix with USB drives empty before
Trying to herd a copy the data
Certainly not empty
Okay
I don't care if you see what's on it I just don't want the internet
I don't know I left some light company stuff on there
I'm so right now going to soon look at the inside of a binary from valve here it gets this
Attributed with the vibe
What start taking a look at what some of these other ones
Don't even have a primary doctor
But I'll still take a look at him
Maybe 20 other files
Did he attack Senator okay so right now I'm in here is going to be digging through the firmware with
With the hex editor and seeing if she sees anything that would be
Clear enough for us to figure out what's really going on
So if I put out your ex 10
I got
A little bit left but I was 15 let's try 15
Hold us up
Cold
A101
Hey what is the
What is the tea taste like
Awesome
We've been trying to figure out all this is at
Who trying to figure out a necktie Ice-T for a while now and we're starting to zero in on the recipe
Anyway
That's 15 you at 14 looks like
I'm trying to fill in the table here figuring out what all this means that's 9501
Coldest up again
Holding it up
9:08 Fe
Interesting
Okay so right now we're right on the edge
If I hold it like this
Then it reads f f e r f f
Whoever get the f f f f
Just wright
It'll read 8
You have a request to copy paste a couple lines from the
Debunks fuel in the chat just for other people too
Okay okay so let's do that interesting data set
Because we were able to get it to go from both this size right here
To this size right here so I'm going to do is I'm going to post this
Let's do that right now
GitHub
I don't think there's anything
Okay doesn't show the private project
That would have been nervous anyway
So right here this is
Controlled environment with LED right on edge
I don't actually know the absolute length of time
Pretty good though
HTC Vive example data files
Recorded a little bit earlier
And they're not there
I'm going to have to record that data can get your hands on some of this data start playing
I will start recording it I'll go power on the lighthouses again
Oh okay so this is specifically if you go
Look at the
Okay if you look at my code I don't know where it is in the other people code right now I handle
Handoff all of the
Where is it
So it's under survive data
Hilton survived a to call back
When you get data from The Watchmen this thing right here
If it has an ID of 35 and he calls it just once but if the idea is 36 there's actually two,
Copy or two separate messages
In the same packet so that's how it knows to go call
They handle the Watchman for the 29 B packet can handle Watchmen
All this code is on my GitHub right now
I guess I could make a push you guys can check it out under a live survive
We had to pull earlier that lube survive or live survive I made it I'm calling at light survive
Just like gifts they were gifts but now you gave them the man gave them to the internet and we
Decided call them gifts
Like when you get a child you can rename them I don't know if that's a practical thing to do but maybe it is
Anyway
There's that data not good so now we have kids coming in on this thing so right now what I'm going to do
I'm is I'm going to by the way
After I have parked out everything I know how to parse out all of the triggers all of the buttons all of the IMU
I'm pretty sure this is just like data I'm going to take this I'm going to go put it on the ground over there
And I'm going to go collect some data and dump it in that just for you guys
By the way the whole thing about that was totally Adams
Line
Sun logging some data right now
Who made all this wonderful day that you guys can go have fun with this
Okay I'm going to
Guess I could can I log into Twitter's that have anyting Twitter
I thought it
Do you want me to open some windows computer sending people that
Moschino it
Here's
Comdata
Calm the livestream
So if you're watching this right now and you want to go play with the data just get it from my Twitter
I just commented
And while I'm here
She probably
How do I get
The URL of my
How to get the URL of this live stream
Can you tweet that to me
Mural
Worry about that a minute
Call the complete with all these crazy
And if you guys can parse it awesome so we're going to start actually maybe getting a little bit feedback from you guys soon
That is assuming the
The reverse-engineering the binaries is not going well we'll find out about that in a few minutes
What's the strongest power off the lighthouse
I'm responding to your sweet summer
Watch the live stream here
I think it's public right everybody would Co know people who
I would have to tweet it out for other people to see it right or did they see that the chain
I think everyone's just tweeted to me and probably good enough
Tweeted out again later so here we go back to what we were doing this thing here just
We found an interesting bit where
The thing took up two values instead of one
Ha
We happening at happens monotonically that is that this led is going poop for a fixed period of two
It's going into
Good thing right here
And it's showing that number so now I'm just curious I just want to see what it looks like
Say 10 microseconds again what happened
I just I don't know let's find out what happens if I poop twice so now I'm pooping
Wants to see the LED waiting 10 microseconds and I'm pooping again
So see what this looks like
That's cool so now we're getting a longer day to message
And the boot data looks confusing to me
That's really confusing
So if you look and see if I can touch this with my
So I can use the computer with my toe
You look
Weird
He look where we still have the the fa fa if I go high enough
Somehow there is 8001
And that's around the same time I don't see anything like that earlier here
I wonder what's up with that so icy
08:08
Oh
You know what we forgot to do
Got to reset marker so this Firstmark what happened was it would start and then it would subtract
Marker 12 times it was only a very short period of time
Then when marker was zeroed keep executing down here and have a really long ball
So let's reset it to both pulses are about the same length of time
We're getting the same behavior we saw before
Where we would have between
To go between F9 sff all that when I go over-the-top it would go up to
1301 the same thing here
People saying to explain yourself I don't know exactly what they mean by that but
Causing your little thing to send a signal to make the LED years ago
Seeing something
Okay so Adam has pointed out that we discovered set up I'm going to go try to increase the resolution
Hopefully it doesn't explode
See
320 by 2:40 Maybe
Explain how the LED is. This one of the, okay let's do a few things I'm home
Hoping the stinky pufferfish
5 right ear I have all of the lighthouses turned off
Both of the lighthouses
Table up to this right here which is an 80 to 85
Kind of produce from spark I love them they're great
But I don't really care
AVR microcontroller
What to do things I have literally connected this led to controller and I can turn the LED
With this command and off with this command and when all of his code gets compiled to
Two AVR code it
It bit off
It'll take literally one or two clock cycle operations and so that's why turns
Turn on subtract marker turn off turn on marker turn off
Whatever MHz
About
And point that at the thing that originally this it all started with the whole LED thing
This thing right here
LED is flickering a high-frequency but it's flickering if the frequency that's necessary to read it into this thing
So
Is this correct
This up to it
I might get like a thing through here and there but it's it's really hard to to read where is now
Frequency
Consider the data coming through
That is deliberately far away
Developers just told us that that the reason that this thing has to operate is the one
Waymaker hurts is because it's really far away and frequency space from these guys which operated 38
I mean I guess they can go to 56 but down it like below 64 kilohertz 1.8 MHz
54 khz that's why this doesn't hose up your system if your you have a remote control and
Oh my gosh did you guys imagine a TV be gone for 5 to take a TV be gone in flash it with the drive
Xbox one anyway
Let's go back to what we're actually doing over there
Searching through the binaries
I seen some plain text that says something about dolls bootloader
Nothing
Revolver
Mindy's right now going through the binaries the firmware binaries that are distributed with the the Valve controller
And none of them look like they're playing text or anything
Something bracelet
Weiser meant to be able to have multiple operating in the same space
Are they
I don't know I just realized I didn't have the camera on that whole time
There's Mindy and there is her there's your code
So she's right now looking through the binaries in HEX editor
Trying to look for any kind of
That's not it
Are these ones here
The various. Bin files that come with
I'm in the firmware here is why I unzipped from the guy from we're here so
City on that screen
Oh really I don't know bummer
File strings
And strength to look for strings inside of a binary Brendan was talking to me and saying to use
Unix file to look for strings inside of a binary I've never done that
How about how about Brendan goes in
But looks for some reason
YouTube friends over there and he's suggesting
Start working on looking at the binaries to I just thought of is
Is anyone going to tell me what what processor these things use cuz maybe we can just get a copy of like one of the arms will kids
Disassembler on that assembly then
I'm not wasting my time trying to figure out what the assembly does
Go back to the Daily Grind here
What I'm going to do is I'm going to I'm going to see what is 12
12 is
Act weird
Stressing this is actually really interesting but I see is icy 080
08 FC 8201a 501
Something is a 201 in a 501 look like they're almost the same number
Which is really interesting
So I would think maybe it's the value twice
So I'm seeing right now some seeing 0808 which maybe like which
Which sensor is so I 2020 08 08 maybe that first coat is which sensor I don't know what the
Tsp is right now but I do see that the that the length of time that the pulse is on
Twice
In a row so that that that leave me to really start thinking about that
Let's go back and let's start documenting this
If you guys think of something you'd like to talk about on the video it's some point whenever you get to find something
So by having the pulse happen twice like 301 a 6in 0183
Give me a heads up as to what these fields mean so right now what I could do is
But the thing is is I'm sorry whoops Oda 201
It's non-paid 601 what happens if I speed
BB's Apso make this say 15 + 15
Compressor that's interesting
There is no such thing as USB compression
He said Arcane right
Maybe it's I don't know what he meant by compress
You can't compress the data and put it in a packet
Done said now you figured out 08080 give you an important tip basically
Starting after the away to wait on one going in reverse
Can you let me go okay I'll do it live here
Okay what do I do
Okay so it's been Jackson shirt is the first part would probably kill you trying to figure it out
Screw up once one starting after the 0808 and one going in reverse from
End
90 now fool 90 people
What variable length
Oh okay everything after those 0808 is to variable-length fields of data
Already knew about the only do anything last night I just had no idea anything else beyond that
Okay and I keep going
Okay so I can compare these two lines so
That's interesting fc01
9 fo1 and FC
I make no sense why is that if I do in there
This is really confusing
Those two lineup those two lineup
Maybe this is a time offset like in time after that happen this happened
Let's test that
Twice Mina
How does that work is that picking up at it up from his room
We're both teams in the video
But he said Hot Spring Point than I am
Oh okay
Okay
Let's let's try to increase the delay time between these two
I don't necessarily news-washington module but it is Watchmen
Open Smart fan module in Washington Seattle jungle
I got to know how in the world did this Ben guy know that the channel is going on
He said earlier
He said finally something useful showed up in his feet about that considering all I'm doing is just tinkering
At 15
At 10 US between so first
Numbers about the same second number is larger
Third number is about the same
So what this says to me is first number is we have a sensor codes
First number is pulse time second number is
Oxy pulse * 1
Just probably
Call Ira
Length of time between pulses and pulse time to
Okay let's test that
Instead of using your body shotgun am actually like doing the scientific method
Tshaka meaning change
Now I'm actually changing only one variable at once increased the start time here and make this
20 Cycles
Message for you Ben Johnson
Can You Stand The Rain I don't even know whatever
Oh Jackson why did I say constant whatever okay
Now we're doing it with the increasing the spirit. Of time to the first one and see how that changes to stream
Hey that looks pretty good that was real
Really good so if you look between these two
The difference between these two streams right here this one and this one is that this one increased
The marker time a little bit so means that for the first one to pause a little bit longer and so the only things that she
Change the substance in the first part of which is all looking at right now is that it went from a-001
The da01 and for the second one it went from its got the same for the third one is about the same
So now just to check my logic here I'm going to try changing the length of time of the second Paul and see if this number here
Boom
How got home the firmware
Halt this is really good data oh my gosh yes so now we
We did at twenty at 20 at 10 u.s. between oh my gosh
We're we're cooking so what we have here is code 1co to
And this is definitely so it's sensor codes it's definitely Paul's Time 1
Link between impulses time to
Vetoed what is that number what how do I figure out what that is in absolute terms so I'm going to do is win
Microseconds between text and see what that goes down by
Hope it still give me data
But I don't know if you want I can probably just like tape
Just to hear but probably just put it on the floor but I can't hold it up and see you guys every time
Cell
Ed bringer
So this is concerning
I don't know how to tell the difference between this and this
So clearly they're doing something to make it to the the width of the variables the width of the number
Numbers can be variable but I don't know how to tell how many
Bite each thing should take
How am I
I'm going to tell that tell you what I'll do
What would they have done the developers what would they have done all my allowance for a solve this
You want him to keep spoiling it for us I really want to know though how do I
Tell how many bytes given field is going to take
I guess we could do is we could scan across a variety
Let's let's go back to the most degenerate case for one pulse let's go back to 21 pulse
Cheilosis test it
Hookah shop
That's da01
If you guys have something for more wise at some point soon that would be really helpful so I can take a break
No nothing it just looks like trash
Uh what you say Brandon
Do you have anything interesting you want to talk about
There's more spoilers okay
Talk about how you're thinking about using the Kalman algorithm Kalman filter to figure out the locations of stuff
If you wanted to talk about that at some point
Okay if you want to think about it over the next couple minutes I don't need to I don't need to
Break right now but
Talk about like the sympathizer which technically is the Charles Moore
That's okay looks like
E2
Did it nicely asset
What's up is the Watchman dongle. Been
That can't be right that must be the wrong processor
So right now I'm Mindy is visible
She's right now opening the binary in a tool that can decompile 4D assemble it
But these assembly codes don't exactly mesh fence
Maybe they are maybe they're not sometimes when you reverse decompile
Program into the wrong processor and even can look like a real real coats
Funny story where somebody took and they put it through at 8 8051
Decompiler perfectly there was Zero undefined things
Except for this like one place that looks like maybe they were using that
And they realized that the 8051 opcodes have no opcodes that aren't opcodes and
Reverse engineer something
The dongle is 8051 is he just messing with me why would a dongle be 8051
Actually let's Google that
This is Cyprus part in there
Apod
There's no way
Why would it be
Someone else mentions the 24 hour
Whatever
Yes the all you that wasn't 8051 in there
Interesting choice for
Now I'm kind of curious do you have an fpga on board that does the timing for rent round-robin
Not round-robin like check when any of these get hit and then that report soft piano riff 24-hour one
And Nordic wifi chip that does the the other part actually
Another one I wonder if this is protocol compatible with the nrf24 l01
Easy to make your own dongles anyway
Turn down five
Whatever I don't even need to know that since if you're saying that it's the Nordic chip it's probably
Free music
If you somebody tells you something doesn't do USB they're just not trying hard enough
Go back to this now
Da01 is that how do we know why
When we advance to the next fight
Started at the wrong place I don't know if it changes anything
Where is there a way to change that actually we have to be different processor
How do I
Different disassembly
He wanted his number I don't know that maybe there is
Now I'm so back to this back to actual reverse-engineer protocol here
E2 and then another variable so I don't know what these are how did quite tell when
When one thing would go on to the next
So this is
Hot tongue
He won
U2
I know what we are I'm just going to take this together
Where is the Gaff tape
Dave do you think you'll be ready to talk about it briefly in a couple minutes
My magic my magic the paperclip
Darn
Okay
Okay so I'm going to right now tape this thing to hear so I only have to use the keyboard to iterate through the site
Cycle
If you want instructions during an earthquake
But I would really like it if some program
Just took it and reverse-engineer it for me
And even then
I don't have a copy of Ida
Hi whatever I'm going to keep going
Okay so weird 11
11 is 9
12 is F5 at 6
And I don't even care about the rest of that I'm just kind of trash that
Call what's 213
13 is 8201
How World am I going to tell the difference
Maybe I'm just not looking low enough
Tryon
Hi going lower
Whatever
Is there more to the name 8051
No
Drawing games
I was going to go back so Mindy found
Online decompiler here
Public under architecture
Lookers just like a lot of fun
Cedar cubby something that's xt285
8051 8051 traditional
Asem 51
Open source tools
Someone else online set
Somebody said asem might be a good online source
And that also looks ancient
Freeware program for MS-DOS okay
Let's keep going here so
Let's see what 93 is burn
A7
I'm going to make it really low
I don't even know if that'll trigger
Now 3 is not enough to make a trigger
Motorcycles for enough to make a trigger
Now for is not 5
Now
Changing the frequency
Haha that's what it is a little bit lower made it more sensitive
Back to four Cycles
No still nothing
So right now I'm changing the clock rate on the part
Right there with that little bit weird that that's
Anyway
I'm changing the clock rate see if I can find a clock rate where the part is more susceptible to
Receiving the signal
That looks like no
Okay looks like 5 is the shortest pulse I can actually generate
The ideas are flooding in
Make a Super Nintendo adapter to play Star Fox with the five
Esp32 Scott a little more power than you think although I don't think I can hook an HDMI cord up to it what that did
Stop me to try to figure out if I can hook a PCI Express Port up to it
Hey so five
It's also kind of interesting
So one thing I'm just now noticing is that so
What I'm seeing in the first column is even though sofive Cycles
20 Cycles
10 Cycles I would expect
Like these numbers to be significantly larger so maybe what happens is there's some minimum number so like
The number 80
Port 80 hacks
Represent 0 in this number and see maybe I don't know
And
As the number grows bigger and bigger and bigger
Stover
Then it goes into the next column
And so zero in the most significant bit might be and I
A mechanism to indicate a termination that's just a guess though
Alexander suggest that HDMI is just fancy ethernet we already have that so
How far to go HDMI is not fancy ethernet
Least it's not fancy 10 pasty ethernet which I know how to do it so although to be fair that you have P30
T2 can output to
100 MB ethernet
Can't wait to get that fired up
Let's see here it's a da01
If there's another interesting thing under new situation if I noticed that the first number here
Has the the most significant bit set 208 means it's a 5 Dae
29 at 5 they're all more than 127 so
Maybe that's actually the factor maybe the compression maybe it's really that simple maybe that
Look at the first bit the most significant bit and if the most significant date is A1
Then this is the number
If it's not a one it's a continuation
Of the previous
So
That would mean that
First of all I don't even know if the last four B here used
Academy Annapolis 5 b here used
They hard to tell there
I'll probably do you think you have a I got to I got to take a break in the night
So unfortunately don't have my chicken scratch with me but
So we're going to take a break but the streams going to keep going
David Chapman here he's going to go show you guys with his ideas are on how we're going to take this and collapse
Into resolving with nothing more than the light and the IMU
Where the headset is and where the controllers are so I'll be back in a couple
Alright everybody David Charles
Friends
Development projects and things like that for a while and I had some idea
He is on the common filter and right now
Family ideas in chicken scratch on my notebook I started writing some code
And unfortunately don't have most of my chicken scratch with me so I've been frantically
The last five minutes or so trying to write down some of it
But
These are people okay
These are the equations for a common filter
Right now we have
Xhat which is the very first I can't come
Can't really see but if you look at the very first equation
Exit
Has to contain all of the information that you have about the
Position of a center I need to contain the orientation
And then this is your prediction
Given that the position is a certain thing I'll give him the orientation I given the velocity of the Excel
Alteration all of that has to be crammed into your ex hat term you have a linear model what you play
Probably learned in it if he took office it's 101 that position
Equals x KT + V not t + 1/2 80s
If you just keep things simple in terms of your state Vector that would be
Be a linear combination where the teacher in your time term is not a part of your state
Time has only to do with the length of time for particular time step so your your time term
Quick change from frame-to-frame that's okay the last turn the BX plus you
K that has to do with some external process control in the state which I don't
Think we'll have to deal with it not down below we have the covariance Matrix
I'm so if you have some uncertainty in terms of what your position is
If you were to take that uncertainty
You have a standard deviation that's one thing but yet other the variance is the square of the standard deviation
Let's generalise az2a covariance Matrix if you have a multidimensional array
I'm so if you were to take the outer product of a matrix with itself that would be a way of describe
Having the covariance Matrix around for awhile
One of the things that the little bit tricky figure out which term
For the particular model that you have and then how do you plug
How do you plug
Numbers into these matrices how do you build these matrices that actually math onto the fence
Countries that we have and one of the things that's interesting about this
Steve lights the lights sweep down and then they sweep across and then another one Suites
And then it sweeps across actually get
Angle measurement what the true position of of
After you know I guess 3 years 2 or 3 sweeps
You might be able to construct where the position is if it's worth staying completely
He's still but the thing is that it's not going to actually stay still so if you sweep is 30
Is 30 Hertz then by the time you have a third sweep you even would have already moved to another
Position that you have to incorporate your I owe you and your accelerometer data
You have very different-looking data sets that you have to fuse together
The you're not getting a true sense of the position all you're getting is constrain
That the position is on a plane at a particular point in time so when we have a light flash
Flashing like this there is a describe
View of a lighthouse and if that hissed sensor
Above win that measurement was recorded
I'm kind of starting from the standpoint that out of all of that we already have a plane equal
The figure out from two lighthouses what are the positions in orientations of lighthouses
Just from the positions the point I think that is a pretty well-known problem in
Computer vision but I haven't really thought about that assuming that
Calibrated then we would need to just from the known position
Assuming we have
A plane equation and then we would need to stay at this point in time
We know that the sensor is close to this plane
And that plane is the plane that's formed by the angle of the
Of the beam of the Lighthouse at the timestamp
Observe the sensor
Sounds like I'm talking at my ass I probably am because again was still kind of initial ideas
And realize it didn't quite work
This is what I'm thinking at the time and kind of what I'm trying to go on so
My initial thought in terms of how do we construct a state vector x-rite
Yeah the first the most important thing as a state Vector X
How do we construct that state Vector my initial thought which could change if
If you're not I haven't really I've implemented a toy common filter before
But you know this will be definitely making something
That's that's really really viable and again I could be talking out my ass when I say this coming up but
My first thought is that in a common filter is effusive linear algebra
Linear algebra we need to have matrices and in particular we want
To be able to a lot of these steps in the formulas that we have have a stinger
Single Matrix X representing Steph and so
Different ways of representing a rotation you could use a quaternion you could use an accent
Angle you could use three Euler angles
But my initial thought was that if we want to represent a rotation using a
Single Matrix X then I'm thinking that
Haitian Matrix might be a good format to know the right
The right Peg for the right hole again that that might invite
Not to be a problem because a matrix of rotation Matrix
Has nine terms and it only really takes three terms to represent a rotation
Could be that the system is under constrained in ways that could make a problem I think more than life
Likely I think it won't be a problem because a lot of what you describe
Here are covariance matrices so representing
In fact that the Peter here that the second equation is a covariance matrix on position
And also in terms of our uncertainties we can say that certain
Turn the linearly dependent on others so I'm thinking that there might be a way that we could encode in our insert
Certainty Matrix that even though there are 9 terms some of them are our Coral
Or actually identical to each other so so that's
That's the first thought thought is that we need to have position velocity and acceleration so
My initial thought it said if we need to represent all three of those again this is really chicken scratch
But we need to have 12 terms for the position
3 for each of the columns of the rotation Matrix the rotation Matrix really represents a
AAA coordinate system and maybe a quaternion would work better because it would only be for
4 * I'll have to think about that little bit more whether quaternions are used with common filters or
Rotation Matrix seems like the most obvious thing to do but you need to have 12 terms
For each of position velocity and acceleration so so that would be
12 * 336 36 terms if if we win you know that route
Reasoning that's what the state of one you know headset is at the time
Now one thing that I was thinking about is that if we
We have this common filter in the update space we need to determine
We need to determine a number of matrices just why I hear this has to
To do with the error residual
Residual in measurement
Are your observed measurements at a time Steph K and on the right
Trx4 is your predicted state
And then each year is a matrix that transforms your state into
Measurement
Abs abs observations minus calculations we have our observe measurements and
Then we have to calculate what do we expect those measurements to be and if
If we can do that then the long story short is that
You have to plug that into this magic formula we're really this are termed
Represent your uncertainty in measurements and we need to ask tomates somehow
Uncertainty in measurement
From the sensors that we have and that's something and I I'm not sure how much
There's documentation on how accurate these sensors are with her we have to measure that by just
Empirically from moving them around and seeing you know how how
How how uncertain the measurements are but so that that's something we'll
I'll have to look at and and if you do that then I belong
Long story short is that is that you can
Invert that Matrix an estimated comandini commongame will tell you how
How much of your next state estimate should come from observation versus calculation
So one other tricky thing how do you integrate a plane equation
Into a common filter
And I think that'll be the last thing I want to talk about because that's that's kind of the treat I mean
But this plane
Equation where you only have you don't measure the whole position you only measure part of the position
I'm so what I was
A plane equation in all of that and that is because what's going on
And so if I have the controller here and it seems sweet
By the laser in the lighthouse then it doesn't it's going to get I got hit at this time I got hit at this time I got him
Where along the plane hit
Inside the planet was hit
So in order to resolve actual position you have to do this plane this plane and from another
And you know both when it hit here and this plane then all you get is equation for a line
The second Lighthouse to get the whole Interstate to where it is
Remember that we're dealing with planes not lying directly it's not like other computer vision systems
Correlate and have two cameras pointed at something and know the coordinate that the object whose that here all we know
Somewhere along this playing any given time
How do we how do we get that into the form of a of a common filter and I have
Diagram here is a really crude diagram there but you
Can see we have a lighthouse up at the top here and then we have a plane equation represented by normal
Plane equation is ax + b y + z z equals so that plane
Would have coordinates a b and c and ND for the for the plane now let's say we have
A axyz which is measured by
By that measured by that plane
The XYZ Starwood Bebe state would be would be the state so
If we have our state xhat right exit would have 36 terms
If we formulate it that way which maybe that's not the best construction but we'll have to play with it
We're allowed to construct a different a different
Observation Matrix every frame
It's at time stamp so that means that h2k -1
Could potentially be a different Matrix and h2k - 2
There is only one plane equation for the position of that leis of
That playing at that given point in time so we can actually put that into our
A matrix to convert
To convert our predicted State into the same format as our measure
And when I say the format is as of the measurement I'm talking about any format that would fit into the,
Filter that we can come up with some of the data that we received
The transformation to get it into a format that we can actually use in a common filter
Would just be a column Vector is if we wanted to go this route
Could just say that the normals of that plane would be equal
Perms
The product the matrix product of K
Be just a single point D and that point would so how far along
How far along is theft to the plane at at that
Given point in time in which we estimate the plan so so that would mean
That our measurement would be essentially how far along the normal the plane
Did we measure it and then our observation is how long of how far from the norm of the plane
Would be how far to the normal plane
Would our is our estimate XYZ
So we can kind of force that. Product to happen by putting it into our
Conversion from from the state Vector into a measurement space and I measure
It is just the distance to the plane to the particular plan that we care about at that point in time
So that would be give us a one-dimensional sreeja one-by-one matrix
And I pray for those of you who don't know the inverse of a one-by-one matrix is the reciprocal
So would be a lot more
Incorporating the IMU accelerometer data but for incorporating the plane equations
Are you can actually if it's if you can fit your most of the plane equation into just your
Matrices
Say is it's just a single dimensional object so we can constrain the point
Hopefully to the plane a little bit by by using that as a way of
Of as a data but not a data format FedEx but it is essentially a
A format that would be compatible with the equation of a common Soldier sleds that's kind of as far as I've gotten idea
DIYs I started writing some of the code but
How that goes and we'll see if if all these ideas can out of scripture fix the drawing board on some of them
That's that's kind of the long lines I'm taking right now
Hey guys so honestly
Kind of bad but I honestly don't understand all of the mathematics involved there
And I think it's really important to remember that when you do have opportunities to work with other people on team you'll
There are a lot of people who know a lot of things that you don't know a lot of people whose brains work in ways that yours
Doesn't and in most of what I do with like
Here's your pen
That that like at least electronics and all like I have a very very specific thing that I'm good at and I'm really only good at that
Almond so I really do rely heavily on other people to really come in and infill in those areas that I just can
I can't I would never be able to match this together I'm in fact in college I failed
Calculus 2 and calculus 3 and actually had a name in the computer engineering department I was called
Mathil so it is it is I'm just so glad that they've came along to
Stick through all this
I guess we should anything else or should we just get started again
Oh
And the discipline to go to the ATM but I don't know if I'm looking
51 +
Oh okay I'll just complicated
They said it might take a few run-throughs if you like going to control
Modify I think the original file anything different samples would eventually
Ugly like vomit beautiful thing beautiful
I still but
This is
I don't know man yeah I would not be able to
Figure out the algorithm
Call Ben was that his name
What was the guy's name from from valve in the Stream
How can I was texting the right quick
Suggested we look at the appreciate they're not encoded
Send someone
Encoding side is not in the dongle encoding side is not in the dongle
Okay
The dongle dongle
Then what
Okay anyway
What these things mean so first of all let's just see if this works out if I assumed
First let's just assume I'm going to assume here that all of these codes the light codes
R&R
I just assumed that for the light code numbers there also
It says whether or not it's the field Studio 1820
I'm going to make a prediction now and I'm going to say
40 what's a 440 microseconds that would be DEA - 80
15a
Hey * 2
Herbie
Oob 15 - 80
5A
Taste buds
So what
A VR a pulse for specific. Of time and going into the control
And I'm looking at what codes come back from the controller for those specific. Of time
So I have da01 is the code for however long
20 Cycles is and we're going to see how much 40 Cycles
My prediction is that will be 436 months we decode it so let's find out if that's the case
I make so we get ff7
AO3 right there at 8:03 let's see what that decodes to
So that would be if we decode that it would be F 7 - 80
Where's my calculator color is
Ab77
A bunch of binary data in the front
Are there particular instruction sets right like they mean something particular so what we're looking at here
Is the disassembled code Mindy what tool did you use
Right now running in Ubuntu on Windows get installed e52 I guess
Outkast shirts to make sure is there first but yeah it was there
And what we have is the location like this is a label basically
The label comes in the left-hand column
The instruction is the next one over in the parameters is the third column so if you see the one up there is
06:00 D7 that means that there's something in the code that jumped potential
Play 2 x 0 0 d 7 so I can function call or something like that
Yep that's how you find it
Yes but this is still very primitive and would be very hard to quickly reverse-engineer their Arkay
Cases where you have to dig through the assembly to do the reverse engineering
I'm making pretty good Headway with my side but right now we have two resources has absolutely no reason
Not working parallel
Okay well
Go for it
Fifteen52 disassembler specifically for the 8:51 and 8:52 I guess
Okay back to this estimated it should be 436 ticks but if
Use the metrics that I decided that I thought of it comes to 375
Text KT that's off by a lot I'm going to just try again
And I will multiply Again by 2
So I would guess
What's 375 * 2 that's 6750 750 I guess so what's * pi
By 2 that would be at 80
And I'm going to keep the LED flashing 480 Cycles
Okay I reprogram DVR and now let's see if that holds true
He 580 at 80 Cycles in my estimate would be
150 but let's see what the calculator says so I take 85 hacks
Reset the top it so that's just five and then
Is the second and that would be shifted over so that would be four
Which is that bit right there
I done wrong what's wrong for
No definite done something wrong
Call 1029
Okay that's interesting
No I don't think I'm decoding this right I think that I must be doing something wrong for me to be getting those
Kind of numbers
Not 1771 F7 hacks
1 after 7
500 okay that's cool my gosh that's a problem wrong
We're getting here what I'm doing
A right here in here which I believe represent the length of the pulse I'm trying to attend a different value because I can control
All the input I'm going to set them to different values and honesty with the output says so that's what I've been doing
And so right now I know for 20 units whatever that time unit is cuz I don't know exactly how fast patr
Cars going code is 0 1 d a d a 0 1
And my guess is that what these fields look like is in binary be term
E65 before b3b to
Do B10 and then the next byte is
Are sorry 7
1211 B10 b98
Yes that's correct so but I think is going on I see a number like 850
81 in binary
Get comfortable with it because it lets you figure these things out a lot easier cuz you can start to see the patterns
I'm stressed rather that's 8
And then I'm going to put in E85
And then I'm going to put it in here
Okay and so what I'm going to do is I'm going to move
I'm going to move it around so that I actually see how I have B 6 is 0 B 5 is 0 B for
0 B 302 is one that 100 is one
Calculator here and I'm going to see
This is just kind of a demonstration to show you what I think is going on I just think it was going to start a b 0
That's a 1 b 1
Is a 025 2234
Sticks are all 070809 a010 is 1
That one fit 10
No yes
So what did I do wrong why is that
I got really excited now I'm a little bit confused
Pulse timecode 1
8508 why did I think that was 1029
I have to be
I'm looking at the hexadecimal representation
1029 okay got it so I think that's what's going on
And so what I would do for two pulses we have that same sort of pattern going on
What I'm guessing is that at
08:08 so it's
LED aleda
Like a code wand
Total distance between Tech
Link the code to buy don't know what the remainder of these bites on this line are
How about what we just learned and implemented
It and see what we get
Oh actually you know what we should do first we should find out and see what three three bites look like
Let's make 333 pulses of equal length and mlc
What that looks like on the the output
Okay
So the output of equal length
Let's go and copy and paste these in and see what we get
Okay the 78 I think that's going to be the LED
Recorded on it
Or was it recorded on a different holiday
Okay what's record I guess I just wrote 08 I don't know why Road 08
Maybe I copied something wrong
Now I just copied something wrong
So what I think is going on is 78 78 78
Adidas LED this led
Can I think this is the length of the sensor 1 on time this is the distance between the Sun
This is the next Hunters on time
Link between sensors and this is the last sensors on time
That's weird I don't know why the first one to be higher than
Why would that be
After 0 0 1 and aa2002
Maybe the first maybe it's at the analog levels
I'll keep the first pulse on longer
Case altez F40 2020k neither really was it
B302 okay so let me get a piece of paper
Great
I just realized I don't think I monetized
Tan right now
Oh
So when I think is going to go on I think that
I think that what's going on is so we have a signal coming from the AVR and it's being pulse
Like this and what actually happens internally with the 5 I'm guessing it's a
But there's analog circuitry that looks that and create kind of a fall like that
What might be going on
And going down rising up and going
I'm down for shorter. The first one
Then the second one and so that might be why the first Halsted
Actually read it
That's just my guess
G302
C77
Distance between the pulses
I'm going to go in here and when I increase that number
So let's make it microseconds between pulses
What's that
32in so now instead of whatever it was before
E1 E2
So a4e 2030k
Now I'm curious what happens if
Make that even bigger let's make it big enough to trip over the the boundary
So now the numbers are bigger so now it's the first time
But now instead of the second number being whatever it's now 9401
Just into the file right now
So 78 78 78 B 302
Tete-a-tete
Four or however many numbers it is it could be like part of the CRC I don't know right now
We are going to have to figure that out though
My guess is so let's roll this back in
Bring it all back home
In here
And survived
If I can find it
Okay so when we get Watchman data
Handle the watchmaker
We pop off the date at the beginning of the packet the first bite is Time 1
I can fight it the quantity of ice that we're going to be dealing with
It is time to
For all of these time codes on the vibe actually has to have four bites in order to
Generate a full number of 48 MHz Hicks since the thing began so that means
Still looking for two more bites
And so that could be at least two of those at the end
So first of all
I'm going to go have to write something to parse out
The numbers as they are
And then we'll go from there so
Moisturizers another problem
I don't know how to know
How many of these there are how to tell the difference between 78
And the actual data was
I'll be things in the beginning 78 78 78
That's which LEDs have been triggered
All in our part of this this sorry which photodiodes have been triggered in her part of this message
Just when I saw some that were like 80 and stuff like that
The timestamp
I think it is a timestamp
Cuz we were missing two bites of the timestamp so
We have the first two but we still need two more
So that's possible and
The first the most significant here I'll show you guys this
The most significant to b b this one here in this one here you'll see that they actually keep counting up
But the problem is down here that the lower lower B
Are so sorry
Here here they count up
Toby 40 fb415 before 1B they keep counting up
And later on because we're down in the noise now I can't really directly observe with it
I don't have any way of knowing
Pencils are actually missing
3 what
I don't believe her
Missing three
Because isn't
I have 11 by here
I need
Two more bites right just
That makes
Big
Time thing
Okay
Three though
Ask him how big the timestamp is
Like attributes
I think it's time-stamped because if I start
Let me start starting right now
Right now counting down so
Starting
Right
Now I'm starting 9
I just realize I need a timer to
Starting when I goes
Oh whatever I'll stop at D2
I'm pretty sure I'm right about the second
B
Maybe I'm Wrong maybe that is
Jose that was 5.92 seconds
And that would be the most significant find out of a 4 B
B 1 b 2 B 3
And that bit right there
Success to death with you
Is also switch out of
Terrible mode
Automatic
Yeah there we go
/ 48
MHz
5.59 seconds and the number on my phone is 5.9
Second I'm pretty confident about that
From the beginning
So that's good moving on
Tell me what those two r's how do I tell the difference in person so let's let's find out
Going to take this off here I'm going to start pushing it on different ones and seeing what I see
That's that one
At 18
How do I tell the difference
Between an LED 88
And
A number the length of the first pulse so 88 x is greater than 128
So I don't know that it's an LED
Hehe rb8
That's significantly higher how would I know right there like it could bb8 and either way like
So here's an example where this all breaks down
There's something that I'm missing right here is a line where
The codes are bb-8 which is which voted on here I'm looking at and then I know these
Next to B are the time but how would I write a program that knows that means I'm missing some
Something I need to know how many LEDs are how many photodiode readings are being read in this message
I don't know how to do that right now don't know how to do that
How
How am I going to do that
Okay time to look at the rest of the data packet and let's see if we can get something from that
Semonite Now display the whole data packet
That didn't work why didn't that work
How did work
AAA
Day date
PA
Okay so now when I've done explain the whole data packet
And this one right here remember how 88 it means I don't necessarily know whether it's in
It is a Santa reading or if it's the first length of time that the sensor is on
Going to go look in this message right here and see if I can glean some information from this message to see
What I think it might be
My first of all it's it's obvious that we have
So this is the most significant fight
Of the time
S
This one right here is what I think is the length of the actual packet
This one is
The second the second next fight down and significance for time then
The LED codes
But there could be more that are exactly the same
I'm afraid to use the length of the packet tell me how many there are
Because what if
Ami packets are really big
Imagine you could have something where it was like
Start code
Very sorry
Free LEDs that each have very small values and that would be
34567 really long value
And they would take up more room so I don't know if I can trust
This right here to tell me how many pieces of data are in the message
How do I know that there's three
Pulses in this thing is anybody coming up with any helpful suggestions for this
Does your purse from the back the ground examples rental, point where the number of
Is equal to the number of fights not parts
Do you want to come over here and say that again or
So I guess I should
I can bring it up
Suggestions in the chat Charlie
The bottom
And then pop-out chat and then I put that on the side of your screen at all time okay
This guy talking about dividing the the B you have
Cyrus something I don't understand
I want to feel really embarrassed if there's somebody in the chat who's already given all of these answers and
I just wasn't reading visible
Looks like
Behind-the-scenes stuff going on here
See your recommendation is read
From behind to get the parts from the back to figure out how many samples are in it and you'll come to a point where number
Spencer's
Hit parsed is not as equal to number
Hockey got to be a way of knowing
There's no way
Problem you're having this exact reason why
Yeah
What did he say
Tell me how things exact reason why it's called something by directionally
Oh my God are you serious
Beginning is totally the Liang
Okay okay fine you were right it's arcade oh my gosh
Okay
Ears
Okay I don't know how many bytes in the back actually matter there are four extra-base I don't know what they do
There are three B here
I'm guessing two of these B are sent to do with the the size of the
I'm sorry headphone users I was
I was just really really
Anyway by the way if I do this like with my own stuff I'm totally using
The air 211 MC S7 like coding so I can have as many bits as I want and not have to worry about it
Anything to you Speedy 266 and maybe with esp32 I don't know
You can actually send just raw packets like a straight of radio and I have tested the esp8266 up to
The full MCS 772 mb per second standard and it just keeps up it's just that crazy so
I'm totally sold on anywhere I can I'm shoving a little lot
Esp8266
Oh and rs.24 can't do that
Beard pocket first thing that the nrf24 l01 started within the nordics
That makes sense okay
I'm so sorry you had to use the Nordic semi part
Anyway
Moving on
It's bidirectional encoded really there is nothing the beginning that I can look at night ride
And been confirmed to tell in advance
How many
LEDs are going to be in the signal
I wish I knew what these last four b r but I don't know what they are
These last two here
Sasa 25 1234
This is counting up continuously
That's interesting
I-69 be
Oh that's weird what's going on there
Might be the math but overcoming on your infection
No stop giving me until I'm already ahead of the game
Oh yeah okay
Anyway
Okay so let's see here I have 2174 1546 guessing that
That's leftover bbc1 C60 this one is counting up all the time
But that's interesting cuz bbc1 see text
Oh okay what kind of cool if you click the link just for the sake of being able to identify the different things apart
Anyway
Corresponds to
Sorry there is
Dfc90 where's the one that was incrementing
CCD 16cc
CC does not correspond to
Probably actually the second
Most significant bit
Okay so that was accounted for and now we have these other two
Which
Add up
So that would make it through that that gives us all four of the B
That's kind of cool
123 that gives us all of the time signature if we start reading
Backwards then we can read out all of the okay fine whatever
From a backwards yes then you told me I needed three more
Okay so tell you now that you're here and you're a lot more open mouth and I thought you would be
We pretty much saw the protocol now like I could I could go right this week
Test it but I'm I am serious wide give the second most significant fight in the time code
Code for the message
Significant b e r is that the code for the message
Change the time code that the message received and not the time code for the OTA
The IMU b b you know what time you're making this a little
All the two easy so you're suggesting I throw out the MSP which is okay cuz I don't
Okay well you just handed me the ranch
A lot of fun today what I guess it's time to go
Code that up now that we have a pretty good understanding of it
See here so I have various functions for popping off bits of data I'm going to make one that's lb 25
Minecon popper Arcane pop
Forgot to make a function for I can pop I guess yeah
Into Arcane pop
He's our star data
And actually this is really weird so got to start from the back
Forward which is the opposite of the way that we normally process the data that's
Passive pointer to the end of string and read it
Backwards so
Also I make sure I don't go off the front
Let's see here that would be
Actuate then second question
Why why did the OT a Time codes correspond so closely to the IMU time codes in Leicester
Oh okay baby off the same timer that kind of makes sense okay
I'm good with that
4 a.m. I think I was up until a little
I was up trying to decode this anyway moving again
So what I'm going to do is going to take a look at the value at the end
I'm going to say
Daystar and I'm going to say and
- -
The second I thought I was going to
Be able to use and negative index in my array
Deprogrammers cuz we still have a possibility of negative indexes about once every four years I actually run into an opera
Community where it makes sense to use negative indexes in my IRA
What a negative indexes in Python do
Oh okay
Top 10 python you can count backwards
Yes
Okay so for reading from the back
An example of daa 003
B&B reading po3 first
And I would say
Another example would be 78
I read the 03 first
Do a nice realize this could have even longer value so I should be careful how I could this
I have to advance backwards one more
So if V1 and Erik Satie
Mom
Okay
So what I do now is I say if the numbers were going from the back of the string looking for words so I start here.
1003 does not have the most significant it set so we know we need to read the next value
That one's there
That'll be
We need to read the next one so v-nam or equal schools
Remove it up seven bit because it's
Did the size of these things is 1 - its first it tells us yeah
Or
Star and
Okay
Save this number
Is the
I'm curious what it
What did I say that that Ben said the funny thing to
How you know what
Shenzhen IO
Someone mentioned that you were basically doing Irish and don't know what is that I don't know what channel
Review about machine language
Oh cool
This isn't the game though
It's like Canada
If you die in Canada you die in real life
Okay so what I'm doing is I'm whatever I'm never going to read more than a number
Yo whatever I'll just let the whole thing fly so I look at the
I look at the B that we're currently on
And I said v-nam this is like my accumulator
Call the accumulator
To be that value-added with lower bitmask
And so this would read out 03 and set it to the accumulator and Advance the pointer one back
Then
If
15 on the number that was actually red has a 178 that we know we're done we stop we have
The number we needed we need to get out
I'm so we returned the accumulator
If not then we read the next value
We advance the pointer back
Am I missing something in the chat
And immediately read the next value out
And you know
Let's also say if it's if the flag is set
Or
We have
Orenda sequel to start
Set means we can't just jump off the beginning of the actual vector and we can't cause problems
Getting flashbacks right inspection
So sorry for you then
How did I get
Forgot
Rug burn or something at some point
There's no way I can be more than four B I'll just return the accumulator there
I guess it could be more than four B
I'm not going to code that
Anyway
So Arcane Popcaan
Go to the end of the string and start popping back
Okay
So in here
Parse
What's wrong with this thing well
What's go for the gold
Time 1
Makes me nervous to do now
7 B back from the end of the packet
Forgot to mention the last four B actually not in the payload what happened
When was that I noticed when I was looking at the data that there were four bites that kept changing I didn't know what they were I thought they were CRC
I tried a bunch of stuff and couldn't figure it out
So I was printing it out anyway because they might have been part of the code but they were
Completely useless so has been confirmed they very well may be
So end is equal to
Creed
Date now yeah read data
Q t y -1
My time is
And
That
Yes
Up 24 and 1 or so
-1 of 60
4 + -2
8 no wait
It
Okay that's probably the time maybe maybe not I don't know
Now let's start Arcane popping our way back to the beginning
While and is not equal to
T-star
Start equals
Free data
How am I know I'm not talking much but I am a man and by definition very bad at
Multitasking
AC Popa
Yeah
Okay so while we're not we just pop off a bunch of numbers and let's just see what we get
We got a compiler whoops
This makes pointer from Magic House without
How we didn't crash let's see if these data points make sense
Okay
Time is 100/66 297
Is a reasonable number as far as numbers go
Starting from the back
19 19 19 6
196 33 70
That does not look right
Definitely 707070 B3
What's the what's also print out what we were looking at before so we can compare them
Holding up the little light thing now
I know Italy format this a little bit better too
Okay so for this code right here the packet looks like this
We know the last four B don't matter
We have 12 3/4 the time code which produces this time code right here
Then we read off 0 to 90
Switch is not 001
Not at all
What am I doing wrong
Okay so I got
Reading the end
I'm not sending my pointer dent
Properly before first pop
I have a suspicion that might be it let me just do this and all off
I'll just confirm
So I'm reading at the end the 8th
Oh yep you're right I'm deathly not doing that right
That would be in the middle of what I care about this one too far so
And should be quantity - 2
Thank you whoever that was who was it that was
Night Nightwing
Arthritis
What's the date
Now I still wrong if its -3
4 - 4 - 4
Okay
302 a002 read that
Nea 0 okay that's good
01 9002a 1
But
These numbers don't look right so ei0101 should not be
Or 280
Yeah that that number coming out is just wrong
Trisomy wrong in here
So what in the world
Take a look at this
Entertain pop that's right
122 that would be the right value for so right now reading back 02
280 it should be 120 hacks that's right
But when I print it out it's 00020 why is
I'm sending to you and 8
Make it a 32
Try that
Gorgeous
Okay
That's that's really happy
Go remove some of these extra printouts here that we definitely don't need anymore
Chelsea Otis says so now we're starting at the end here
Caesura 290 is 11
11e which is correct
VR 9201 is just 92 hacks 029 1:30
Anyone hacks
Oh we'll know we're done when we've read
So we have
We have 1 2 3 4 5 numbers which is length of time the distance between time
Distance between distance between time no distance so we have five numbers that
Will mean we need have three lighting events
And then if we do if there's three more bites
Left at the beginning of the packet we know we're good to go let's try parsing.
Whoever you fell be on the safe side
Equals the number of sensor that's right that's unfortunately
Yes I said that but he probably already said in chat so he's a little bit faster than me
Then I'm just so you know I'm not pulling the 24-hour one traffic and we just found out it's not the 24 LOL
I want anyway what's happening is the
And I'm using all of the USB commands to go
Connect to Vista Wireless version and pull the data off
Something else
Why use heat rather than control messages because
Ever since even low-speed USB you can usually get better performance from the control meth
Messages when you have really tight time constraint you don't have to answer that but
It's something a lot of people do a lot of people use the his stuff or the interrupt mechanisms instead of can
Control mechanism
I just never
Never really understood why
So if you do want to comment on it great if you don't want to comment totally understand
Is it clearly there's something I'm missing I don't understand why it's done that way but
Heartplace is
AC pop
Parameters I equals car
Fireplace plus is equal to AC pop
No I'm not making custom firmware for the guard
Oh my gosh if you are willing to tell me I cannot get
The haptics to work reliably when I enter it it something like really quick
It doesn't feel or sound good but you know whatever
Going back to this now we got to actually make forward progress the purpose of this is to
Reverse engineering anymore like I'm just
Whatever we're implementing something we did some reverse engineering
And Mindy is still reverse-engineering the the firmware is
Okay
So what is the equation for this we're going to be looking for a situation in which
Does anyone else I'm really bad at this kind of logic I am the math dolt
I do not need a chair anyone else can you think of this cuz I'm having a really hard time
It's par plate the number of parameters / greater than
Okay I will take a copy and paste of what you just told me and keep it for later
Ben Jackson says
Anyway I going to this little bit more
Light code that is par place over to so we have
Be
53 flashes one
Opposite one
If I have 53 messages here
Good fall I have is one message
I would expect one light
So
If
Our place
I'll be 35 -
5 / 2
5 + 1 / 2
Is equal to place the v65i 23
Hip replaced three okay got it so par place
+ 1/2 is less than or equal to
Remain
Now if it's
Greater than
Prequel to remain then we're going to break out of the loop
This means something went wrong
Otherwise we probably have a good packet
Okay so now this is annoying cuz
We got to read them from the back going forward
Okay so let's make sure that we actually know the order we're reading this all in but I'm going to do is I'm going
2in DVR program I'm going to sit at 225 2015 and
When I said it to 8 + 16
I can't get access to that so surely in here
Now we're Cookin it's hold us up to here
But let's see what the data says
Oh you know what
20-20-20
G502 9401
Find CO2 in 601
BO2
Oh you know what I didn't reprogram DVR
Bellator 228
Fl1a 102
The 1020 is increasing the delay and
You know what let's figure out why the washing counters matching I figure that other part out later
Anyone else noticed the problem of my code
You're just giving it away now okay
Describe there
And -2 deltas
Yes I have
So 2836 4452
Why
Oh the number of B remaining is this minus this plus one
I don't really want to do that
Maybe I do
Hey why don't you match
52 why didn't you pull off a third
How is it
I do while logic was wrong
Okay pulled off the data
Sorry Charles Foreman
Okay so that's the right number of parameters
Direct time is the first edge of the first hit
And we just figured out that the first hit is the first one here so this one here is hit number one
Sorry that whatever the first
Logical hit which is at the end of our list cuz
Whatever
Totally did this all backwards
Oh
I'm actually one step to not here
They Mindy decide
Anymore
What is a live here
This is going to get very meta very
Very meta
I wonder how long it will take before I can put this together and can actually like
Recoup around
Stay here
There goes
Okay
Goes my time
Handle lightcap
W
Genuflection
Working on phone
I think we have been hasn't said anything
Close
Then proper size Hungarian experiments to break it on
Okay then I got to work fast enough
Tcmsp from the packet
Princess watch
Ben says he's going to experiment that will break it
Cmsv from the packet
That won't work cuz it's going to be at the edge
What is the time code is right on the edge and the thing from previous
MSP lover
Okay so that's one other thing that I did forget to mention I do have a function handle lightcap so anytime
Time did the centers received anywhere I do all of the stuff to determine whether or not it's a code from
The lighthouse or the code internally and I do the stuff to sweep
Or The Flash and I also do the stuff too so what we get is we get the time of the
First Edge what we really need is the time at the middle and that's how we can figure
That that metal thing out I noticed I'm not sure if we will really work
But I'm pretty sure we actually need to sample at 24 MHz
Because then we can back out in advance before sending
What's beginning would be based on the beginning and Edge edges of the beginning and closing it to the packet
848 granularity of 48 Mega samples for S we can actually sample at 24 samples for
2nd and that's a lot easier to do on the esp32 so
Ha4d is not divisible by 48 we could totally do it at 40 and then divide 2
Yeah anyway
So I'm just going to pass this data into the handle lightcap function
Panini to advance the time to
The next one after
Think that's correct
Logic might be totally wrong but
Is Ellie. Type I just don't remember she really look that up
Oh
Actually Ellie type has got to be
Valid
Ellie. Type
But that is your wife
Let's just do the clever thing right now to get the most significant fight of the the time
Timecode
So what I'm doing is I'm going to copy the most significant fight from the IMU time
Loaded into TGIF and then if it's small great if it's
Then I'm going to need to bump it up or bump it down one so if T diff
Is greater than ffffff
7 and he'd if -2 equals
Okay
Leon I don't need to print out all that date anymore
Unplug
I find it hard to believe that I need to pump plus that much
Can hear your sneeze is okay
Yeah still one of the things you guys can't hear is that Adam is in
The room over there
An echo of several seconds later
Anyone else in the channel should I be paying attention to
Someone else about your educational guy answer phone
Someone that's going to get there
Wait what no no no no no job at Java bad JavaScript okay but only if you know see first
This is clearly wrong
Little engine
The Jackson just like jabberwock where's makes people flip
Okay
I'll take a look here
That's a much larger number than I would have expected
Hello came from than 145 6894
What's 30 milliseconds
Seems really big
Seems too big
Vader really that far out a day
Something wrong
Something about this is just wrong
I'm doing something wrong what is what is up with this
Sorry I'm just going back and looking through these
Let me know not sure why it's busted
I'm pulling up here I think
It's weird too cuz it is tracking pretty good
No it's not
No that's wrong
Yeah there's definitely something hosed
Charles beautiful when asking about the car
Quadcopter and positioning system videos
What
Quadcopter imposition mean
Stop
I will go sailing
I never even thought to put an ESPN
To use this with an ESP tell where it is with a quadcopter in 3D space that sounds like the cool
Coolest thing ever I don't know but I could make
Can do one although I did actually make a new quadcopter motherboard that I still totally knock on the pro
Programming that used to be a speedy 285 so it's even smaller yet
Whatever
Still wrong shopping from 64 to 281
And what about positioning playing the person masks
Tobacco
Why don't know what they're referring to positioning thing
But the positioning system
But I am going to be still tinkering with it so this here isn't esp32 on a circuit
Ford I designed
And I having problems getting it to work at all as you can see I have a bunch of wires trying to figure out why the Flash doesn't go
So this guy right here is hopefully my tempted that because down the ethernet port
On this board I can actually influence the Clock Crystal so I'm just going to see total Shot in the Dark
Any papers probably won't work maybe I can synchronize all of these exactly the same clock and then be able to tell all of that from
Granted there's a lot of Reflections and stuff like that so I could totally hoes my data but I have
I've never let
Like actual science that tells me something is impossible from stopping me from
Trying it anyway
Because sometimes
People's understanding of science is wrong and it's worth trying it
Has he got the free time which I don't have but I do have sleep which I can cut into
Speaking of which like I have to do a v tomorrow at church so I got to be up at a reasonable time but
Don't need to be very well rested so
I need to do the things but I don't need to be prepared
Some definitely
Is wrong
+ 0 y
Look at the post date again
Oh I am still try the other way
Nobody has any ideas about why my codes busted
Obvious
Charles can you program nana nana nana
Actually I just realized backwards hubby
- 1 - 2 - 3
So why am I pulling off cao2 OB all wrong
He is positive
How are things going
Oh I'm reading the Matrix inversion
I think
It's going to be lying right now
So this is going to be a 9 by 9
Which means we can do it really fast
Libra is attempting to do it using
Like
Really naive updates were just kind of like drags the model around maybe that's good enough
But I really I don't know I really can't wait to see you at the
What the actual Kalman filter
Even necessary because
Because we were looking at some of the position data from the headset before
And it was really really
It looked really
Not going to come over here
What
I was just saying I don't really know if we need us common filter cuz we were looking at the
Headset data and we weren't able to figure out the exact coordinate system but when we moved it a little bit of
Really really smooth and I went when we kept it completely stationary we saw a little bit
Noise in the timestamp then when we compared that the amount of noise versus
Motion over like a couple of inches
You couldn't
I couldn't see any noise in it at all so I don't I mean
We don't need it
Queen
I want to see what would happen if we do it right
Maybe that's right
Cuz what I'm looking at right here
The last for the CRC then it's 123 and it looks like 93 to F10
And that looks correct the marketing
I'm probably going to freak it out so that's.
Not able to
Still looks wrong
How do I make my time scale
The rack the time scale
Actors that
I thought the IMU and the lights would be
Be on the same time scale
And it appears they're not
Why could you not have used the same clock for both.
I would have made it so much easier
Now I got to go pee clever in stuff
Blastoise
I guess I can just treat everything is a 24-bit number
No I bought something
Oh I was wrong
Gorgeously
Indian Miss would that be
The bite at
Most significant
The number in the whole system then
I think so I think that's it
Looks better
Well is that really going up nicely or
Numbers too big to be going up nicely
Now wait maybe
How big is that 123456789 3 billion.
It is right bb60
Dd69 pb66
67-59 for synchronizing the IMU
You and the light codes that really makes it a lot better
Totally had Indiana strong
I think it's time that you send me something that'll that'll break the
Well I mean I don't know for sure maybe just doesn't quite look right I guess something
Little bit closer little bit better
Looks like the wrong like wrong
I did want to make sure that it bumps in the
Right direction when it does
Bump back
Oh oh my time
Make sure this pump function works
Cats right now
So the 14-7 whatever is definitely wrong 14 741
On our way to getting that idea
Yeah I don't know how it
Smoking
Going here can't figure out what
Oh
Right
Ben's most recent comments
Was Beyonce density experiment might help anyway it's all sensors are multiple eighths make your LED
What happens
Did you really compress it that way too.
I find it hard to believe that this was the most efficient way of
I'm doing it
I just this is haha
Not the way you're thinking ook
Questions
Wanted with your last night
Light number
I know that is right okay that is correct Spencer ideas right
Park Place i x
You're not right
Okay I'll check that first
Light number i - x 2 + 1
Really concerning why is that running off the negative end of the array
432 10 - 10 K
337 316 216
Hey let's try with different constants so right now I'm going to do is when I change the length of time that the LED is on
So I want to make it 10 10 and 20
So
1418 295 that looks about right
Recommends I suppose
We will now
Suppose we can look at everything and Delta's
And now I'm going to do it then suggest and look at the Delta between the frames
I'm definitely getting tired you guys can see me making some mistakes
Correct
I don't know I can't go for a fact you catch that
I got a clock reset I want to make sure that when the clock reset it doesn't hose my data
Well that's not good
There is a negative number in there
There's more negative numbers negative numbers bad he can't go back in time what did I do wrong
Thank you for asking me to check that
What is the Chapman doing
I'm not ready to handle simultaneous hit
Why is my Delta wrong
I don't want my Delta to be wrong
Oh I know what you would have done you're going to do something clever with the B when there's more
Multiple hits at once why
Whatever I got to get this figured out first why is my Delta is wrong
Help
Does anyone else see what I'm doing wrong here
How many people are in the saying right now
Okay
I'm not interpreting my belt is right
First my time is starting the first hit the end is my time plus First Alpha
That might be possible
Right down here
Ben says that's not quite right you mostly just not interpreting or Tilted
But I am taking my time by the parameters of this place
The first my time is the start of the first hit the end is my time plus her first Delta the next one
My time
First plus s
It is accumulating it's right here I have the code on the screen
420 3548 39
It's definitely incrementing
Including
Ulta
Exchange nearby
From the end of the packet
So don't the one
Your first
And
But Delta to is your your second start not your second end
I'm interpreting it as the number that the end of the packet is the time of the first hit
The time of the start of the first hit
Start of second it is
They're also know it's that plus
The Delta time that I read from the parameter
I think right
It's not certain which like you think it would be more obvious if you did the experiment
Okay we will shoot
Life
At 2 lights on musically
True
Only starts and ends can be interleaved if they overlap
I don't understand
Oh my gosh I think if I was more awake just be a lot easier right now but I don't
I want another 30 minutes
2:30
Each sensor
Don't know what I'm looking at
Wait a minute what
Wait a minute
452 is the new code
252 is probably like
Why
We're going to Vegas
Frustrated
This Is the End
Okay
Silver frosting from the beginning 52-18 4821
48 is the actual LED code 5250 to both of them on
2000 advance
Four words
Oki Siri
You've done something extremely clever
I'm definitely getting worn down right now
Matheny's only licensed one light
Two right two lights
There we go
They got that stable
Alpha trigger both of them
Come on both we can get this
Come on
I can get to other real
Plus 58
Not 160
58/60
Interesting
Is it
I would need to led to test if immediately Heating
Put the order of the LEDs that I'm reading the minutes is backwards
Tanto Metro my Deltas are wrong
If somebody leaves monitoring chat
Okay
I don't
No cuz I don't have any easy way of making patrl put independently to 2.22 MHz
LED strend streams
Oh gosh
Oh
That's interesting
It's significantly lower than when I
Oh my gosh what is going on there oh
The Delta OIC
Is actually the Delta between when they come on and off
Okay so it looks like I made earlier about being able to do this for the 24 MHz clock I'd have to
Retract
That would not be the case
Say what
It's not the length
Saying probably
Here is not the 1136
What's the distance between the events
What's the distance between the two events and time
Oh okay so it's this time
Is
Microseconds later this turns on
No how would I differentiate between which one it is then and then this event is later
I was told that I do
I don't usually though
Clipart snowflake the dining room.
I'll try to come to us
How do you spell
Yeah
Next to his name
If you're not over his
Chat
Comet
I just get it asking me if I wanted to spend time with you
Let me see if I can find them
You can fly grandma
But we can report
Do you know how about
Persons
4 +
Developer for the Vive is in the chat and has been very helpful with
A couple
Like t'bus here and there
But I'm definitely getting stuck on this Delta's thing something's not quite right
And it looks like the second flag is the amount of time between
Something and when the next event happened but I'm not sure
What that is between the two of them like
Fight
Like in that little
Holier
The B2 and B8
Satiate
P0
My hit them both
B2 in VA
B11 the world
What
Is the lowest
Order
Oh no
Determined
And I have no idea how are you developed able to keep
Crazy
The world is that one's dead
To be a continuation from last reading book?
Like since the one that lives in tissue with bit set?
T852 Jason
Wait wait what 5860
Enjoying from the Netherlands is asking where we're currently at capturing light with controller to do what
To make a lighter weight
I don't even know I'm doing this anymore but honestly it was
Was because I used Linux I have a Intel integrated graphics card I kind of want to reverse-engineer this myself
I want to make a really honestly might my big old are is is dependencies as possible so like
I don't want to mess with osvr I don't want to mess with any of that I'm a c program or just want to have the most basic
Interface I can be able to tell where I am from the the vibe
Time
Hi-5 can you tell me one thing
Can you tell me if the order in which I'm reading these is correct is 5 a
Coordinated with this and 60 coordinated with this or do I have them backwards
Like is it the first second one third one in in left-to-right order or is it reading
Backwards from the end
The first parameter and then reading out from there
I haven't yet updated that 27
48 million to the second later 60 happened
Really confuses me cuz 5 a.m.
60 and that's 5865 why is
5A what is up with the 619
What is up with that one's dead
Forget 5 a.m.
Interpret the end part correctly it's just a list of times expressed as a star
Birds and dildos
Oh
Thank you
Thank you Ben
Okay
I will
I will heed your advice
Where am I
Really 226
Realspace
2:26 a.m.
Currently
I'm going to push this back to 2:40 but then we're calling it quits 2:40 p.m.
Unplug the network connector
Saudi feeding forward
Delta's okay set
Can't we can't really deal with it that way totally
Not the way to deal with it
I don't I don't see any use them
All right but the like try to turn the firmware into anything meaningful
Quotes
GIF versus GIF so he's going to post that and chat to go vote
Jack asked how far you think you would have gotten tonight
Far enough to the point where I would have realized
The arguments in lights out of gotten an order of everything correct I think that's where I would have ended I would not have
Unable to assemble it anywhere close to like the meaningfulness that we're at here
Space asks if you saw the integer video of a lighthouse recorded without my haircut
I saw a video from a while ago I also recorded a video of myself
Which I'm probably not going to put on YouTube anymore since this livestream is here
Just wondering is anybody at all getting ads or do I have to click the button
Heart straight through just wondering
Forsyth no answer what else okay
Delta equal
1%
Okay I'm not going to able to close it tonight I bring
But I'm going to at least what I think it is
Check out of tomorrow I think the format is
Time equals start of event
Math equals LEDs
Yeah you're so jealous
Yeah I invited you to our conversation
Places many almost
Invite chatter I did send invites
No actually that doesn't make any sense
Why would that
NFL
Instructions
Disassembler 4851
Are you
You know I love you
It's so funny for hours and hours and hours but then when I do it live
I need a working harder something that I definitely get dull very quickly
So
4 hours before that
Yeah yeah yeah I got to hear it
I think that's a cuss word that is a moderator I guess
River little wrench next to him
Euro
So I couldn't make you a moderator just say anything cuz I'm not even the moderator
Only one person is allowed
Whatever bugs
No I need I need to go to sleep
Where does Audible and resume VR
Coronavirus
Where do you get from working
Frances
Beautiful body
17 BR local fire files for it somewhere
Stop like all of those files that you were looking at
Free
Great but they don't have those files to again texiera
You mean the other wall I mean if they have 543
Optimum package
Say
Whether it is or not
Are you starting to get worried but I need to download Steam I don't know
All of my screen packages extinct black so I might not be the right person.
50th Dakota turns it on 124 Cycles later turns off 1698 Cycles later returns
Tennis probably face-palming now cuz it took me this long to really actually gather
Everything together
Delta p
Actor
Okay
What other Shameless plug if you are still thinking about you know
Development in the future
Expressive make some really awesome parts
Just just looking at in there
Total
Think that
People ask is Jamie going to happen more often and surprisingly fun to watch
No I mean I don't know it'll happen the reason this happened
Was I have been trying to get this led to work with this and I just couldn't it wasn't working in somebody
They commented in one of the things like MHz
And as soon as I saw that and I tested into work because I knew I would be
Stream something that was a
Maybe doable task most of what I do I have no idea if I'm ever going to get anywhere close to being able to do
I don't bother because this one had a definitive I can start I know which one
I'm going
I'm supposed to be here
5 a.m.
Super funny YouTube
We went to what
So I'm almost there
Get ready to react to frog
Express parts are so good they don't need to pay people to advertise
Another one say he's become the next big Clive
Afternoon zverev plug mini motorcycles
But I'm not
I don't think there's much risk has such as collective
Oh really because I'm pretty sure everybody who would care to watch this is watching it right now
Now like I don't think there are more people out there
Okay
YouTube
5A
Is actually some sort of code is not the visible
I don't know how that would actually code into thing that the next 10 sec
The 5808 hold on that's not right that's not right at all
I - 1 - 2
If that is greater than or equal to 0 then you can't find it okay
Revive performance around 12 lights
Encoded
Infrared
It's going to just ignore anything it's not that the codes that is looking for
I don't know about that because everything I've read about the Nordic
The problems with the like the other like coexistence with other 2.4 GHz
Stop but I don't I don't know the details I've only ever used the 10 rs.24 l01 a lot
And that one was okay so I didn't really I don't really care and
I would never have guessed that this had a Nordic chip in it because
Historically
Leaving performance I get out of the five
So clearly
7 microseconds later
The 60 on at the same time
Indicates that it would be five and then the sick
And then 90 seconds later it turns into just 60 so 50 is now
Off-road four and six on at the same time
5 first two
And then 60 for some period of time and then 60
Returns off to nothing
So this is 50 then
60 later
Then
90 later
Exterior only seven
Now it doesn't make any sense ohyeah 7 later
60 off 17 not 19
Later
50 on
* 7
Later 60 on
Then
90 later
6050 off
Then
7 L 60 off the understanding of the timecode
Having some way of figuring out how the multiple codes works
Do try to understand multiple code
You do make sure order of on office correct
To do
Cat fleas
Okay
This is for completely horribleness and sadness
I'm going to save it and committed
Okay
Think I'm done
Think I'm done for tonight
Thank you everybody for hanging out
I'm off
I'm done
I'm definitely done
Does anybody else hear everything else so I just log out
The exterior light I did push
Kelsey cannot
Really
Lots of hugs and kisses from Gigi
A minute ago right here
What are you going to post me with update
I don't even know what I'm going to have a update
They do not have all the files to Tori
Data process USB data
Datas deep roster
Okay that's right
Streaming will have an opportunity to start
I have a clear definition I'm going to be able to move forward with it so
I was able to work with the controller I had a clear way for those going to test this and make it work
So that's why the string exist it's not often that I run into an opportunity like this
I did push I do have to log off now though guys so
Thank you for coming out
Stop
Pop