Is 3360
Hello hello Ramayan
Still being called Jackie also another thing I just realised
I'm going to want to try the forgot
Broadcast YouTube live stream 2
Will it rain
CD if you guys remember from last time there is some neat stuff that we did with
Just checking
363 desi on 18362
Classic
Are you actually working on the project
I'm related projects
Unless you are one of work at work I'm trying
What's the latest with the arm pi and display
That makes sense
Right now
And then go back to stop
The camera
We can also really do is start with the
2 probably
So I guess this probably half an hour doing with this cos it's just something I wanted to do and that's it
The chat room that we have right here and stream it to
Still hard sorry I guess we can but what that means
Real estate on my screen that you guys can say
Which is really annoying because I really love having really stay on my screen that I can work in and you guys
What yeah
Reminders
Set up the display
You have to buy
Single of technology
Spell maybe
Upload video
Things to do a few things off screen
I do not
Because I do not want certain keys certain API keys getting out that's ok
I will get that stuff and then please give us a shot
Do you want
I'm going to go back to the street
Hello yes
Brandon
Inverse phase is working on
How long is crazy
Ok
This lighting here
Good point but a discord link up
That's should have got it working now
Here we go
UK
If you want to see how we do the YouTube chat everything like I guess this is it
I guess I'm willing to show you
I'm not like you up yet
Create a new project YouTube
Cast chat
Create
Even met either
I don't want to have me
Are you alright I need to pop out the YouTube chat right now
Very long
IKEA
Come on
This
The light
Seems like a recipe for disaster
Austria
Active complement
Add is unlikely
I think this change this lifetime
Sorry guys I thought this to be a second a bit longer
The way in which the keys work on
Stuff
I am really confused completely different now
Sounds like Google
I don't know
BCM 3633 is from triads and conductor
Sorry guys
New project and if I look up over here
YouTube API version
Free bingo
Enable
Keys up on the screen
Turn on
Play credentials
YouTube
From other you whenever
Will be accessing commentator
Please can I have that Kieran fast you know what you guys too so
Please turn off the Ikea addresses so I can see like
What is my IP and my gosh
Call
News Mikey
Ok
I can take this epi key in and I can put it in
Dit
Probably make it so that these two are online
C3
Usage colon
KPI
Vtiq well actually drv
Around
Advanced make a weird clock
This one this one is often this one is on
I will keep playing with the team
Will use this API key
We have to go get a life charity
This thing right here
Is it broadcast on
What can you do
11 let's go further
Live chat ID
Hello bingo
In the chat
In the shower I'm just doing this to beginning of the chat
Make a new channel
New channel
And it's all of the YouTube chat to the
Meeting on the Sky today
Is to get the reading a single 36
3633 CM1 esp32
For him it's not going to be very very much
Using the anything like that at least not yet I haven't been able to talk
But hopefully I will get one working maybe
Project how many how many
Do you think you're gonna need
I think I should just one
It's good
Actually
So the next
Midday
Wine please
I think it's going to go to Ltd
Siri discord RTE 1
Can you test loggerhead specifically that was mostly
Masterov I don't know right now
Oh I did put the live stream link in discord
What's screen sharing in use
Tell me how to use DLC bye
Something out as stream
Go to set alarm going on over the last mile
Working with the with Whitehaven can expanding
So really do want to go over in my hope is that he'll be able to actually go from his
Computer
Kind of meat
So hopefully be parking in that so discord web
Sad easy message
I'm trying to
I want to take each line of input and with
Beesline executor shark
Why do I have I have my camera on
That's going out through steam
Wine
Have you won't be there
Definitely not right hey chat somebody here
Play do that
Let me ask them in an hour
Oh dear chat on YouTube if you have something new line is coming from standard out how would I take
Flying from Spain Adele and then make it execute a brand new command
Dearest charts
Stepping out with that type of Xbox
How would you say oh yeah how would you say that
That's a good question
Is that maybe there is a way
Because I was right at the age
Also that
How old is
Romanian
Opening signs in his like some made up user
Ok so Jack what I want to do is
VR YouTube chat thing
How to go execute my discord webhook
4 eastline and then have a habit of that outputs a arm
Lights off
Still like you have codes spawn a new script which then once that to the
Actually like you
Shell script for each line of standard out
Alarm
Also this is making me really nervous text you these things when
This whole thing
Sing your text and ask me to come out
That's great
Yes it's a brave
I live in the the edge of that which is terrifying
Dash and 1
This is definitely not the right
Ok guys healthier
You know what I can just go change the YouTube chat monitor thing
Takes up another parameter and it's specified it just calls Dad
Yeah that sounds terrifying
Optional
Command to execute on
You
Message
Yes we're on this route
BMI
Volume general ideas if I see some really nasty thing coming through the YouTube chat I can just unplug the computers
Stop the window
Turn on the office
To get someone now
Oh no I'm sorry guys I may have already moved on
I like a musical.ly rias somebody just to chat Arms
With all the stuff in the backlog or something
Starts
Esp8266
Connect discord on my phone
Do you charge VAT
Toilet
Oh yeah that's good
Who's like there's two
One is called Seymour and one is called YouTube
Slight
Yeah
So what I'm going to do
What's the next cute the Communion with this chunk
New lights
Skip
They were stealing in thing from 2 m
2 seconds ago
Can you play charged
Hey Google
Turn on office light
Make sense
People talking about
Zoo bar
Forester life
How old is doing
The 3rd
How do solar panel
Safely
Because it would still be inside the double quotes
Batteries and corroded things
I could record my day
Nervous
Shutdown dash 8 friendly face
The people who've been sending this stuff looks like it's all
Like me looks like it safe
Passing me to
No YouTube seems to escape
Team safe
How do I get to sleep Tower signs
Commend
No because you can do dollar sign curly brace LS Close curly brace
No I think you can
Can you turn off the heating really like you like Echo yeah you know
Yeah I know who's back back
What is your running at evening
It's directly from thing can you just do like
Light
Stop
You must not do this now just worry about everything else
This is terrible I feel bad now I don't want to do this
What do you know we will use this this window right here
What's happened
Are you
Have I done it now
Status report
Play wave my hand over it like stuff
This is not work
It's very
Here callous mask is stuck
Ok
Ok that makes things work in the in from forward so this for now and worry about that some other time
Some other time
That's kind of what we came here for
Stop
Tom February 24th
Give me like basically
Guys when they're not popping
Lower volume
Ok
Removing alarm
Stop some things with them
What's your number one recorder
Snooze tvi
Earlier today
To check out
DVD recorder actually off please
All the data outputs a really need thing here it's the time that
Rolled I'm here so 10.45 640
The specific event happened
Yeah ok
Turn on this
Was made by Elbow
Armin the main light to buy chat and on that was like
Play Back things in real time so we can go take data and play back to
Detest the posters and stuff like that so
Volume
Ok good now it's alright
Oh nice
You guys want to get that setup weekend over there
We can take the vibe over there and then
Ok so got the live data in Catterick
So I can do this and my
How do you use this
Set a French no albino
You have an example
Play Bad Things
If you do users from playback
Time
Wonderful actually do is it can playback
All of the data from basically all of the different match
Because I would love to record data and ensure that you guys live
Music which is actually excited which is actually which is
Who knows where that editors started it's life song
So are you doing ok with your stuff
How many events are in the other
Ok
So why are you everything's we needed to come in early actually do
Lightstream cos I would love to get feedback from other people we need to decide
Proper coordinates or reference
Framed for the poses and how it works
Turn lights
Almost 2-year old now but we have just actually never formalized it and as
As a little bit before today
Poses
Message Nicola 1
Annoying
So I don't know what you said it
Ok this is it
So the problem is that we have these poses that operate in different spaces for whatever we were trying
And are
I have no attachment to any standard the closet oi basically and you're working
Dim the table one obviously one needs to be
It seems like
Assume that the
Lighthouse
What's z and then
Return the position and
Orientation of the object game crack
What you actually need to do calibrations but that should be just fine
Lightstream cos
Surgeon
Everything's fine
Snooze that the bottom now bye now
Be able to play the Tar file
Anything so I don't really know this is live data
Live
What's the time
Felicia y&l
Play the song before 2
Turn on floor light
Not reading correctly today in addition to working with
Hear Focus mostly on kiss
And then we're also gonna focus on his work along with a brief
Play the same
Play crazy that happening after the side of me
Sylvania Ave white houses or in the upper corners
Explain that one
Girl
Yu-Gi-Oh
Update 14
New application
That's too quick
6th Gear
Looks like something
Cast
So clear
Incredible
I really want to find some way of telling
The lights please don't use calibrated values here
Lights 50
Car racing
Or maybe that's what the
Play 2Pac
I have
Microwave
You can blow through my battery
And then
Whitehouse euro in my house one there is
So much of a good thing by the way
How
Is there some way to say please
Turn on
For me
Instructions to light survive
Playback
Meat
Lights off
Follow these instructions
My playback
Hack
Play back
Goodnight
Between the eye and you DAB I've been having some issues
It's fine
So this is happening
Starts around this
Over here in movies things around
E.ON
Syria live playback
Really wrong
What's this mean to do that
Play bachata
My cal
There we go check that out so it's actually playing that the day that was recorded through lights
With the timing information and everything and actually works perfectly
You're very happy about that thank you I'll buy now friendship for adding Guardian
Pakistan
That was the
Ok next thing
Meat ok so what's he here
You saying there is no party there is no way to say don't celebrate because
Is the poses always based on a calculation in particular output from the Poacher
If you override the White House positions
Every time
Information hose information is still there
It should probably
Accidents while that is actually correct it should probably though
What are you doing you need more Airport
Because
Would you prove me that that we really shouldn't be sending a
We shouldn't be recalibrated get the calibration data is re building
Reminder houses
Light
Help
Temperature
S'more
Stop
I'm ok with doing
Simple post-test the lighthouses are both with zerozero.pt straight up
And then we're going to run against the database coming out
So in this one I would want to manually configure lighthouses to do
Market as calibrated do we not have a
Don't do the calibration
Hey Josh
The life survive the side
Live survive the sides
It definitely doesn't decide the calibration based on
Decide what it needs to do it doesn't need to do
TV stage I guess we could just forcibly set that
That would be in that age
Play time to revive caldinez
See hear
Right now
I'm happy with that
What's check here
I'm really cool
Pointers actually knows begin with
I need some way of telling lies please don't want to do my own thing
Let's see how it's done
Install Siri
Callum solenoid on in
So I never do the install
I never do this
What happens
Thank you tell me I'm an idiot I just saw that now you probably said that before I found
See hear
What's a kiss really like to do is
Opposed
What makes your actually getting data
The angle functions coming back
That's good
I could do
Add Amazon
Thinking about it actually is I was doing your sister live stream here but but I think I want to do is Piper
Turn off and then have the Script itself people timer
Stop
So polite cat dinner so why is it not giving me
See hear
Actually get cold
Tori actually goes in
Suppose you're actually doing that
Ok turn by disco not getting executed
Are you getting to the point rushing the video in the sand
Crazy
Stable
Actually you know we could turn this into a livestream showing how to make a YouTube video
I'm guessing he isn't watching right now so I might be on my own for this one
Ok
Stairs prepping at getting into
Why is light surveying
Please
Oh my gosh
Yes we need to get some video right now
Stop
Hippos test.com just want to get
How is your data coming from your thing to do is overwrite the Lighthouse positions put them
And then trying to get your things out today so I can take a peek at it
That exist
The reason your thing is not happening
Your code is not getting cold
Calibrator
Turn off alarm
Does the flashlight on your phone
Yeah
Where is the FM news
What line is there on Kirby
No trees we are using white survived
9 HTC vive
From that time
Upset right now
I think I'm wrong with it
Pull-ups
Snooze
Ok
Do you want to prove it
Logic analyser to monitor the pin to see
To see if it's actually turning on and off
Help me through this that would be really cool
You guys can take it back I'm going to go right now so I'll be right down
Go see what his
I'll be right back
Remind me
Reddish-brown
Coronavirus France
Transdigm
Orange One
Orange
Albino
MW3 and I like all your stuff so far
Seems like you're pretty good at you what contributor access directly so you can work correctly in the tree
No no what day what DVD is the only
Play off
Oh ok well calm down
It's plus eggs
You can put around as soon as you get up and GL I don't care
So
Which one did you plug in orange or yellow yellow
Oh oh I'm probing you so you will have to plug that thing into the
B32
I'll see you later if you want
I'm still
No it's not revoked it seems like like
Your invalid are off that you're not going
Into the code something which is Gonna Put around and then put it back so still
The offer is still stuck down
So I G O T studio 3
Light survive is kind of an independent project from the five which just basically open source systems
Music for lighthouses
Are generally preferred on
How many go to settings
Contributors
Collaborator
The red was
David burtka
Ok enjoy if you can push
For the calibrator right now that would be super cool
Yeah ok what's my name
Play Lighthouse Theatre to me
Is it break here is using I do want to move around so you can see the light
Yeah ok
Ok so what were actually looking at right now is the output from the yard
Cheers
Ba633
The rain hour looking at the output from the 3633 that CM1
I'll put years he's going in right here and b2c like this right here is the
Call the sinclair's
Repot people Speke Hall
362 TV
With the 332 and receiving the evening
The order of the receiving the erupts it is ok
Remember
The Beta looks very clean to me
The data looks very clean
Really know if it's clean or dirty
What is reason it doesn't look broken
Hi-lo hi Will hi
So let's sink sink sink
Sing thanks sweet
Because it goes like pink sweet scoop
Ok I'll buy now
Call minor
Time right now making out of you
Call little
Turn on video
Sorry I just wanted to plug
How you put ground in the class
Oh no that's yeah yeah this is Graham
Sorry I know he's he's using Redford round
Brown and white background
Brown pods in the red dress
I lost all the pins in
The ground to get more pins
Use offer to give me sleep what if I don't make red brown
I'm ok with that
An open source library for 5 that think not
On the definition of opposable seems like
Open source platform will let us do
Crazy stuff including running a lighthouse based racking stuff on things like embedded device
And that's really one of the big targets the other target is to have it run on really low and
The light
Yeah I know I don't know where that is
After which BTS after initiating CDs so I can my code
Mobile
Now did not work it's not giving me any data
Is this what you meant for me love you
It's not right
What's going on there
Stop
Aware of the problem was
What we can do that
Various levels of network
Play the GPL
Interrupted did you
I don't know if the numbers on the esp32 match the
The actual PIN numbers
32mm off
Play the listing is gpio on the back of the thing or
Yeah it's gpio but they haven't number depends on the board
Turn the lights
Lesbian
Try that
Look at that
Container
Occasion
Mypos data
Hi
Yeah looks like this broken and I was told me
How much longer do 20 guys are going to because I'm definitely the point of frustration right now
Bedroom light totally not something I should have tried to do live
Put on
Are the the calibrator stuff I'm unfamiliar with the
More time with me just chilling over it and I really want to do a livestream
Yeah we might just want to go switch to that then
Turn the light on
The post information to the lighthouses to me that doesn't make very much stands
Goodnight
Is that why what's going on there
Into the headsets posted by
I'm really confused
I don't know cos it's going to be a good live stream today
Esp32 getting some in Roxanne
Whatever
If you are if you don't feel like watching this but
You feel like watching you on that
Play I am free
Absolutely no sense to me
Why is it
Pilot drunk
Is really twitching all over the place
Just one of the east Indies and understand what it's doing here because
Moving around and see what happens
They don't want to see that
Pick it up
Can a working maybe
Hello looks like it's kind of wire
I have to go now
Hexham heads old
It looks like it's working
Kirkby Tori
Outdoor
Pause
Stop providing absolute so
How to make kebab
Play That's really what I want to test today I think
If there's any way for me to get to actually
Are you message St my I say
Simple pose cast I would just update the Lighthouse positions in here
Give me 1000 no rotation I guess
Be right back
Set an alarm
Which like do you guys have
Yeah I'm looking at the same thing
You need some methods of communication
Timer for
Yeah I'm looking at the same link
Can we have utility functions for the typos
Also we should probably comment right here what the definition for a no rotation
Just checking it supposed p0001
Is the kitchen light
Xyzw correct
Hey that's super wrong
That is
Super mega ROM
It has a very large x value
Wish I could grab
I wish there was some sort of thing you do like the litter all crap
So it didn't
Sometimes things in your double quotes and I'm literally
Single beds
Save my house first is your ankle if you start ok
Only 41
Like
Play play
Can you use this
I have made an example of one of just an ADR
So we could do like this but have three different colours hey Josh Allen
Let's go figure out which lighthouse this one is
Booking app
Think it's this one like of Iran
So turn by Plus X that
What comes out of the White House
White do
I thought you were killing when you said that we would compromise on for sex I didn't
I didn't think that you were serious
Call Andy phone
What station is actually in the Lighthouse frame of reference
Off
Which I don't care what you think it's like you
Just wrong
This is pretty accurate
Actually that
Incredible
Radio
Play another accurate would like
If I hold it still it's pretty stable and I'm moving a little bit it's really stable locally
Cos I don't think it does everyone for some reason
Every round
It's nearly as fast as coming in from the Lighthouse there hey
What the heck
That's ok so Josh do you know much about which way
Turn the sisters I don't really remember myself
Hi sweet
So the intruder by that people usually will describe is they will say think of it
Is the axis being defined by x y and z and the amount of rotation has been defined by W
Accept the amount of rotation is kind of
What was strange because it's like X squared plus Y squared plus Y squared 1 - they're so
Playlist
Where is the Isis
I
Don't know
What's really
Confused all the do we might be able to use this to figure out with what they could turn Ian's are
I'll get this to represent in alternian
Loungewear
No they're not just axis angle
So
No I think that
If I tried explaining it would just be the blind leading the blind
Ok right now I think this is a normal rotation
Whose laptop is on the couch
That was absolutely no sense to me because it feels like America
Play I hold it like
Zerozerozero
Me and that's confusing
James Stewart as the access into a Dev
Set the alarm w it's the unintelligent park so
I don't know how much I believe that but
Houses
So just so you guys know the Lighthouse is up there
I'm trying to rotate
I am so confused right now if I hold it like this then it's 00
I'm so confused
0001 it would mean that
The minus x axis on the HTC headset on a bike headset is
Going into the Lighthouse
Oh my gosh Turvey what in the world have you done these activities make no sense
Also sorry X Plus
X
X Plus is up
Turn by
Did you get it really yet
I got laid
I don't know how to figure out
Early on the extension architecture esp32
Example
Using assembly functions you can get in and I'll tell you the time exactly to process your text
Turn light 3 assembly instructions it's like a built-in aspect of the processor
I am
C c o u n t
So
So I'm still thoroughly confused
Ok so we have to Jack goes along with one side of Jan
Total side Quest
The the idea is were trying to figure out some sort of unified
Operate all of the poses within a poster with them like to live is basically
Systematics all the angles from giving my own house and then figures out where an object is in 3D space
From all of this information
And the second part of the second injector today is 4th year to get the esp32
Reading with the
The
Ask
Just be to read the
Read the date
If you want to display a calibrate it will tell you the lighthouses in the track objects as team
Lighthouse
I understand
Quiet
I really wanted to be intuitive like mathematically
Set alarm
What's the least look at Turvey Tory and get a feel for arm
Play Catherine this will be the figure out
Sorry
Because I like Mike are you are you for real
Actually
Like when you said plus expired
I just wondering if you do just double check what we think is the the the
Turn off the Onion
First and then we can verify
So under registration by age
Interesting
It says Katrina's queue XYZ which I am now inclined to believe but let's just
Play anyway
Aqw equals
Thanks bye
I'm still my Kirby the crazy thing I'm having
The
Actually know that there
Oh no that is actually wrong
Ok that looks nice
We hold this here
FFX
Do you want to keep charging those by changing the light on
You have like the song
Play nothing
Please
So far I have not found it
I don't know what size you are
Understand the light but I feel like if I said
The Lighthouse 300
Ok now it should be
That's probably what was going on
The rotation to b0001 instead of 1000
Are use a Sunday we using the lights
On my own
That's interesting to 0 or 100
What is being interrupted white house if I go in
So if I go
Into the Lighthouse decreases and increases
Man this rotation makes absolutely no sense to me
I am so confused there is no way that is this corner frame is right
Objects
Probably the right way to do this point
Actually do that
Cold now
Rod rolls overloading * 014
Change your name
Play radio
Turn on the living room lights
That's ok
Now I'm going to go create new thread
All of the representation
Stop
Window
Including a copy of 3D
Am I doing wrong
Turn the light on
A picture of a wall of lights
Open
Only vaguely
Yeah
Ok do that
Does the plane on bedroom light
Sometimes
Directions
Why
Thread
Should be able to set up some basic 3D stuff
I would like to make sure it's really
Kg lb
I need to look at
Show me
Put that way on it is like we are inside the White House
Set the doesn't really work because
Exit off for some reason
Stew
Access for a long time
So apparently
It's wrong I don't disagree ok
Plus s plus XL buy now
Possibly
The lighthouse on the ground and stood up and then
Imagine of Ray shooting for Friday and that is called the
Turn the volume room
Lights
What's the least something to me know what the world is going on
I'm going to go
TTR
Ok
I will reach out the thing as
Hi guys ok sorry about that so there's two things were going to be doing tonight
2 millibar cyclist
I want to do this one
Please try and come up with some sort of standard for the poses in so far as the rotation and
Position output from
Sitting up with like pointing up where is the Lighthouse relative to
Dad dad
Where is the club
5 headset relative to that lighthouse looking up
Poses with them Lights On by using the same right down the standard so we can actually pay attention to it
Everywhere
He's going to be working with esp32 and being able to monitor a position of a
TS
3362 3633 and esp32
Hopefully I might take
Rear A21 still and you really want it all on the esp32
Workout guys excess
You know what I'm doing is I'm trying to come up with some sort of way visually understanding
What would actually be coming out of the
The data from the posters
So right now I'm doing
Look like
Right now I'm just really basic stuff
Josh to that makes sense
So
Problem is that the posters themselves we don't really have a good way
Looking into them and understanding what Corner train everything is operating at
Settle line
Good call
Thanks
Calling sound
That shouldn't be an issue
White Crow
Amanda on here
Do you want the bathroom last
Thank you
Matrix is breaking
Like crazy
Where is here
This is just computer science I guess just the fact that I'm sitting here forever
Tell me something really like getting two lines to show up on a screen
What the heck
Use the Corner train I'm used to
What am I doing wrong here
Oh my gosh what is the
Should not be hard
Should not be hard at all
Now
My perspective nature supposed
Spell
That's interesting but
Send in the code I need in order to
Wow
How's my activator at hose
Can be unsavory
Aspects
Why is screen excellence
Oh my gosh
Providing the right values
What's
So what I need to do now as I need to write a function
Light xyz
Connect to my TV
Suggesting you get real-time yet is that
Turn off in 30-minutes
It was like this
Use xmpp to sync your changes
Once
You probably spent a very long time getting into work
Turn on the bedroom
Very interesting
Play perfectly by INXS
And we would
Each other
Can we win
Pause from down whenever when we get there
Eventually
BBC History you can see like you know merge commits 185
That one 26
Groups of people
What's the weather like in Hugo
And I be like
Can you do this
Where on the lines involved
Is there a car park in Derry
Works
Like Mike
The stuff they do where like
Home
Play
Something's
Very cryptic error messages that make no sense
What's the fastest
Stranded position of the saying on the screen
Sing a song
Are you ready to go on anything
Figure out how to login the team down
What is the right kind of thing
Thank you Rudy is that right now
Really need a forum post on how to do something with the ESB and
Like most things readers
Bye
The second one
So what you doing is because this is a double for me
You don't really dead advise there's no reason to add curly braces raining all because this is just
Xny so it's not like
All the way down
Play thank you again I just messed it up again
Redeclared something inside the White House
Probably draw a line joining outside of the five
What's what's do that
Plus line shooting out from broken
No we are already in explore space for the stupid Lighthouse
Thanks Turvey
There is no primitive Road paint bike with onions
Euler angles right by specifying
Somewhere or something
Wolverine
Muse
Light on
But I think it'll be really cool to apply
Oppose
Has that I can I can treat the sourest the system
So I really have I have
Xyz nhrs
I wouldn't do any of this stuff
Really what it should be
Time
Separate things
So I really think we should be switching this
Oh sorry for talking to chat
Oh I see you're saying Josh
I'm so
That is because I feel like ok
That is the right way because this function gives me on Ho's night
Can you give me sorry oppose with separate parts and quad
Just use this function
Yes you're technically right Josh
Radio world
Stuff
I could just use quite routine thank you
The hose thing
I feel life
Deposing should be opposes what gets passed to another position in Portmeirion
Just changed in life survive right now
Hope you guys are writing to her because this is
Can I change the VAT on bed
Are you working
Do you mind on
YouTube
Are you have to take That Number subtract that number and then see how much time has passed
Volume 4%
Yeah I don't think what you want after you I should be able to do as I should be able to take the pose
Given to me and then apply that codes
And I don't see any reason why when we pass these pointers to functions it would pass
Separate from the
From the position that should just be a complete close all together
Turn off ice Amy
Oh my god Kirby
Your poser is 1600 line 17
Turn the
Why is your poza 1800 lines wa
Oh no
Curvy
Fast and quiet do the same things
That saying bye
Pose
Expecting
Yes the Champion's tunic Apparel
Wait what
Smileys trampling spaces between your smileys
Smyths
Please
Amazon
I know Michael is going to crash but that's fine
Are too many arguments in function
The Lighthouse
Pause
Turn off Brown lamp
Kirby which which career entail
Postal code
I'm ok with the duplicate stuff in there if it makes things clean
Are you making any progress with that finger now
Episode episode of the current main lines of enquiry
I don't know
Play something exactly use the other power plug instead of that
Ok you can try plugging the SD card from there into the other one
Stop
See if this works
IPhone close
Ok so it looks like somebody wrote a pipos the point in the header file
And nobody ever actually brownie ball fighterz
What's the weather tonight
KT12
Stop
That was me
Ok Josh haven't you suggest applying that transformation again
I need to do a
Both 16 tables
Whether or weather
In the end
Like fun
All the cables
Green one
How's not realise this has to do it
Projector
Turn the light off
I'm not using my my USB
Great now
Animals that live in
Set a 5-minutes
Wonder if the power was just being jammed on the bus using this time
Do you mind handling
Very 1 calendar
Sally
You are allowed to do so
Get back to the
Off
On
Noise
Talented documentation Ireland portal
Hey
Actually Josh and figure that out for me that I'm really cool
I'm sure I do it wrong
Ok bye now
Frenchie
Is a black wire in a green wire which one should be positive and which one should be negative
I got black and green
Lights on
Play The Black into the black and green to Red
Ronaldo
Power plug
I wish we had more cameras so I could light switch camera used to like everybody
Ok to show people was going on over there
Turn on the lights
Over where you are
So
Mark over here is right now try and get the orange pi to work the orange pi
No
Raspberry Pi light for that does the porch theoretically the dark clerk of the
Are the HTC vive
That kernel so hopefully they fixed all those stuff though
The orange Pi actually can use the modify panel with acceleration and whatever Da Club
If you're ready we can go run life survive on an Orange Pi and then have some love all this way inside
Revive headset
Fairy Fountain dream big for a while and haven't gotten that far
What is the definition of infer
The Lighthouse
Something maybe going on
Every single quote
Cycles to be amazed
Do something to the internet so it doesn't fire again
Unless that's not
Coming out of it
Sing
Play convenient for setting a president dies and stuff
People request
I seem to find it on eBay
Sorry dude
Some catching up to do
I just realised I have no idea with apply closed
That would mean that you would wanted to
Being the poses local for hernia frame and then
It's like a point in closes local corner frame
Where is applied to a location first
And then shifted by the amount that the thing on
Yeah I really need is some way to
I really need a way to I don't remember
Classroom
Buying Orange
Living rooms
Anthem
I guess I'm just trying to do it
By the way Justin Argentino any code you paste into all the chat on the channel automat
Play becomes no no no
Having licence and you automatically transfer copyright ownership to me
This works that way
Oh I see I'm going to change down on the bed
Mourning the loss of my rotation code
Ok
Thanks
I'm really confused right now
I don't want I don't think that's what I want to do
No I really don't think that's what I like you
Help
Half
Biology notes
That's terrifying
Ok
Actually there is a funny story
Salon in college I have password in
When you reverse engineer or when you when you tried to crack it with the Rainbow tables I think it was under
Turn one second between when you gave it the hash and and when it
Cracked
It was also bad password
Is it bad
No it was not put it was
5 letters
Now as I discovered ok I need a real password
The end as an MP file system
Which is one of them
Absolutely public
DFS
Set alarm for 5
Don't give you
UK use any of the compromise mb52 get the source material
Yes
The plaintext I thought you could modify the Playtex in such a way that
Keep the same hash
Bob Willis
The shower is the moment they did they only have one specific
Versions of files with the same hash
The first one
Like you say anything
File
Very much
Hi Josh this is what I want to do in concert
Also I'm really concerned by watches am in here
Where
Supposably a unicode symbol somewhere in here
Rewrite it manually
How is that
I can't be on this out of the YouTube
And somehow
The cause
Everything beyond that point three spaces instead of 4
Fix it
Play the top of the fire was fine
I just had to ruin file by hand because
Caprice
Why
What is going on here
Breaking in
Heart
Wow it's just Host
So Joshua I really want to do here is I'm trying to
To take a point and then I want to rotate that point by the Britannia
And I want to translate it by the translation of The Pogues
I think that's the right way to do it if you want to check me
Updated rather than just image
Use it to compile lasagna
You are a terrifying man
No no no you just terrified me
Never never
Busted
Last few months somebody's desktop PC has been an Asus tinker board
Office
Why is the scratching
Alarm for 10
What's going on
A friend of mine had a think of the word eight 30
5.4 monitor
To down on my laptop broke
2 months
Depressing
Interesting actually turns out
Apparently he was able to get I really don't know the 80s think of Warriors so not really know what
What's that is
Off
YouTube
Never called why is this cold never called
Come on man or Linux system for composite video
I wonder if I having the chat inside of his terminal hear people are less inclined to spend because this
Speak
Non crown whatever
Hi
That's really interesting
Now it looks like it's out of order thing going on
Like
Like the data is going into the thing before the date is right now
So what's going on is one of the drivers get initiated before
The button Q summer is being populated
So this stuff looks like it's going to have to be executed beforehand
How old is Skipton if it was not
B&Q
Make sure everything's fine with you
Interesting Bob wouldn't come up until now
So I know what's going on here is having a sad day
Final of Watchmen
Turn LEGO tower game
Generally is saying that he are is overclocking his
Online
OK get Revived sitting still
What's in the alphabet
Also buy translate first
No ok so what we have as we have the union of an object so we have
This is another Lighthouse
Are rotation and
Position associated with it
The rotation the same
But I am move it through 3D space
Like this way of this way
Then
Yes but that position is unchanged
Rotated I only wanted to rotate by the amount it would be surface on cervix
What you in
So why do you invert the rotation I'm worried that I'd be doing like maybe it's solving the inverse of the
Or something
I really don't understand why invading
Why why would we would be in Reading
What does protein powder actually do
Does this quote about get kind you get quite routine Abell
No no no so I'm going from space to world space
So what I want to do is I want to say this point on the camera
Local attic space is like plus 1
X + .5
Where is that in world space if I have the pose of my camera
Right now I'm trying to figure out why
Fix this code
Angela Taylor
How far along are you
I'm using the timer
Music
Bromley
Light mobius
Sometimes I do that serious day
Always down
Tell me I'm really confused now
What's going on why is default not being called
Are you know it's nice when people post links in the YouTube thing by click on the link
My thing
It works
You are doing quite rotate first
What's going on here camera rotation ok that makes sense
That's exactly what I want to do Josh
What is actually going on inside quattro TT
What what why
What is this Josh
Was very strange
You taking the cross product of
Everything now
Cross product of the Union and the cross product of the Union
V
What's
Does this work at all
I've definitely broken turn lights around here
I Never Said
Aragog
You need to commit
Josh can you decode was actually going
Americas
I am
So confused by that
You are actually cross product King
Doctors with
Linkin Park
White quattro head
B+ 2.0 x crossover turn on xyz
Which is the product of the point
What's that
That crosses
Ok tonight
Crossbow
Just accepted as gospel and move on
Directions
King from the internet somebody says
Well I will have to try and see what happens
Looks like it's more stable especially if we have
Watching off
That was from Mercury engine
HG3
That's just insane now
I mean
I'm doing
Is now
This is the code I'm doing twice and cross products is
Watch mice last
What's the door code
I'm going to leave a no here
Themes of the freezer is Rocky
That's right we switched to the post from the post in
Position in Italian
Thermometer
I'm confident Mercury
Which was way better even though
Hey Josh
Yeah I would we need if we take life survive in using mercury three
Number 33 was kind of like
Mercury to we need back in the days when people called XML was good
If you guys could get along
That was bad
Everybody
Pause
List
Really like inspiration to json
Pretty much of the Ripper
It's much positive python
Play cool music quotes I can just
You'll do it
Json
So that's all so annoying that was one of the reasons that people so
Brfc released a new RFC
Play basically
Please stop making the mentality straight
Emitting and receiving
Because JavaScript is one of those things were like everybody in their brothers
Accept all these things without the double quotes what the heck guys this is terrible
And that's just now being a new guiding principle
Principle was Sound Liverpool received
Always always always
No
Maybe you should accept it not everybody's perfect the first time like lol
Tuesday
Give us a shot and see if if the position thing is updating as we'd expect
Susan December going to go into
Close as in quite right in the head
Something is up with R&R
Is it going to rain location understanding wrong angle
The whole thing is rotating around the access so I can get a better picture of what's going on
I love you
Have you heard of that project from the
Sorry tears
And overlays the 2D representation
Someone I want to do is I want to I want to pretend
Rotating around
These
Set the lights to 12%
We can also make high tea
Minute
McAfee
If you want
That looks like pointing in word
Topps Tiles
Stackoverflow review
Dating back to the first page to the last comment on a forum for earlier this week
Off
That you guys feel like we should know
Siri before and post just like everybody else that was the answer are you serious
I am convinced that this is 100%
Because
Electric Avenue
Yeah everything
Who desires the caffeine and what kind
That means
What's my name
Archery
Instructions
Can you follow instructions
Ok
Confusing
How we can just use normal directions instructions for cooking
Because like it's just like isn't it
How is 30 cups ok
30 cups of water is 3.5 cups of green tea
Play cups of sugar
You have a different television tonight
One cup of boiled water you stop boiling and you put the 2 minutes
Sugar in
Josh I'm going to leave this in for future use
Thank you with Josh
Ok so all I've been able to determine that
Oppose is completely and totally drunk
I don't
No it's make that I'm about ready to give up and move onto something other people doing
Yeah ok I'll definitely by the supposed to be there
Position
Do you think he's watching something from the launch
Show the airport
The ocean
You know what this is not going to get pissed tonight
Thanks for coming out
I10 Tara me I
I know what's going on you can also be my micro that's doing the transformation is broken
Stop playing song
Do you guys want to
Showing
Feedback for people do you want to have a screen share on your
Stream
Like with you have any
Now
Tuning a tiger up running
Password for Wi-Fi right
Actually no I'll do that I will get the ok so
Like I don't know what the deal is I am I'm frustrated now
Me
Sugar
Play things
1.5
Turn on the TV
Recommendation after graduation in electronics
Actually guys do you want to see the ridiculous thing that are
The other folks
I'll get my other camera and the mall record the video live on live stream 4 live
Doing live
Ok
My alarm for 11
So hold on
And then we can do a
Play the recording video
Probably not that one
I know what's not do it because I want to
Turn off see if I can video this
So basically a while girl people and they have gone
We went Home Depot they had these solar powered garden lights on sale
Next clearance
So we actually bought all of those dark because we realised
Please turn off when it gets light out and then when it gets dark
Dreams
You put the top off
This is a NOT gate
Somewhere out there
Can you turn off
So with an app game
Can get more points into it
You can turn into
Is very sensitive
How old do you want to try turn off that
So should be right now
By the reporting on
Temperature breaking
Call
The pretty good at working this way
Ok so
That is off
Days off
Vice versa
Turns out
So this is 11
Realise
Why
Hey Google would you take any number
Because
Online
Today afternoon forever
What is the capital of assyria
The side of this state
I'm basically so I can sell it
Turn it down
Because by the time you get background
Really fast
So between these parts of an and gate
Can we have a memory cell
So we should be able to build a pre-op computer if we can get enough of these
And tweak the the light Bolton area just right
Will vinegar
Turn on the rolling shutter you can really see it
So stable lights don't have a rolling shutter
Like this
But you can see that these ones because they're breaking so fast the rolling shutter
Makes it so that it's really apparent that they're freaking out and blinking on and off super fast
Lights on
Stop
Even use the tubes to the light tonight
You have
Museum
Use the hard drive Platters to
What's this
Light calculator
Before tender
Solar garden light turn off light
Turn it all the people online I like what did I do
TV schedule
Ok
Hey Dylan can you have dairy
Oh my gosh
Is there
I have coconut milk
What is it
OK well that also work with this
Yes but green is
What's the actual cream
Some sort of coconut cream
Is it Christmas
Specifically
Stop
OK well that sounds like a might taste good with
Dwarf things
The right now
Trial cooking by Charles
What's the people screaming
Music by YouTubers like a Jag algorithm
Stop
Riots
Ok
Eventually you will be crate
Never do that again
Change to BBC One
Ok so where is the picture that we put the TN
Off
Is after
Sunset
Radio based on now
This 2014
Just doing
Network auctions
Pretty good
I mean
Recipes I think it could be greatest war
Recipe
What is Lee min-ho
People's
Anyway I just try
Stop until I find the one thing that you eat
MOTs
Do something
F1 pizza and now two people first up
I don't know what you have to do to make something with three quarters of a cup of sugar and it tastes bad
Online
Ok will try and then you can just
Boots
Fight song
What are you
Actually ok
Can you get the reading chat
Turn it up
Mayo ok next live stream on now
Limelight 2 more webcams you guys to watch location
That's awful
Next of one cup
Without
Wake me up
Can you take one that promoters light
How much more tea
Masters in maths
Michael was doing
You should probably stop the camera
Stop
Can you use a coconut
Play s
Yes my Xperia X unknown linked to my search engine
Who is that
Like
It would be
Rice and cream and cinnamon Girl
DNS
I'm sorry
How old am I remember they're here
Michael style
You know they have all the one in the style
While the other under similar result contact because
Actually light
Behaving themselves now
Play my library HTTP client library and do the whole thing in here
I will definitely
Thank you Matt for door
In case you missed it I just shout
Very quiet
Implementing that
Is the property I'm sorry
Black and brown green is power
Is that buying a Frenchie
Lights out
This is what you just posted in I am so confused by this picture
Absolutely no sense to me
Eyebar things
Charles slow matches
Lettering the centre reindeers the the camera
Decorating is the tracker the other two or cameras
Charles Lomax of your open TV
Does it matter at all
Can I still buy a ring
Coronavirus
I know this works because it does it
What's the operator
Confusing what it would look like if I took
Mike Posner in rented in the switch
I mean to be fair
Sorry is also correct
Position orientation
Hot take on access frames
I think so you just posted this is what they've been using desktop PC
Aaron Moorhouse holmburn I didn't understand the topic
Adidas
Looks like
Rooney what team do I mean on a form
Don't think it's banana pie
Ok
1 - 10
And has a big clock and has video acceleration that would also be cool
Mark
Stop
Which is the
FIFA 17 PS3
Find the one from scratch
Stop
Just wondering when he talks
Banana Pi duo
He says you have been on already and you can convert that back into a fact
I'm glad you guys are here
And they say yes they can hear you ok
What is this masked
Why is this existent
This had video out
Duo
How
How is the even possible
Yes
Play Sweet Nothing distracts origin on my mind
Ok so you guys can do that you guys know what the deal is with Carol on the Old winner
BBC apparently asking hard
Divided exactly 9 FPS
They call it
Real
Ok
If you do that can you still get custom plans
You can compile the song Exile as a
Subtitles online
Turn James light on
I think I mean that was
Mobile
If you guys online wanna try to get
Hi Google do custard not raspberry the other one talking about
Running with custom outlines
Hey
I use to make OpenGL
The install of this junk
Installing LED driver and networks
Step-by-step guide to do it
How's the mainline kernel only the
Somebody out there seems to understand
Have you ever gotten that working on a Raspberry Pi
Cancel
I'm supposed to be off-topic
When you can take a peek
Tell Rooney you are using on
You're using your SPC and
I'm sending can you 4K what can I do combination of custom outlines along with video gallery
You can
Ok you got your ex back
Breeders
Things I should probably drink with right now
Whitby
Just tried to do a different type of rotation
Is it going to be
Goes
Are you XYZ right ok
Hello
It's not plugged in because I use the USB cable for the camera
That's me
Extension cable
Waitrose Dublin
What is the weather like in Thailand
Skip
Google scrap this tst-622q with Dad
You can't use that the reason is that the mycenter produces
Is the carrier wave it does not produce like a nice clean like on off
How useful that would be to you
That makes me wonder what you're doing is a really I think
Value to have support for multiple sensors
Did you actually have the horse characters
Between those two things that seems like a problem
Maybe if you were using I haven't let them know you might be able
Use that instead to process PR
Then using the timers
Do you have
Set up an alarm
Something esp32 eskimo
Wacky
Have you guys
Because I have that works been out then
Rugby matches xdrivers accelerator are needed to make it work
Could you imagine if you did this in actually made a hell 2
Ok maco MK if I give you money to do it
You actually do it or there
It would be really cool crazy
Skip that's that powerful and nobody knows how to actually use a mainline Kernel on it with video accelerate
Literally seems crazy to me
32-39 Lord Ashdown
This particular one I believe it does it's dreams
Double check that it has stream in
That's what you really want and this one streams in it
Probably too slow for you
Is a Tom if that's a please pens on the esp32
To stream the data in from
And then it to them and then you can go read the data
Compare live stream through when you like an extra operated compare the frames to each other and
You could say clever in how you do it quickly
Up on the spot in down on this clock to
What is this something you can probably do without too much effort in the work so you could you could probably
And see how it goes
I have not worked in 9 months by 9 months ago
Yeah yeah
Making things work
All the lights
You guys drink that much
Did you want any of the tea
Is the bit left is going to be
Where is the try guys right now
O'keeffe's working on actually
Stream
Coconut milk
Video stream
If you want you can pick up alive and well known
This
They're still talking in chat about details baldi.exe driver
The problem with the Raspberry Pi Jamie Christie is that
Raspberry Pi does not support better can have more with the device
Does not support them at all
Navigate to go to work with the hardware physically cannot get that stuff without like
Ok
A proper display driver for somebody and put it already gone in schedule
4.17 mainline kernel
Hey hey hey hey release date is there anyway we can get an answer right now
Volume 17
Take me to
45-16 is production stable
Thank you jail
Attempting to have these charge themselves
Yes
Do you want a video on my channel
Stream
YouTube videos
Yeah
Blake
A high person
Define hyper
Looks like it's doing a lot of other stuff in there too
Volume to use on light turn up
Yeah
Oh definitely no we don't want to do that
Turn the lights off
You don't want to mess with us
That does that
Filter or summer
USB removed USB
USB
Play some more stuff
Does gastritis
What are they using recently orange playing one
Fingers
Please please be Paragon so you can Ltd
We know nothing
Double A batteries magfest employees turn
Emperor
I did forget to put
Volume down up to put it in there though
What's the time again
Stream in for USB
No it's gone forever
I2s stream put into USB
Alarm off
Working on a huge missing thing there
Probably we heard it so
Does Oxford FM
Yes that was a cool Project
Garden lights
Just happened to be calculating crimes or something
Actually can we just manufacturer from China
Turn lights
Light designed the garden light specifically for this purpose we would all be power
Turn off of work for forever
Remember Night Time comes to thing
Extra bright lights be able to adjust
If you half an hour prices
Made
It
Transistor water tolerant so
Everything in silicone
Just do nothing
Turn off
Rvt filter so you can code with Code information with colours
It's not too far
Reduce stupid stuff already man
Ok will be crossing the xyz
Feel like in the past couple years I have more than like a week without seeing
Stop alarm
I always keep forgetting with w
The cockerel is running
Lights
I would not put it past me to recompile it from scratch
You should not use it
I'm just not working
Turn off the TV
Create this book
Mind you
Eventually
No I do use the lot of stuff from the camera that's true
Ok you should be able to actually use that and you'll have to go which
Who's the couple that need to change on the
What's left when you configure the ice cold see you need to change a couple of lights camera and it's like
Can you should be able to vary
Use use
Clay Cross
This is awful
I want to keep the individual lights that simple layers are you still there
Red could be Clark signal on distributed by each unit drink
You have to
Like transistors
Bargain Jackson's gay men
Yes yes
More people who've been getting involved over the last couple of months so I'm pretty sure this is now like this way
Mei Mei importantly pretty high at this point
Definitely from me
White survived
We just made a tyre see for ourselves song
Hi how are you everybody is going to keep working but I feel like I'm finally starting to make progress after 5 hours online
Let me know how a building goes
Volume down
No no but then you said the bits to stay I just want to read the digital lens
Then you can just stop the tea room
I think we'll be a good idea sooner or later I go fix my demo
Sorry about that
Anybody else
You can search it if you look for Iceberg Carroll iceberg ice word s
Parallel esp32
Someone out there might actually have a
Or better yet you could check out my Repo from a date in the past
Actually I can give you the
The date to check out
You should check out from
June 1st 2017
Can you do a get checkout
Of my demo from June 1st 2017
Esp32
CQC Morgana
And what you do is you check out from
That one from the
Christian Jackson
Are we have this now we're going to go for it
For the night you don't want the end of my eyes I really don't want that stuff
Think that's the one you want
That one that one
One of those two whichever one bills is the one you want
Interesting plants
0 equal to
2 x 220
Fingers crossed that's different
Bra
Strong
I wish Josh was still here because I can't go to work
Crossing the 2chan
W x y and z
W x
Cross 3D both of those things
Currently looking into the
Who's looking into the RBS
Right now
If that's cool
Captain's never that's ok because the cross 2D function here outputs
3DA
Time
Is setting a persona on fire cast
Hey dude thanks so much that's really cool
I'm picking up the wrong values that's why
Come on
The date is different and it's reasonable
Excellent
Very
Actually it's exactly the same
What is the news swanky way to multiply two vectors by
Apply a invitation to a
Despite
40 x 5
Avant credit
Ok
Look at the the at me and see if it's running the in Gemma or the alterna
One of them one is H
There is
Instagram dedicated to
Sizes in space
Exactly what you need to
Play
Something that looks like a synthesizer
What is
Turn the radio off
What happens now
Is it working for you
In the morning tomorrow you want in demo because you'll be reading indila
Say what
To be on Wi-Fi
That's really confusing
Actually it looks like it's poses
Exactly the right thing I don't know why the apply function have been wrong and I also don't know why
Someone into of watching the screen but it's definitely if I look at the numbers like right now
What's rooted very heavily towards on
2 + x -
Swine
No it's minus x cos I'm ok
Corner trainers x off which is confusing by
Looks like your further along now
What's the we can formalize an idea as to how these processes
What's the time
Stop going on what is wrote do you know
Wxyz
Video
Stream
CNN
Down down down down down
I'm gone
What's the next one in the end
Go down
Ok
For this
Tell me 43 people
My favourite is a really long time doing almost nothing
Oh no
Twitter
That's the wrong
Play Blue text
How to make Twitter refresh the
Room number
Lights off
Right now
Open interesting thing if he intended it was
So he's taking the Lighthouse quaternions
Positions
A20 does the Lighthouse calibrations for really are 3D space consideration the fact that
If that's how you position of lighthouses
You should probably just tried to compile with that and then so
Music
TV streaming
I know which check out the one it is supposed to be
Pearl Jam Ten
Double check the
Yeah I was just trying to make the main call the accident in functions
What's my name
Because you don't want it
On this
You can go to the
Instead of doing that right
In cast
What
Alarm
RCN
Take ibuprofen at 10
While true
Pause
Printouts in Italian
My one
Account
Hull
Underscore countdown
Ok so now you actually it is it is operating
If you want what you can look at you
On
Cancel my phone
Re but somewhere you have to tell her
Where the data goes descriptors
I squared buffer
No I would like the first element
Reprojection
What is reprojection
Am I serious printing currently on
London Eye
Projection branch
Projection
Skip branch that's why
Leather something
Turn the light to alarm working on
Skip today
Just like the first percent
8X
RPG
Opg
That's weird
I don't know I don't know what to say weird
Lights off
Playing game I think
Sound
Benjo triangle
Cancel
Ok so spicy
The next thing is
Talk about
Can you send
Zero 8X
To do it
Again
Bradford brackets 00
You have to
Who's better friends
Ok so now
Tell me everything
Set alarm
Imagine Ireland
What are these days I should actually use flask properly
Siri
Another
Yeah I'm totally going to watch this player
Lights off
Can you direct messages off
Are you serious
Why would you ever
People do things you'll get answers
Heating
Hey Google
Only know one or 10 x 96
Ok
Royal my hotspot from my phone
White
Lights on
And I really want
Pause
Hey Bella
If you stream
I want to see it
An artist if you want to see it
I I want to see
Ustream
That was confusing
Waterline
I want to see if he does it I want to see it.
And then let me know streaming
Get rid of everything else just rubbing off the internet kill it
Not both
All hoses
Give them a lighthouse at
Lighthouse
Disney Plus
Which 50A pose of 08001
Produce
Proper
Object stay for the
I like anybody who actually has a big in life survive I'm really hoping you would be right now
Make sure that we all agree on this so you guys can all read it
I really want it actually agree on this and if we can agree on it then things will be
I think very good
Specifically
Still around but if you are I am really hoping that that you can
Light mirror fires
And the same thing goes for albinos
Well I not remember your name and everything so
Still should be handled
Looking at your own picture of this
Hey Justin ok
Alarm to make sure that we agree on
On on the the definition of it
Proper AliExpress for the the object being tracked
The object being tracked
The Lighthouse it should be at
Bank of
Lighthouse Bude
So now you probably want to do is
Figure out which pins in the I squared as Potter in thing on map 2
The that you have that pot India
The pin number for
If you look in the Stream in
And so you find one that's like your 45 and 8019
I have plugged into
Should we be number 44 because the UK Open
Do you want to unplug the septum pierced
26-33 and verify that it actually goes love
Microlight
Ok so don't forget about that
My classes are spin defining zooplus to find Xbox as well
I mean it is right hand rule with all other map on far as I can tell
When is an interesting point out what are you defined as the rotation of the base station
People
I'm gonna go away
If it's on the ground
Nud passes up
Then
You
My middle finger is Big Boss
And I'm going to go with
This thing right here is white what
And that would be the direction from the lighthouses point of view it was sitting on a table with the run
Down
Ok hold on
Make light coloured flowers and you're taking and living room
Love my vibe
Ok
Take a white house right now in wall actually
Just write this first
Insured
Positioned
From the Lighthouse
Pause
Brown Brown
I upside down
Can I think that he is almost there
Arm note
Correct
Yes it does
Which is the original intention
What's the meaning of your own
Come on
Ok to do work at gravity vector coming from my house
Sorting out and see you new one
What's 9
Down
It 1
Play XYZ axis
Play Hopsin
Turn on the bedroom
We should probably match our location so it may offend me
Yeah
What
Ok before we write this
Oh is not finalised
Before we finalize it let's go find out with the gravity
Otx2 colour help us
Zelda xyz
What value is in using the acceleration data from the Lighthouse calibration
We would definitely want to be using all of the devices that were calibrated by and you information
Another thing to maybe helpline
Is running right now
Calibrate
That makes no sense
We're definitely getting something wrong
Can you give me a second
I'm going to a mountain lighthouse now and we will see
What's actually going on
Ok so now you know you can read the data from this point
You could do something like a plus
If you go into the code for the iceberg
Scroll way down the bottom down here there is an is10 isr
Is currently reading but there is a way I can
More soon
Through the buffers
On be able to tell me through the day
All whenever completed and then you can go red like stuff through the data
11 the time and you can keep a current account
And then the left and this time that
And then the next train is low again or something you know that time it went well
That's seems like a place and then you can use that to monitor
Like events coming from the things or something like that
Right now you could probably just
What have it have a thing in there like a counter where the first thing it's called you know it's on the Buffer and the next
It's called you know it's on the first offer 10101
Get cold
Every single time on the airport
The buffer is full you can operate on that data
Which is what we put out the Darwin
The first time that function gets called by the hardware
After the first time you can look at the first and all the date in the first bus
The next time I called you gonna get through the day in the 2nd
In the second bathroom in the second half
That will probably work
Movinga
Ok
Which was
Really
Today's daylight saving
People probably dead now
The first day of autumn
Exterior lights on
I'm running at the deadline tomorrow morning
On the timer
Anymore
Cancel the picture
Tip top the
Hi Alicia t32 fingers a little painful but I'm sure that once you start actually getting data
It's going to be a lot easier
Like what you can start passing through at 10
Stream absolute
Gloria definitely
Completely useless to try to tell what the actual angles are
But it doesn't look like he used to think frame because
When it's like that
Like straight up and down the Y component is positive
Please
Negative
From green point of view
Please tell me how is brain works
That's really cool if we all just buy happened to Belmont
Off
On the tractor
Always possible so
Producing negative 39
Thank goodness
Hey like I'm free
Stop
No giving him
All the crumbs
I can
The down so from
Point of view it would be best if this was negative
What is the
Set the gravity vector
The down
Moonlight the up vector from the lighthouses forward vector from the Lighthouse in point
You know what
This is how I imagine it
Setting up on it staying there
This is a very large negative number right now
Time
Outward 11 towards
This is looking at the Lighthouse
A receiver for the white house now to go
Where is
It says -3
Pause wine over 47c
Play the devil
Porridge
I'm going in the sea answer just 10 minutes
I'm so confused again
I'm the 18 years receiving data from the Lighthouse it is not caring about
Play acting as a dumb receiver
I think I earn more than friends
Common
Hello
So much
Entertainment for real
Oh you know what it was updating and I was holding it
Turn the vibration was problem with it
Music
Can we can we act like
Away ok so it's measuring e-force against gravity I didn't see that one before
If it's unfortunate gravity
Wanted to be positive Z in my world
Would be up
It was an inspector pointing up
Yes that's what I'm hoping
Objects moving away from the Lighthouse positives and negatives
Link invention the figure out
My inclination would be the same as positives
No it's not no she's just gone
In the Liver again
Coming out music
I'm ok with this what's this
Does seem fair or whatever
Ok ru
No when the Lighthouse is
Condition
I'm ok with that
Set the right hand rule works and you can't read it like that the Cartesian plane
Like the angels make sense in X and Y
Ok
How are you
Light on
Who to talk to
Alarm
Hey no I'm talking to you
A lot easier to draw
Return pass Texas backwards from taxes
The Lighthouse
Then things start to make alarm set
Ok
I see no reason not to use this I think about that I do like it it's a bit weird
Because I wish I was a white house on my back in for telling the plus that put the
Up
Yeah that does kind of mess with
Lights off
Because I be worried about posting a publicly in
Github repository
The picture right here
How do I
Forgotten how to actually
Looks like the cloud
Useful
You should have another space to most of the Rose
Turn the lights off
Can you just do that done
Lighthouse
Pause
ATG
Ok
Cavity base playing recording and all of Leon 1p alfa-2b roughly
Recording
Emotion in Motion
And then stop
In motion and stop doing that
Because we will also give us a like that we can work again
Final affected by
That would be really nice
Emotions
Valentines by Carol giant
Skip
We will have something that wall at least verify that our stuff is not stupid
I want to do this and the
And the
Turn up volume
Free camera system
Ok I would imagine the matter what I was going to brutally crushed
Concerned I could believe it
Excuses
So what you're saying is we are forced to trust you
Are you waiting on Mark take you back on
I'm sorry I didn't know that
I love you
We will probably try and we'll all different
General
Respectively
The second is the rotation good for good there I think
Livery on Now 1
And then the second one is open or should be sure
With the front of the Lighthouse
Looks like music
Ok
I hope we can work on this
Lights on
Rmkv Ladbrokes enjoy your
Lights off
Yes you're welcome
Ok so I am going to take
The is not universal indicator using
Pause for all situations where he is
News
Turn off
Stop playing around 8 or 87
3000 lying on its back
The Lighthouse
Zerozerozero
Lying on its back
Turn off word
Actor from the amateur
0 positive 55 right
Incurred
Get tricky
How can I get this park ride
Maybe we should we should have the Lighthouse
Have the definition with his right here
The Lighthouse is
Lighthouse 5
Differently later
A brown owl
My house
The Lighthouse
Lighthouse
Yes it would be you're right it would be
Will reviews
Close of
Euro 0 of 1
Think that's correct
Although no this is wrong
Are we finding the post of the eye
At some point too
I do want a rotation because
What ar no carrier will be
Oh actually no
Do that
Friday
This way back to the same
Union to B18 5JS
Hey Kirby or somebody can you do the same sort of thing with the tape and with you or
Based on the imu cos I'm starting to think that the proposed
Sing is wrong
Pose with Michael definition for what way is up and down in in everything on
Which I believe I did
I know I don't know
I know is that issue
Refrigerate here
That might be the problems work
Yes
I agree we are right handed
Do you know the copyright status closed on that like that would be awesome
I do not run looking at know what I'm looking at now bye no friends
Is able
Hornet
Local to the hmd
And then
News
Transformed point to WorldPay from the
Lighthouses
Light of the
I think we all agree that is the direction it should be that light
The poser should give you the position of the object
From the Lighthouse is point of view
Is when you're doing the calibration
BST data structure
Seriously only Northern line
Really healthy at the base station opposes elsewhere I think go away
From LA pose
Old is complaining to be a 30 card
Ok
Actually that's a good question and not remember where is the Lighthouse
Pause it
Play Spotify
Rape videos
The poser should use the same flight out closes when calculator
There's no question about that kind of the definition for the internal operation
And like the intermediate like when you get a lighthouse poem
Suppose of the hosts of the
WorldPay
For our example
The Lighthouse is a 000
Practicality Lighthouse
Other side
By applying the output of the
Ok when we read everybody agree about that
Ok I wish you have an HND that you can
I'm just checking all everybody doesn't agree with
Is your should always be returning the
Listen or pose of the object that they're tracking
And weather in my ideas when you first RL
And then you say 1000
And then you apply everything and it would be giving you the effectively and lighthouse based at
Everybody agree there
What is the patient data
How's
Off
Ok stream houses provide pose
I'm ok so now we need to define
Read sorry
Defining the value of pose in
PlayStation data
I'm incline to 1
Nothing else tonight
I think will be good for tonight
How far along are you
Stop
Constance Oldham
Does Netflix use data on mobile
Emedia wing mirror device
I am now
A hard-wearing in userspace but spotting is Lidl's Connell
So I think
Pause James
OK Google find the value of clothes in Beeston
What are the pros and cons of defining this pose
The White House's position in world space and its rotation
As a conversion between
The you take a point on the Lighthouse inside lighthouse based and you apply the pose
Gives you a position in world space
Will convert
Bang Whitehouse local space
Volume 28 position in world day
Calibrating
You have an armchair
Define 000
You will need to
Hey good home and invert
Poses will
Song Moses
Alarm
Turn the TV on
I'll buy frenchies that means something like an hour ago
Spotify
Ok just checking
Take into counterpose of lighthouses
Operation and return of object
The lighthouses
Off
Ok I think that agrees with the
Without by our friendship there
It's a little bit too really gather it but I'm pretty sure that is the same
So that would actually Media case I think we agree on it all now
I'm gonna go upload this picture into
Ok Toby and everywhere I'm going to go this into the discord chat
And then we can
Verify that we agree on all seasons on
Studio
Differences
Different
How long is danger statement about sing lighthouse with an anchor point
Is all kind of want
Daylight saving someone
Quiet
It's 145
Because they haven't gotten to 2 yet is it 2 everywhere
Who am I
Lights out
Wait 3
News
11:45
My world is everything all terrain Green
I'm very different than I was
Burning thing
Poppers
And there's no it operate the whatever is on the screen
Early looks like the last time
Driving
Start lights
How is London I always feel weird because I'm like I don't I don't want
I don't want
Window Direct
Open the gallery GL
Relieving light
Stop the volume driver protocol after my next flight
Turn on
Believe that the only
More work and most people who want this
Not to use it with x
And there is no problem with using it with no negative consequences
The more layers you
And I do
Data files in a virtual environment
Environment variable to script
Done for today
I'm guessing you're not in the next 5-minutes
Pause the ground for five minutes
The rest of the world
Why
Listen to the books from
Put the timer
Put batteries in it in there Mike
20-minutes
Runs until the right time
Thank you only just got a cute one
PowerPoint
Are you referring to the DMT machine that Mark was mentioning are you referring to the female that
Why does my washing machine that they could use to calibrate receive 5 data to
Work on
Email
Feel like it's within reach
Especially like
Around the corner
Why
Play my own version of space pirate trainer
The value driver Repo
Intuit
Remove that last to do
Tracking system
Camera tracking
We love the vibe and we have the
Platform
Time for jelly
Turn light
Compare them all on
But you have to get something
So you're saying like you
From steamvr
Remind me at 4 from the Oculus bigger
Yeah
I just live
The only problem is
Right now or the lighthouses and crack
Brt system
Bolton please
Radio speaker
Just wondering classification robots
Light on
Which one is the Mali
Acting like a children
Going on
Sorting make bows Neon Trees
Why is
Make install anything else
Tkl
Models
Now
Play something ok I'll files anywhere in the tree
Angel
Turn on spirit
IKEA file anything we could possibly producing
It's nothing little brucehill file
OC files reading what we doing
Really interesting
American operate with or without 11
I don't understand what you're ok
If we have a positioning data for it it would help
Alarm to call eftal values
Probably Out of Reach
Depends on very specific representation that day
Better do your own
Equipment calibration
And we could probably be
Back light wood bathroom from FM
Especially if we have
You could take your arm thing
And move the object for lighthouses point of view
Very Extreme Edition
Any idea
That's fine
This is more than enough for all over any disability later used more than good enough for that
Hi
I have ASDA up and running what is fba
New song close
Austin
Surrounded
Just looking for anybody else who's talking about you missing my idols
Could I just tried running eggs and running the playing and turn off Windows complain about the modules
Painful
I am inclined to believe that the modules will not be produced outside fly
YouTube
About library of the dark story PDF
To do
Exactly
Call switch
Are you guys watching the Stream
I think it's going to disappear
Hot pepper
It looks really cool
Osteopath
Reduce the effect would have to do with it off
No it's got a have continuous
Is Deli containers can be inside
Play
Pretty sure
Yeah
Ok had to be like this
Where
Continuous
Orlight
You are 18 absolutely viral
I'm pretty sure that is the dress Theatre
I like this weird doing that
You could just be that all those things they are ok
The same thing
I like that Dad
Where is holding the can
Dad
No my my reservations would just accepting that is going to be the next planned release
I did this a year ago and they said almost exactly the same thing
Light a year ago they said oh yeah it's going to be the next time
A later and there is literally nothing done that has gotten any closer to this
Are you serious
I'm so angry
I just
Ok whatever
Turn the radio off
Giro exodus crash
Oh you know what
How dare they not get working on anything in a year
Burn
Is Siri more than you
Do you mean the same word waiting for the rest of the world to get there together I will kind of by now
Project team site
The question comes do we actually make this livestream public or not
I can tell really much was done useful
Brighton open dating things network
What do you think
Nothing
I'm not running free 3D things right now
Reading James the arm
Peterborough
Add dx11 decor.com
Just like always ONE Post
Experience in Vida Loca
Off
Interesting with an LED driver has an example file on airplane
Man today what do you want
How long even know anymore
Streaming 4 hours to 7 hours
My mind is blown now
Will try and like right now or trying together
Orange Pi one behaving
3D Star
I don't know if I've had a burn that's taken literally
What what happened on
Set alarm song
It is realised something really
Skip
Who sing that get key
Bali
Is this really terrible
Light
I can't believe that we are the only people in the world you actually want to try to get 3D working on
One of those systems
Are people from 2014 at this morning
Like in the last 2 years
3D acceleration
Clock
I don't know
0 people border has 4K support
Small
X86
Getting a 3DS working with the bedside lamp
Quite the problem is we can use because getting the dark cloth for the vibe working
Is that
Which we were asking if you're still here
Is what happened with the the vibe was that people started programming in other other video
Some points on music
We don't really need them and they just
Or was like some sort of light required for the standard
Is asthma a dry
Do you have a HTC vive just wondering
Somewhere
Working with
Explain the two reason why does support the other one is because
If you don't really annoying
DLA
You know if the 34 stuff cos like other people said like yeah you can actually
But I have never been able to find out how to add video mode
The main line video drivers mainline
All of this is going to be in space for Life survive
Are you doing something
There is a concern you only have 4.1 GB left
UK
Uploaded to Google drive to me
You know you are working on getting it working on the matter one then
What is the current VAT
The new one
How old are you
Checking now
Next
Please like none of them really surprised that they would be open with that
Michael Owen the lexical on
Yes ok
Quiet
What is what is BD
It's not lying down
Blinds4less position on Driver
Power drivers
GRM
Names for the
I like the right side of the screen dim
Oh my gosh
2015 languishing
Turn on the radio
War of the ok
Hey
That's all the calculations for the rock FM
Amazon drivers
What healthy diet really is acting like right now
I say that
Reasonable chance I think
PC World
Forearm calculating
28k
The liver
TV light in hardware by the Light
Candidates by the A10
Which mean like you could like a virtual
HDMI get mode
You know that meaning
Reviews of the accident
The thing where you hold the configuration for HDMI device
Is it
Raped
Edid
That is absolutely terrifying how much is 100ml
Volume to 3%
Imagine not based on looks like that
If I can find the median of something
Play
By which involve information
Downloadable Eastham
To-do list
Because you would need to specify an orange by 111
Is like a heart
Read the volume 14
Videos actually sent to the monitor
I am curious why they will have a file with that name on it
What are you up to
Up
Migration
Website
Are you actually using extent word
Remodelers so I could have won
Alarm
Go to run on ESP
So can take in light
Request stop
And some point that into
So I have a server
Call out to
Harding
That leads to
Half directly to a server
Punching
Eventually let it manage confirm
I find it surprising that there are this many people on the planet who actually understands enough
Everything
I don't see any
Anything like that
It looks like it is using me
Like that
The different one
I think you're supposed to do it
Oh you know like me there using hardware
It's so funny and I were all I do everything in software within I don't really
Time
Stop
You find a config Park
I don't think the radio tonight
Thank you everybody for coming out
I guess I can make it
Public live streams I don't know if I really want to
Because we didn't really accomplish all that much
If you open chat like watching do you would you want us to make
Or is it not really
Ben if they every shoes Oscars for burns you would be in the running for the policeman
Turn on Sam's light on
Write down when in the video stream is really never
Call Norman cabin
We like to save it on the Ganges or something like that
Wait just
Caribbean new partner
Next
I think Mark
Screens
Hello seduce light to 100%
Volume get down
Ok we'll head over to the lights to buy discord
At least the streaming is going to stop
Ok
Fairly well