Hello everybody and thank you for coming out to this V12 I think you're up to our lives
Five live stream and this was really fun because I got a Snow Day today
Go watch the snow out my window while working on all the stuff now an ordinary we kind of
Spaced out all of the live streams over a fairly wide bit of time and that was because
We were going fairly slow until I'll buy no friend who is also known as
As I G David Berger on who is apparently neither albino or French
Decided to start contributing to live survive and all my he really
Hi Gear here with the probably a couple hundred can be it's over the
Couple weeks here
I'm actually really curious I can see that on his profile here
My where are you to David Berger
How do I get to you
J David Berger get up so this guy
When is this guy has been committing tons and tons of stuff including
In epmp poser now for Life survival were trying to do is figure out where
Houses and then what's mean
Houses are based on the headset then we can figure out where the this the hmd is in 3D
Yeah we're also able to figure out where virtually any other devices are including not artificial valve
Traxxas so hopefully like survival be fairly
Versatile in wide-ranging as far as it uses could be so what we've been trying
You up until now hours can create all of these different poses and algorithms in order to take the sweeps of light as they say
Cross and figure out where the thing is now up until now we have been
Last in spectacular this and that was why I guess the last week or so
When she started getting done
Is he was able to actually did through now in all of that there were a number of problems found deep within the other light
Core part of life survive the problems is his poses right now require the use of sea
Aegon
Can I fly to the long-term before right now I am more than happy to take his stuff with all the odd ball
It's fine because it got us moving it found tons of problems and we have a much better system for
Well
Running the whole life survive new configuration option tech right now I can run it with Kim
Decoration auction so like if I go at it like config json and I looking here
Headlight default poser poser territory which is the default browser instead I want to say
On closer is a default closure is poser
I'm now deciding if I go do that look at this it's selected by P&P poser you can actually use
Turn the line flags and their useful now which is like
Turn my Hall live he's also one of ridiculously awesome stuff which is like so I can
Unlike a data recorder
Headset back in its place
Which I will bring to you guys attention
I'm so right there sitting on that chair is the headset and what were
Time do you were going to go wrong data recorder recorder the normal way that you wanted
We're going to run data recorded in the ridiculous work on
Also he developed the whole play Back to Black
Playback system
No this is just
Insane on somebody go use websocket d with data recorder and
Go on
I'm going to go look in the tools free power and then under here there is like this thing that
Find it is right here you go open up this thing
This is using
I think it's ridiculous it's using this thing website and that's just a regular
And so now we can visualise where the
The
In 3D space
On
Ghost weakness
Set up doing that I'm going to go use
Will actually go use the pozary P&P for both a cow
Fig
Things running radio
Ok so we're going to go run this
Ok
Refresh
No I don't want you to
UPnP
Like dynamically
Using pozary PNP now for everything
Cancel is doing the ODEON Exeter
I'm so just got packets 0 packets 0
Come on Forest other packets
Set down to the wife not running first
Calibrate
Making lighthouses
I know what's going on here
Macmillan do it that way
Accused poser Kirby Tory for the other thing
Word cloud
Hopefully they'll be faster
Can you use the
Banakum use the Kirby big you later ok
I hope that was supposed to be just a quick presentation
Ok now to actually running
What I want to do I want to set
Allowed to Thailand
The whole time I could just get that one value and everything would have been fine
On Hay can something of an A1
PC does not run on a on that quite yet though there will be a time
And we'll see how that goes ;-) I'm actually doing a port myself for itself
The right now this is
Getting vo2max data
Continuing
Hopefully this is actually going to work right now
Pingo to check this out better I'll buy your friend she me
I'm going to go pick this up and moving around
Can you can see that it is actually working
Design move this around
It's glitching up pretty bad
Bye
He is able to take his cpnp poser and it does solve for the position of
The headset now between the lighthouses for this
Quite something that we can use other poses for SE18
News on Jose
I Dave ortho
Anyway to do the same sort of thing
Refresh has a couple problems with it one is that does not do any Fusion
Clean the lighthouses so you can see that shows both lighthouses point of view
P&P and this application is actually much slower than
Much slower is much slower than I would like it's only getting 240hz
Where is something like dave author was getting absolutely absurd speed
But the Solutions that a morpho put out just as good as the EP and he song
So that means the least for the time being we are married to
What was the other one
We were married to keep class and Lockie
So there's that
Interesting things if you use the same holder to do both
So like really I'm gonna calibrate the system using the dbortho closer
Or not
Ok now to using the composer for Dior
On
And that
Ok sorry now this is using purely Dave ortho for calibration and for
Operation and you can see that it's not great
20 days work
So
If you only had someone that's all we really looking at
Then like you can see that I can point there I could actually point it at the
At the webcam
Guys
Set interesting the Den I guess I don't really have the webgl thing
Pointing out from the camera point of view but yeah so this is this is actually working and it's
Ridiculous
If you're going to get you something
What are you are the hero of the week between all these ridiculous tools that you've added
And this functionality
Arm
No yes
Do you want to make sure that this will work with the 30-day later
I think and the distance is what handles the light pulses
And Tamsin into meaning for angles to the rest of the system can operate
So I'm going to go
Hopefully this will still work with the curvy
Disambiguated
Hey I have no idea has been entirely too long since I've written
Justin Waite
Is ok so are you albinos French DJ David burger or Justin Berger and why David W
Stop listening Justin David burger
But yeah you were truly the hero of
For a while here
I can't seem to get terveys disambiguating Running With
Rang the situation
You're like a tribe I could just try use one lighthouse for right now
What's easier
Think you can calibrate using one
War movie does ignores me and operated with both
Settle
Will definitely have to get some work done to get the
Justin
Can I call you Justin what should I call you
Adam can you Benny for
Hozier
SDA and poser
Beta-2
That's right right
Justin pozary pm-te
ASDA
This should work out of Becky white houses
And we'll keep using turveys
Ok what's try using the child 1
Hey Justin I have never actually use your ASDA before
So is Anna messages I'm seeing hear about a canary Prada original reproject
Is that expected
What is that on expected
Oh my gosh it's a stable
Little Jackie
Little clarkie
What is working
It's actually working
ASDA Photo
Change that
The hottest girls
Checking on discord
Our yes that is one of the big things I really want to do I really want to be able to take
Sp32 strap a to a couple of the senses and making an add-on for your phone so you can look in
The three-dimensional world almost like an ar system
I don't really think it's an interesting this mean like replacing Google cardboard but I think this is
Really need it now what does the SBA say with this
Oh you gotta be kidding me
Oh guys look at this
That
This is incredible
So it's jaggedy and all that there's no imu sensor Fusion
What are so I guess we should probably get started for the day we spend about half an hour recapping everything
Going on
With with life survive and
Now what the goal is
So this
I am I hope you was watching
Q
Are you watching the
Ok
So I have right here a orange pi
Play wine listening is like Tiny actually I do have to add a heatsink to this
Get down to do that while working on it I'll be there this thing right here normally like
They have a duck like that enough to Alperton the vibe in the vibe on fortunately has
Very restrictive set of modes that it allowed to operate in so you
Operative ID at all if you can't drive a resolution that matches the
One the stupid 12 or 2160 by 1200 that requires which is
Would preclude operating on something with very limited hardware except
Orange Pi has a dark clock that can just eat by so it does mean
Turnpike an output to the 5th some problems in that there is no kernel there wasn't the current
Few days ago that would be able to actually run
No actually be able to run
The Mali drivers the video card drivers
B
Thankfully
I can't about this lifestream which was the best person ever been going to see this later but then was like
Play Somebody put a project on hiatus for a year
Need it went on hiatus but they came back in the finished and I had to make some Carol patches and I'm still trying to
Some things ran through the main line it's not going so hard they don't really like my recommendations and I spent hour
How to send an email so they all go through but
Regardless what I do have
I have this little guy right here and one thing I can run on it
What I'll do is I'll see you guys going to unplug
The arm
The projector output which is projecting over there she can't really see that you don't really
B2c environment to do is plug in the five
Sufficient I think needs to be rebooted even better just decide to reboot itself
What's
It's little dealio
I'm gonna go kill live survivor here
Close that window
Ok
Miss me
Play one thing we can do is cat daddy
Random into Dev fp0
Ok so if you look inside here
Get all jaggedy
How do I set that should be
Oh no I need to do that with
Cubic view
So now you can see that this is a large pie is actually are putting to the Vibe
Thought I had it working with the drivers but I guess not
Can't initialise by GL50
Sonic build RC
Ok I'm just try reinstalling device drivers
Is it
I haven't seen anyway in a while still working
I'm an idiot
I started somebody type something make sure that the
The child is working
Ok I actually ctrl-c did I don't know what I why did that by accident
Also increase game song
Anyway
IPhone
Try rebooting again
Silicone turning there was a DPF issue
No be crazy if this is a but for something I thought I had working
There is actually a bunch of stuff that
Ok
So you know what
What is a core dump
Inside the channel so it's power off and back on
The other interesting things the
Even the Bootloader knows how to help with the device which is just while
How to really see it in there
Going
Device
Working
Can you find the mode
Yeah probably take about 5
Play minutes but it's something we're going to have to do to get it working in sewing keep on moving
Where is that
No I don't want to delete emojis before breeding that's half the fun of watching you guys
Heating just stop
Off
Ok
Wow
Well Mark just deleted that one
Arch arm too
1direction
That's interesting
Sure that's copy tilde slash son
I'm so what I'm doing right now is doing these files the DTS files within
Ok you know what it's some point I'm going to just have to the band hymns
Somehow I don't even know
Is just going to keep making emails or is
Yeah the bridge light is on
Whatever
The description on bridge is get hard
Social media tools and in here it is
Tchat monitor Bridge discord and then the other one is
VR
Well live survive years get hard
Ok
Very go go go go go make a thing so I can get rid of specific
Play anybody doing
Anywhere
G-board
So I'm going to go copy it so anyway on the all-weather trip like the arm
Lyrics system-on-chip things what they're trying to do is there trying to unify the kobeissi they can use the same kernels
Different light configuration items so these DTS files describe a high level what the harbour loadout
Including like white part of memory things are found in that kind of stuff so you can have something it says like
I'm in orange Pi 1
Col go do your thing and it will automatically KNOWHOW all of that set up now I spent hours
Been through it trying to figure out how the world to use it works now I'm good
This is one of the files that I was trying to get them to patch this still haven't matched it on
I'm really bad at getting people upstream to do things
I just don't know how to make that happen
Anyway
I'm going to
What's make sure
What's copy Dad
I can say vtbd TDS install
Ok so
Now I know just go double-check lsfl till the / boots / my TV
Website BTB
Ok that's pointing to that folder there
/ ttd / 4.1 6.0 Dash
3 make sure that's the right time
March 21st 20 day did ok what's reboot
Panicked again
Send it
Colonel club panicking and doing more stuff
Detaching loop devices
Is actually from
Really lemon in there yeah inside the headset
Go actually read the the thing there
Yes Dan
Ok fingers crossed that we will actually get 3D this time
Don't know the I fell off
Can't have a headset without the eyes
On
Hey bingo ok so what I have here
Are you going to get to see all of those all things hair bows
All individual triangles now it's something weird that goes on a little bit further down but
Are the triangles are a lot of them and it's rendering this at 90 FPS
Little boys right here he is able to keep up
Delta overheating crash and die I'm going to kill it before that happens so we will have to
Play ar add something to a turkey kind of temperature ok
Which I just realised
I don't know
The Tread the thermal things to have thermal pads on sale
Let's see here what's going on ok so right now
Play show you guys is this or like Mali testing right here which is just
PGL Buddha but it's running at 2160 by 1200 Bandit showing 150 by
150 triangles 150 x 150
Is
What year is 22500 triangles are being rounded in the vibe from
A $19 computer so my goal is to in a couple weeks
Maybe have a something that you could actually play Like a video game that you can play in the vibe it's probably going by
Friend on
Just imagine also run cmatrix if you can display
You command in headset
I don't know what's ematrix is
Orange Pi Amazon this is an orange Pi 1 not in orange Pi PC
Have an orange Pi PC here I haven't actually looked it up yet but it should work with the five
While I think about it let me go fix the game
That looks better
Also 1960 11 to 52
I'm not also fixed the
Hello
I don't know these controls deal
I assure you it's very bright up there
I don't really know what the cameras doing
Ok
Artsy what are people saying in chat
You can read the catalogue from the Viber made me to the Carol
$90 Amazon
Art like this all the time
Yeah dude 6.8 asteroids that would be the way
I'm thinking the things going to have no time keeping up with on the 5 with wireframe
I don't think it's going to be able to draw very much because between clearing the screen and rendering
Triangles wants and then rendering like overlap for a factor of 2 it can't keep up and that
Are you the shader it is so minimal it is in Spain
This is the shader
Were used to doing like 100 operations in the shooter something it's kind of
Generally is minimal nowadays like
What is cmatrix I don't also I don't have
A keyboard up to it so I can't really type things into it on
Anyway this GPU is literally that the fragment shader
Is literally the pixel into the buffer Indian like ok it's Toronto
Stop this all of this this all brings us to what we're actually doing today
The Matrix in my mind
Vibe headset that's strange
Sometime but not right now for this part
We're going to change the chat window because we have now done
Last 2-weeks and now are going to be putting rod raw on
Ok also that way so there we go
R2c
Oh come on I trying to actually spend almost the entire time actually recapping stuff and I would imagine this
The interesting for you are I would hope it's been pretty interesting to you all see if the viewer count to 100
So yeah I'm going to go with this was a pretty good livestream so far what we're going to do though
Is so smooth you guys might be aware of Rodger it's how we are we operate a number of things like a
Can you tell us 4 cm pick so if I say see anything google.com
Right here is strong or FIFA
RC I can type without
Placing my fingers ok
Check
You can help in web addresses this is actually pinging http
Call back home within HTTP thing
But I think this is just to burst swanky because like it's actually require
I'm from Google by K can I get that webpage in your actually paying it and you can do this
So somebody wanted deportes en paying over the Android like you actually could now
If anybody does want to port City anything over to Google please do so
See hear
My friend just texted me she was administered she says if I won't lie
Everytime it snowed I'd never get off my phone
Actually no day anyway
You being close all that over trying to do right now is trying to make a on
Etl driver for Rod rod and what is going to do is going to give us a common platform to be able to
Draw things inside the bike headset on this is gonna be really valuable because rod rod something that we
Unlike use and test in other environments as well so we're not limited in so far as the
Development in developing and developed in really specific things
What are you annoying thing as egl completely removes immediate mode so you have to claim a fake It Yourself
Which is a little bit awkward
Can you just do it anyway so
Alright now as you guys can see is supporting rudra and that would be important to the headset
Understand the end goal for today is to be able to see an object in 3D space
Please may I be able to move the headset and heavy object kind of see
Still a little bit during that so yeah
Gomovies
Ok so what I have in St cyr
Raja cmfg you can do things like a pixel which would go out put one more
Pixel to the screen on a specific location or tax segment which would take a segment cheapest
Line segment to the screen at the specific location so these are all really basic
We have to in order to work with egl we're gonna have to put them into offers
Turn my problem we go setup
Excuse me setup a buffer and alcoholic
Alarm in specific to Marty
I was same a maltese whatever same thing because it's really fast
It doesn't have any of the composites of slow down it's it's just
It's super duper fast so you can even use it in the arms and it feels real time
Anyway so I was actually working on tax segment on before I started on
We're going to go now so what you can do there
Briefings X1 y1 X2 Y2 and
Colour butter
We want to make that x
Because we have a line a colour for this segment and a colour for the end
Text we have a colour basically
X 2 she know how the lines worth with Tom
With with a g l e s wear with dark PGL so we'll see
Alarms
See how that goes so next is
Vgl
Acquired
Sergio quads
What is that
Airlines tier points and what are they
We have
TCL lines GL triangles to quads
I'll put quads
Accounting for rectangles of that uses the background colour of the foreground colour
So inside here
Tack rectangle that doesn't really tell me much
Brush based off of last
Yes so uses the EGR currentcolor
Ok cos there's four points
We'll see if I can keep ringing back Morar YouTube I chat stuff I'm glad for this one I was able to get the
Thing up and running
I'm really happy with that what is your question with GLS less than 2
I don't know what you're on
You got you do are you serious read
What is this the
Oh my gosh you guys but so depressing
Why would the
Why do people get rid of things that are so good
So wait so it'll be
I guess I really only had two triangles then right there's no
Heart
Whatever
W = 2 triangles how does that work
What school look at the example code
Conveniently we have the
Basically basing this author Melita because I do know that this application works so I can
One of the things I am looking sorry about this to get sizes that means there is no z-buffer with the cast
Will worry about that later
Ok Josh if I wanted to spew some lines of the screen
I don't understand why shouldn't be allowed to spew some lines on the screen
Like I get that it's slow as molasses as it should be
Outline the got to go somewhere
I'm not having a buffer object
I guess you'll triangles tries count x 3
What's the number of vertices that sell pudding
So really
If I was going to do this it would be
But but
Are my friend just texted me asking me what I'm doing
Right now I'm trying to get this orange Pi the small $19 computer and a man
Try to get this thing to output video to the HTC vive
Possible theoretically
To have VR entirely in the headset so I won't have to have a long cable
Going all the way back to the wall and to the computer
I just did that thing
Saudi X1 so making the quad and so that's going to be
So that's going to be X1 y1
Over 2
X2 y1
And we got to be clockwise when arranging things
Don't forget to go clockwise
Tell me read your guide stuff you've been saying a lot of stuff
Yeah it's really depressing
Yeah it's fine I'm just looking at the amount of bits you have to give to the the headset and it's just
It's just completely depressing so the next so 1234
So the next to sea would be x 1 y 2 which is that
And then the next ones we would do is X1 Y2 than x 2
Y1 and then x
2 y 20 123456789 10
Navan for the 12th and then for the colours we feel it in 12
34 123 45 x 6
Ok on wish that you had it had
The thing where you could
Vertically anyway
Neon pi is is OpenGL ES
Clicking like music on nobody's referring to
Are
The bandwidth is hard anyway so
The rectangle in X1 is transmitting polygons
Arbitrary polygons
Now drivers not intended for normal operation it is just intended for
Bike
Right output but you can abuse rod ra2 output to open up a screen
To have the underline OpenGL OpenGL ES available to you so that way if you want to have it open to your window
Don't want to include or do all the window open yourself you can just use rather on
Just throwing it out there if you guys want to have some fun with it
Yes ggl size
Overflowed
The buffer
And I do have to subscribe to
Describe fewer is 2
The stride means the number of components per day died in Sofia right now just X and Y
So I'm selling it to till
Krd point
What is an early point I don't remember
So where is the thing for
Keep using shorts
Turn the frame didn't go copy and paste that from over here
Add
How do I should figure out a clear with back cover
To do that
I lost my preview
At that right
Ice pack
I lost the the YouTube preview for heart secondary
Anyway so we're going to take polygons for going to clear frames in order to clear the frame programmed to be cleared
Where and declare possible clear colour
What's the hell VX driver does it
Clear frame
Foreground
We will use that too I guess
And sobr which is That Ends Well
X
That number
Turn down
55 times
Set a timer 65 that number
It's kind of wacky then for the next one cause you can't multiply that out because you'd lose bits of precision
Turn it down
24-bit down and then we can do 255 again
That should clear the frames now swapping bottles that should be fairly easy to
Offers
Ytl swap office what is a function for it
That's a good point Morpheus even the stupidest of compilers will do that
I don't know it's just force of habit I guess
Probably better I probably should have written it the other way
Anyway get dimensions
Do we already have screen with the height stored anywhere
Need a window handles that
Is an actual fine
Turn the light off
Ok
You had better already be in full screen mode
Candle import we don't have any input on the system so
Don't know what to do there so next thing we have to do that is set up the screen
How do we do that let's go over here unlock
Copy and paste this code
Xopendisplay Noel the Wi-Fi using X11 which were not be
I have still not been able to get the thing to start up an X11 window with video acceleration
Forget it
Tea here so next thing to display which should
Work
Theoretically
Probably want to do that
What's to all this stuff this looks good I like all the stuff
Looks like a really good stuff
Stop stop stop
Let's go copy on this wholesale
I am really starting to hope that
This is
Under a licence I'm allowed to use
Don't need to do anything else
Probably make sure I can actually with this code
Yes I can't live this code thank you Mr whoever you are
Ok so
That copied
Still want to
You still working on to do now is we're going to want to take
The the end here there is a thing worse x 11 for getting a fan switch
If we someday have X11 available to us which we got today
Whatever
Ok
I'm going to do now TV Jet2
It's my mum
Hey man I'm actually likes doing right now
I need you later tonight
Hello ok I will definitely done before midnight
Rhodri
Oh you know what
I'm gonna make a staying in regatta call Roger
Orange egl
Do not want to use rasterizer think that might actually do me
Ok
Off
Start digging through
Courier
With undeclared here
That would be fair because we don't yet know
How big this is going to be
What we do when we set up the screen or at least we know how big the user thinks it should be when we set up the screen
The next couple of Christmas
And what's going on here
Should be should be
No
What to do in wrong
Does anybody online see what's wrong here cos I'm not really sure what I'm doing wrong
I think I can use GLS your
Wz grg
Says unexpected error expected identifier
Open France use before numeric constant
Service needs to be a un 16th
Thank you
You just took the problem
Next
Now there is one annoying thing about when your operating on an SD card is sometimes your data just disappears so I'm
You pushing a fair bit
Saving files as nothing when the the bringer of death comes
So24
Window
That's doing there
Next one is go shot
T0shirt
What time is ardee point I'm known
Have not done in food
Chat typecast
Harley Quinn
What type of fat is that in C
So that song
Yep just Corbridge is definitely working
And if you go over life survive
You can totally see
YouTube live chat
Can you can go read through it I did disable
Editing the things so so
If you really wanted to search it or go back through the chat history of any of the live streams you totally can now
Off
You didn't hear me I f*** you
It is not two-way
I did not want to patch it back to YouTube says YouTube is temporary
And discord is permanent if you want to chat just chat or not telling you to so next one
Repoint why is Ali point
Ok silver here
See what line was there I was on 227 and it says
And not why
Finisterre
Not have any good way of returning out of that land on it
It has a problem
I just crashed ok that's great
There is no way to fail
I don't like that
I'm going to make it so that CFG setup in fail
For all of seeing actually
Hi corn dog
Actually is anybody tried checking to make sure that they can't write in the discord chat Ark
Arm that seems like a thing that should have been tested that I never tested
Probably open the rest of drivers to make sure on break something
Who had all this jumper I have no idea how to return things in
Does anybody in there know
Objective-C
I have no idea how to
2R
Return a value
You can write into a live chat
So you can wait until I said that's right
How
Can you just return
Is anybody know live chat
Does anybody know Jack Dempsey
Return integer objective
No I want to return integer from a function
They have this function here which I guess it's a functional real wacky to me
Arm
How to return a value from it
No return
Yeah nice try you can
I'd like to see you try to make an apple desktop app in see a lot of people have tried
Succeeded
So the reason why Roswell was ported to Apple was because
Specifically I'm already in that file was specifically
4recent so that people could run see anything on a Mac
Isn't a language much like Python it's just a cold
Ok
Play Netflix with a lot of noses
293 g size
Ok where is EGR major come from
Undeclared income
So very strange year
So first
Reporting this text Michael clearport Roger to the Orange pi
Killer portlight survived and then form
Yes actually I don't have any way of flashing it near all in
Unless you can send me a link with like an actual guide is how they do it which would be kinda fun to do a live on air
So we could try it it's going to be at least two more times before two more livestreams before I
Get Ty going back to getting a whole bunch of my custom FDM tags
Ok so let's look try try try
I get my drawer
Include user include
EGR EGR the HR
Dpy config native window type
What is that
Avoid star
Punks
That's not right
Unix isn't only X11
Ignore it for right now
Whatever happened in North right now
Ugly
We can do we can forcibly
TV
Hello weird
Sure let's just used Dad
Vertex shader source not found
Default
Things same things probably happened for pregnant
Thesaurus
Rat
That's an easy fix
Capital Mali
Yes that's all secret
Snakes reproduce the fire
39 KB
Made a file
Yes we're on it
Everybody's waiting for me to run in Marseille
Yeah I couldn't get the GPU working with sorry services who wants me to run
Where is ITV guys hanging
Who sings is going to crash
We are either going to crash before does anything
Cos like it won't link Wray it's going to crash want to talk to making calls to OpenGL
Or it's going to start crashing as soon as he tries to understand the screen is not going to crash but nothing's going to come out of the van
What are you guys thinking
Using a crash were you guys thinking of crash
Before does anything
Ok I think that's a reasonable thing so it's probably going to crash when it starts the Open
As driver
And honestly I haven't tried running the ogs toughest boot
I'm order crash up that's a good point if it crashes the colonel that's going to be hilarious
Ok
Ready like my heart actually kind of breathing fast right now
Adam gave me the fire extinguisher could you go
Heatsinks under stairs and apply 12V on pi
Yeah you're right here
Have I ever radio purchased
Looks like maybe the problem is
Well
Where is there's no gdst
Cancel
Pulling out all the time
Yeah
Adam is now applying Keepsafe to the
I don't think so I don't think that was the one that got hot
Imagine that only if someone is the main one is for the GP will tell so
Memory warm but not hot
That supposed to be heating
Play Holdem
Do you wanna show the camera
Nice things about the surface area and then there's just a flat thing which
Seems like it would do virtually nothing
Most heatsinks always worry me
Yeah they do seem dubious xochi pensions
Which is way for that I would have expected you to garden
What's this for
Will the shops
Yeah we put this on Mia
Anyway
Ok this code got wait for another night
Piece of sorry only this half of the cameras visible this is an orange Pi PC
As opposed to this one which is an arm for orange Pi one
Find ktc Hazel
For something else is used for
Yeah that's fine pipeeasy is identical to the Raspberry Pi
It is not identical but has completely different
Physical
I appreciate that actually instead of a stupid micro USB
Actually you know what they're all now this is the wrong one somewhere I have a girl
Play so it's actually getting all the way through set up in scratch and some
Pause
Tvd guys
No orange Pi uses of very different shape
If you use the same ship we wouldn't be able to use it for this
Pixel
Oh hey look at that
Set off
Yeah I know it's not the right resolution by default so
It is utterly broken
It is
Completely
Broken
That is not even remotely right
Ok
Time for us to start the debugging
Ok hello
Is the first part we have to do
Change one thing deep within our
10-ft function stop
Somewhere run
Yeah it's pretty bad right now got to figure out what's actually going on
Is 27 frames per second of nothingness so
Cancel audio is just to their
Trying to get something working
1000 1000
To see what happens
Well it's
Big blue screen
Solis clear colours working
Check to see what
How are you know what
About one's numbers that are much smaller
Seymours play this 5.0 wine
See what happens
Turn it around some like shapes
If there's something I need to see and chat let me know it cos right now I don't
Don't intend to follow you guys for the next couple of minutes
Girls into the strange world
Nothing nothing at all
What's going on here
Cell
Going to have to get this going
OK Google what what's right now for children clothes
Floats down
I think
Come on
Smart working
Ok
Let's just prior rendering a triangle with the Melly test
Also I just realized I'm an idiot
Hitman display so you can go outside without the optics
You can I believe remove those lenses but you also have those prototype head not displays that
If you want to go check that would be super awesome
Downstairs under the next song
Blue screen
Listen
How does that not work
No it's just that it's just wonderful just just
Getting cold
Ok thank you
Are you serious
You can probably pull the active site of that one just as easily I would much rather not not after seeing this
Here's one that doesn't have the whole thing
Can you get another
No I don't but I would need somewhere powering it
Valve send me prototype head units so this is one of the perfect iPad units that will be
Will a call to have set up
Yes that's a really good idea atom
That song gets tied to you guys
Ok so right now I'm able to actually get something on the screen
What's called back to what we had before
Private and see what happens
There is nothing
Nothing
Who's the powered by
Small barrel connector
Actually that's used
Do you want to pull that out of there yeah we can do that
Cos you're wanting you didn't seem to give us it all that without feeling like an unexploded it
That's why it's not rendering that's a degenerate triangle how did it get to
Triangle triangle
Is Mr Strong
Do you want to keep it so that we can plug into this fairly easily
In case the damn thing doesn't work at all
Stop
Hey ok maybe it's about putting something right now
Power down
I see light there's something in the corner to see if you have it
Message
Are you random into Dad apdl
Hey
That's really Jackie though the camera so yeah it's
Hard to see but it's like a bunch of noise
Ok so we got to figure out this year I will try to figure out
Why this is not working it just black now
Anything right now
I'm actually probably going to go to slightly different Direction with the next thing with Steam
Then I think that they are going to go
What's good to me what's wrong with it artificial
Where is Genki
Give Adam a moment to see
Fixes doing anything
Dad but yeah yeah blue
Ok because I had no idea I thought that was
Not a screen I had no idea
Turn down funny screen texture
Yeah it was like Grey black
Really pretty though anyway
Displaying anything
I'm not having the party
Black totally black
Not right now thank you
Ok check that out
There is a triangle inside the five for making progress here
Adam heating somebody to hold this up here while
Tending to be ok
Let's go to stack of chairs
We do have the chair stack
If you want to build something ridiculous right near me
Freeze dried soup
No it was Nicky smell it was 25fps when it's doing the default test which is
Intensive of things better didn't Crumlin
I I will do that but not right now I want to get our kind of working first
Looks like to see
Why would a
What's what's take A Peek inside of the Colour buffer
Unsigned by for stride
No you have it can you be looking
The background on the matter what it's broken right now definitely wrong
Skyline
Stop cast
Turn off the lights
Horrifying
Crashing ok sorry about that
Oh that's not a bad idea
Difficulty
Meant to be clearly visible
Very dark compared to the outside
Is the display 0 years by it but it's all
Doing the stripy thing the rolling shutter
Song because I can manually can control the exposure Times online
I might w Jack so on the IP camera
Media image
No no
Set timer
I don't see it
It looks janky
30/60 it's still look pretty rough
Because it's only open for a very short period of time
Ok so this is clearly wrong it's passing FF 00000000
Cheers just playing Black why is it passing black
Webcam cannot do it you have to go
Before you can do that and I don't want to be a serious because there is enough x
White bits white you have a triangle look at that guys
Ok
How is going ok where are or are making inroads here
Hair erase
More useful Charles
Is there anyway good too
Now that's probably fine
Video message please
I can maybe we can see is there anything going on the centre
No nothing is going on the centre
Actually let's take a peek back individual buffer
Is there anything visible on the centre on
Look like now
I don't actually know it OpenGL does with
That's the wrong thing I bet you people were
Writing in chat
Turn the heater inside the shader
Hey ok we have a triangle again
Is it worth doing janky stuff to make that work
Security a good way of getting quite
If you really need to see I'm done
No more need to until 2 minutes from now
Sideways
Something
Saying thanks bye
Put your screen is cut off
KFC off the right side
I like somebody wanted to know what was going on like going line
Anyway
Tell anybody else to have a use uniforms Josh if you're still watching you probably know better than ideal
Did something go wrong with the
Oh no
Are you looks like a prototype is to display panels Adam did you happen to notice of the display
The prototype was to display kennels
He says it's just one piano
Ok so
Yeah I know I understand what uniforms are I just don't have it use them on
On this platform
Let's see this person is done it how you look go uniform it's a thing
After the program links you would call
Security uniform shader program
Recalling the
Screen scale
What's 4 in here we kinda now
I'm so going to try to do is try to scale the object by x&y appropriately
And I'll show the FPS in a minute imagine that the FPS 90 FPS
Only driving a single triangle
See hear
Play so will I by width and height
Ok
And would actually be saying /
So we have like 500
Will want to say for 0.0 is your point
Position a
X
Scale
Let's be
Chill
Electronic if you want to do that I have a source code for Rod supports esp32 another
The things so it does let you do matrices on Mike really lame hardware and princess on the
8266 works there is no floating point so it's all using like
Movie Lee basic operations if you want to see how I do it then there was the wireframe example with
Ok
Maybe the sort now
Nothing there is a reason why that could be
One of those reasons will be there
What's try rendering really dig
50/50 and over and
So you need shaders because you aren't allowed there's no fix functionality pipeline in in
Move down there like yeah we're just going to rehearse Elves and triangles without tutors
Flippantly but I guess it was nice because now all hard work has to support shooters
If you want to be OpenGL yes but I don't know
Hey there is a little
You guys can see that in the upper corner
Tiny little
Do Dad
So let's try blowing up song 500/500
See that looks like the top corner of a triangle
That looks super wrong
Really wrong
That means there year
Turn on
I guess we just shouldn't be having things at the screen edges
And the other thing is going on here is the way that works is 00 is at the bar
Turn on bottom corner right here and that's not where it is
Anything like graphics we're on graphics it goes way up at the top that would be easier as your own so I guess
Adjusted so that
I can handle all that in this year
Pudsey here I'm going to have my tutor and then you
Lip
I think it is
3 - 2 and then that would be plus 1
I think that's gonna look at around so that the triangle show up in the top corner perfect it did
That's good insane now
Something else now
What's 2160 / 2 as 1080
1205 8 to the 600
That looks like I should be in the middle
It is yeah we have a triangle
Ok
What's the term in framerate
9.5 FPS which is exactly what it should be so we are getting
90fps out of the system right now that's perfect
Ok next one let's try drawing some wines
Gorgeous
Excellent that is the way I want to see things working
Ok so what that means is now we have a odgl driver
4 Raja which is one of the big things we wanted to college today so I'd say where
Cruising along pretty good just double-check some things like one thing
New right now is re-enable this junk and see what happens
On the other thing I want to do is get rid of
It's not quite right
Actually painfully slow but I can't see in FPS
Turn the lights as well
I'm going to have to go over there and take a look and tea
Something's definitely
I don't really know what's going on I could be like a CPU I don't want to
It could be something like maybe I'm switching dramos really quickly
So all I can do is every single frame I can print
And then what I can do is inside of the
Here every single time I would draw a new settee geometry I can
Like the lights nation point and I can know how many different types of
Oh my
Oh my god that is a lot of draw calls
That's concerning the bigger they I wonder
Hello there tiny why are there all these tiny rock holes
Also Sue
Busted
Why would we not getting 90 FPS
Yeah so you just can't intermix segments and pixels in the same thing
But I don't understand is so I guess what you guys can't see
There's almost nothing you
Can you do some get a glimpse of the the little piece of geometry but it's almost never there so
Not really sure what's going on
Turn black back on a blue background see you never going to see it
Make the background much darker
I forgotten how to make a background darker
Where is the
This
So now I'm here
See like a little bit of red just Barrett
Invisible so it's like it's only the very first and very last bit of the geometry
Play bits of the geometry they're actually being rendered
Natural why that is we should totally figure that out
So
Clothes
I was only drawing one thing that's why
Completely plastered
118 APS
Samsung trolley broke
What about day
What's
5 x 3
Nothing
Vertex attrib pointer how's this thing used
Potassium 3
Alice the number of vertices
Number of colors
No it's the stride it's only the stride rate
So maybe that
I'm getting the same basic stuff again
Could be doing something wrong here
Make sure not clearing through multiple times
Oh you know what quarries
Calories has that function used
Set an alarm tonight probably why should be doing
Not home stride
What's NI
Buy there is definitely a problem something with the speed of this is really slow
Can't imagine printer office what's slowing it down
Alaska I will stop printing and see how that does
We want to also cancel the
I'm swapping buffers twice
That would do it
Oh hey it's gorgeous now
Oh yeah
Decorate a hole in it for some reason not sure if that's about but
Yeah
I was swapping offers twice in the the same like swapping in swipe
Stopping at back which is just a recipe for all sorts of failure
Cecil that's those
Should we all see the texts that should be being wrong
I'm gonna come out and see what happens with changes
See any text anywhere on screen that should appear there
Oh meat
All you guys
Let me go
Online 111
Why is that
My colour
You know why
Life doesn't do that I think it does
The dialogue colour whatever
Yes the spies rendering this
Rip headphone users
I'm sorry I have no idea
This rate you guys can see what's going on connected to the Orange pi
Right there through the HDMI plug
What do you mean like taking it out of the house
That's silly Adam
That's just silly
I guess I could put it back there I couldn't see the things on the
Before but I can't now so
I hope that's ok I just have a huge
Hi Amazon
Work so hard
Play displaying keep broad right as it is it's because there is no available with video acceleration
I want to be able to have a very xvideo accelerated output
Ok that's so much better
That pretty good
Surrey now that little area in the top corner should turn greyish
Richard end
Just to spite me
Nope still in Accra
I think would be very cool somebody reported virtual boy over to this
Maybe it's actually just that dark
I just can't see it
Yeah that's what's going on
Blue going on
What does refrain do that could be breaking it rain
Just comment out of bath
Graphics programming can sometimes Go
Ok why is this not behaving the way over expected to then
How is Rob Oxo
How are called does play into it
Why would the colours be boosted so heavily
And last
You know why it could be little endian
Began dry Indian
Most significant bye
No that's not the case but
There is a function somewhere here is
Set the colour of pasta
Crgv up
I'm just walking around
No that was my great ok let's try fix guys
So you know why
There's a thing you can do and it's
OpenGL I think it's with this
It's
Sing about this knows that the new viapro the old one first
Normal eyes
What's right setting like to true
So right now I'm sitting red to be 1 out of 255
So should be nowhere near as Bray
Perfect ha
Ok so now
Undo everything here here
Set the back to GL horse
I lost my video stream
Ok I show you there's something on the display we just have to figure out why the
Radio 1
Hey there we go
What's even weirder what's going on it's like
Call Jackie
I would not be amazed if they hacked it
Wow what's going on I can see here
Volume again I guess I have to
Well
No it's still host it's just lost the ability to sell
Rtsp streams
Very strange
How I guess we could just watch it in a stone
Or something
No it's a wired camera
Re9 viewing in the web browser so to using an mjpeg stream
Whoops
The full width
It's working now so I have a functional
OMD the red area actually has texted you to it ok
What song what do a wee bit of a stress test
Without doing any kind of clever optimizations let's see what happens if we try to render a
One More Line s
Still able to keep up
Critters in the background there
Turn up to over 10000
That it's not able to do
Yes I did unfortunately it's going to be a pain getting that all the upstream stuff
Because they don't seem to be taking very
Play to me and I don't really understand how to get Lanark to club patches for me so
Yeah
Looks like actually 9000 is probably about the most but I'm gonna bump back down to eat right now concepts
Plenty enough for the kind of things I Wanna Do
Ok now what I want to do is I want to see if I
Turn the change the line width but see how you do that
Vs change line width
OpenGL ES is that like actually offend
Aldi Darwen
I'm emailing to make sure that's actually
I can't really tell
Try not see what happens
I still am I going dumb
Really tell
Oh yeah it's definitely they're all look at those wide Lines
Look at that
Oh my gosh survival keeping up to
That's great
Let's see what happens if we are
Things I can try to do the tweak the output see if those speed it up and all
No there is just an upper limit on how many lines the
You can draw looks like
Answer right now or somewhere between about 70 and 85 FPS so what I can do as I can try
Turning on deaf testing and we'll see if that helps
2416 is all we really need
Pressing suit about the same speed even with z-depth stuff
OGL enable
Neighbours cast
Right
An example Example
Is fine example I want to copy and paste something I don't have to think
Does anybody have any really quick OpenGL code for Harding like quickly do dips stuff
Why did I click on a direct3d 9 link
I just realised this isn't going to be able to be testable with Rod rockers rod rod doesn't had a deal with z
So it's pointless
I guess I just wanted to see but
Please don't slow down please don't slow down please don't slow down please don't say oh my gosh
Wait a minute it's not slowing down and it's clearly working
Testing completely broken but
That's a really good sign that means we can use death testing if you're really
Ok I think 4 time for do for a break
Back at 7
P.m. to do is commit stuff
I'm going to go back abroad
Make sure it doesn't explode
Goodnight ok
Is working just fine up there and everything's fine I guess I should not
Do you dab
It's really cool that you can have
I didn't know you could set up screens in the castle that were not full screen
Yeah we need to fix that
It's killing the framerate because it's switching between arm
Pixels and segments so dramatically
Brendan
Mirrors at mine
Play I in Chard
Can somebody in Shotton work the time of the
Like when everything came together so I can use it for a coming together or something else
Something's wrong with this not running it
Speed
What is this thing doing
Confront the powers of quietly practically
Did you want to make something for dinner
Ok
You know what movie I want
I know it's only 2
GPU or PC PSU it's this thing right here which is really
Smart grinder litepower right now
Do you know why it's only drawing like a couple milli
Hideous waiting
What happens if you let it go as fast as I can
Marius just fine
Thank you Jamie
How am I going to get my credentials without
You guys seeing it
OK actually I should do
To worry about that again
49 no
Cheese gluten free
Alternative combined the white shells and cheddar
No that's even worse
Make just one
Ok
Oh so there is
Turn off the fan in the video the video is behind the sound for the fan
So you probably would hear our him Mark my order fast food to our house
Do we do we want him to do that
Ok Haymarket London
Lighting are you seeing that we the orange pi is actually working with the van everything
Actually not we can do
Diamond port life survive there is
Number to anymore stop
Another box of Ono I don't want the gluten-free I was just curious
Like I bought two boxes I only everyone also Dylan ever comes over I'll do it for him
Get it
Did taste pretty rough
I feel very sad for Dylan
Ok
I think you're good
Mayo for the second part of this which is the
Bury park to me right now
You guys wanna Morgan chat
So here's the second part the second part is
Lights to 52 the orange Pi the original plan was for white survive to only
Require a minimal set of libraries that's making a very easy to Port to anything unfortunately
Justin Berger thank you very much for all of the work you've done you have made this love
So we'll see if it's harder or if it's really not that hard I have my opinions
What's find out
I forgot I also have to remove the extra copy of linux
Selma install the extra packages that are needed to make the Sling run
That's not that bad
76 MB isn't that bad
I was preparing for that number to be with bigger
Esp32
Probably fine
There anyway
Can you help me Adam
Got myself in a pickle
Get a real stand for desk
Hey Mark and Dylan if you guys want you could actually attach the live chat back up
Your help and then we can be controlling things by live chat at your house and I could stream or webcam
Your house to here
So I'm right now going to try this on the experiment
Actually I should do we have the experimental vibe has
Again
So
Live survive what's the running and see what happens
Wow no it is not going
Turn off the old developmental for hardware
No no
Log into my computer I'm trying to run on my computer
I don't know no
No it doesn't work
Volume to my desktop and I don't know which of these USB ports to use
Check
No it's definitely had it in the right one
Brown sugar
New Viber is working just fine with the video output from the orange pi
Hey also one more thing if you guys are up for it if you go into discord
And if you like you guys to do if you're if you're up for it would be going to
Off-topic
And tell me what things about the stream you like in what things you didn't like or things that I can improve
Would like to try to up my YouTube streaming game in the future
Also really pretty good
What would happen the people hate it so much ok
So actually I just didn't should I pull on my
Last I don't even care about my desktop I'm going to go plug in the arm pie
Unplug the vibe
Stop the White House
So now
How to get a copy of web socket be on here as well
Websocket
Cardiff city website
Oh no they're trying to download go
4 X86 64
R32
That's not gonna work
Stolen websocket Dion arm
Ok I guess we'll just do this that look scary and
I really don't know how I feel about just running a
Binary from someone
Hey
This game
What nakai
I really don't want to
Hey Justin
Wait where is the arm binary is in the fish alarm binary
It is there is in a pickle or binary
Do you need to get my hands I'm live USD
I can just copy the line
I don't need actually much that stuff
I don't need light x 11
There's no way this is gonna link
There is no way
Not linked
Wow
0 lines of code needed to be changed
Well we'll see that right about that
Actually one thing I should do is I should do why forwarding
That way I can run things like eggs
Through the thing back to me
Like this extern window is actually running on the Orange pi
Lights off I've
Calibrate
You've gotta be kidding me
Our can keep up though
What's right starting with Dave ortho cos that's gonna be the easiest one the wrong
Are jelly that's a really good point exporting might be slowing it down
So we can run as you can do that black Adidas sockets webrecorder magic socket
Name
And I will
Stop
How do you tell it
You can change the HTML page
Where how
Window that location I can't override that
Friday's here
Now it's not keeping up
Website could be sucking down ok
J David Berger I think I know what I'm going to do this week
I'm going to rewrite websocket D&C I can have all the features
By the way I journal I would have said goes just fine until that a minute ago in which case now and like
Because
There is no way
In esp8266 can do website as this world why why is
Websocket d not able to keep up
Ok
M&S
That's a good idea
I was so there is this other problem that happens with this sort of stuff where
Where
No you're right it could also just be using the poses that could be causing it
But it shouldn't be using 47%
Have you disable so there's this bug in people's brains for they think that
That's not SSL should be killed in there just there just wrong
And I don't see any way to do this without
It is website secure it isn't secured it's still not working
No ok my opinion is the website needs to go get
Yeah this is really lame but you're right I'm going to go to change it to use the
Sores / survive
Are processed us from one survived data
See in try using the trolls 2 simulator
Now ok fine we'll try moving it
I'm pretty sure it just doesn't have to go
I'm not using keyboard notes
Turn on smart keeping up
So what's happening is the second number is coming up and resetting because it missed a a packet
It doesn't need overclocking
So there is another thing that we're going to have to eventually get around to doing and that's going to be
2 on
That's going to be to dislike decouple the incoming data from
The system probably and I've been trying to like push that off but
Yeah
Oh no it's only using 14% CPU
Compilot I didn't recompile like good call
Quick guys throw some more things in chat that I would jump to conclusions quickly for
Time to turn off the infrared part of the camera
Can you not
Discrete
I got distracted
Yeah it's working
It was able to get past
That's good
That's really good
We'll have to go Duty more tweaks but right now
What's wrong mate I make sure that all the data coming in as expected
Ok so this is spectacular
Json
And hmd I think is what we want
Please Ryan please run please run please run please run
Ok
Next week Friday run with the e p n t
And because we're going to views
What's the name of the thing something shotgun
Euripides shotgun method of debugging where can I change two things
Stephanie John
Can I change two things at the same time
Go back over here
Can come on please work
Good good
Good
Golden
Oh yes
We are running live survive ok and so
I know you're going to tell me the news
RSPCA
Does not seem to want a girl
I know the tractor visuals are not running on there
This is running on my computer
Hey Justin burger if you can look at the screen now or tell me what
I think I could do to find out why
This isn't working that would be awesome
I don't see The Catcher in the white House's
Maybe
It's fine let's try moving around
I'm thinking this is working
But
It's doing something
Ok
Yeah looks like a never 0tx
Can I see any otx here
Never ATX
Don't know why
Figure out the configuration AdultWork so
Maybe if we can fit pose based off
Read a minute
Hey
II
Swap TNT TNT for default poser
Do I really want to do that that would be the us all I want to do isn't it
What does see what happens
Baby God knows he acts
We got another 0tx
Oh and by the way see you no like some of the people have done
The past like Josh Allen XL pressure in the chat he was the one that wrote the 0tx decoder
Candy configuration system ok
Do I know 1PS pie from my default that I would
Are you tried turning off the infrared lights I couldn't figure out how
Do you like you do is just stop looking outside
Think it's going to work
Haha
So we have that they're gonna go back here pick up around
Looks like I'm looking at the right things
Really jittery Rough by
Night workout
So guys we are still on schedule
We are going to try to talk to you guys directly
We're still on schedule
Codeword for talking in chat about something like
Go to this point for a highlight reel
We're still on track it is
8 p.m. local time I intend to spend about another
Hour and a half to two hours tonight
The goal
Is to hook up light survive to what we just did with Raja
To see if we can see
An object
In 3D space through the 5 running divide off of in
Hi
I think we can do it
I I think
I think it's going to happen
Ok guys I mean
I can't wait
I need a new version of Raja
We can pull in
Call me on
YouTube Peppa
Show them how much you driving down the flu
That's annoying
It looks like
Take me to back horse and fixes first
Let's do that right now
Ring driver
Which one of these was more up today
Cancel button
Which one
Chloe
The song
Thank you out for dinner
So question right here is
NFC image driver
Where is the deaf
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
The problem was that this is like been strewn from all over so
Hi Mum I'm gonna assume that the other one is newer so I'll just do that
I don't know how they got changed in last Dave Chapman had his own version
Looks good
Are there is one but I need to add
Good
Heard
Might need to get tweaked
OK Google ok
Change without to me we have to use the trolls poster on the system instead of the derby poser
Download should make batter
Difference ok so let's go back into this year
Now we're going to have to
Make a new tool
Live survive
Make
Orange high test
Ok
You're right
Thank you Google
Sertraline
Survive
Read pie I see you're coming up with the new name for it
Once you guys in chat Settle on a name
We can rename it
Redist online 5
Thanks
Someone need retest include
Live survive
2160 by 1200
Lights to revive online 6
You are
I think I need to take a little bit aspirin give me just a second
Ok
What's just copy and paste example from
From Rod right in the here
Why not look at a weird grid thing
Raja
Going to go for dinner time
Not really need to do any other stuff
Weather stuff
Or the stuff I don't know what that stuff is even
Why do you need to do this stuff
And I don't need to wait
Set the goal right now is just to get back to where we wore
With the yarn
Bacteria with destroying stuff in the
Survive
What I do wrong
Nothing
Ok
So we need to get
Sinach
3D
Why is that night
Put away
Lionel living character for
Oh my gosh yes I was definitely I think I might be getting a migraine or something I started
Lapack
What is it called
Sea glass
Candyland
Ok C-Class apaki
Actually that's even wrong wow I am just losing my mind right now
See what's going on
I do see a full screen
Video of the things so
Actually do the pair
Sunglasses but I think it's a little bit ridiculous to coding these cos they are Led sunglasses which are
Very dark though I can still see everything with him so sure
Who do this
It hurt my eyes to maybe sunglasses
Stop alarm
I want to run with the same scene twice from two different points of View
I looked over the 5-in look up and it's just the sunglasses are so dark and I
Can't actually read text with sunglasses on or welding glasses
Where are there
It's too bright are that's an interesting point I should probably switch at 2 a.m.
Come on
Under the sea
Spice from two different points of View so I think I want to do is
Respective m here set up the
Newport
So
So everybody knows this is not the way you would ordinarily code a game this is tremendously horrendous
But I'm using RAW for a game it's just not care for it
What I have working right now so by Galley I'm gonna use it
So I should be able to do now as I struggle to say
Turn off rain and then what's 2160
Add 1080 by 1080
At did not work at all
IC1
My left eye and nothing in my right eye
How do I see nothing in my right eye
What's
Probably fine
Ok the weather Toronto
Why nothing to displaying up in the other eye
Why am I getting only up yet
Google are mysteries going on right now
Is a water mysteries
Does anybody see why this which is not work
One-eyed
Offset axis should be 180 or 1080 cos I want to be over there
What's your local screenex in a local screenwipe
There's no confusion about that
How to use a are much wider field of view
See something in my left eye nothing in my right
No there isn't
What what train will see what happens
I think that's going to make the second frame a very wide frame but what's a
What is definitely interesting you put it in the middle instead of off to one side
So maybe it's
It's just nice pushing it over
Oh it's not using hpto jump that's why
ADHD so ABC
Well it's something awful
How would I stream this to you guys
I'll show you guys whenever I get it working
Almost
It looks like the centre of the frame is not actually
Like centre of each frame
Does anybody remember a diopter
What's the same seller to tan so that would be
Minus diopter in this process died after make it 40
That
Crazy like wrong but
So I'm this
You have one and I'm just by you have the of
That's that's pretty good now
Snow like separation between the two but that's ok for the moment
Try to do next is make it so that the I can be adjusted for Peugeot point
So you actually don't want to spin around like that it all
See how we just want to pass i n
What is the size of this thing that were looking at this
What UNIS deeprot nhmh my
I bet it's huge
Probably huge
I have to steal a dance song
Like my kind of you
If you was weird that I'm finally getting the point in something where we're going to be talking about
Things an actual unit so when I say 40 units it'll be 40 m by
Dead so
Ok
I'm gonna just put up I won
And I still at 111 as well
You should be looking at the thing
I think the one thing we're going to have to do is change
Scaling on the height map
Undo that got to see what we say
Free Guy
Look at home it's a very top I see something so not really sure why that's all the way up there
It is up there in both eyes the same those that's good
Ok I'll see here what will be next
Stop
First I need to do one thing affects the performance
Yeah that was definitely a migraine coming on
Staff we must persevere
Hall and about 1
Ok so it is Center but it's very large
Height map
Sub
You should probably try scaling
Scale here
Hi
Play up
Why is that
Car right now
24 look at
Not exactly the same
You're doing something stupid
What can we be doing that stupid
You know whatever this movie I asked song
What makes no sense
Diverse
Crucify applied to scale there that does anything
Here
But you know what I can do I can just manually change point it's fine
Performer concerning the night
Use the lookup function O2 are so right now
In the centre of frame the
That's working I don't know
Why I can't get the same effect
I just moving the eye back
Exactly the same effect
That's good
Ok so the nice thing about that would be that means two things one if we were 50 m away that's what
Look like brown inside my house so we can get 50 m away at the most we could really get it up to me away
What the thing looks like it out
The kind of big at 1 m away
What's drinking a little bit
0.05 ok so now the next thing to do is hooky and live survive
Actually probably want to start its own trailer
So what we can do that is we can go look at
I won't forget to call my mum back
Our source
I have text
Well I want you texts
Somebody
Obama discussion group Whitchurch was cancelled for tomorrow
Anyway let's go look and see how
Data recorder works
Not need any of this junk
Where does junk
Hey Justin are you still in there if so what is the command for actually getting the final close
Back it up
No like what's the survival after install to get the nice
Like the pose that you randomly your thing with the hook into it
My Rob process pose pose I don't think
What a nice pretty bows and question is there any way to prevent it from trying to do lighthouse calibration right
No I don't want lighthouse calibration
Go to ducal install so right now if I run this it should not do Cal install
Ptx
Outright
Always have a hard time remembering capitalization start
Going to try the rotten world
I want to just say
What is incompatible about it
I'm going to hold the over here come on
Oh ok
Sea flags
Equals double
Wait why is there redefining
So I might have to rebuild long time ago no it's gone
Ok just so what am I missing
Offered to the chat diary of something
I want I can use that
Ok so now we have a pose
That's working
Next thing
We're going after render the eyes from two slightly different point of view let's try that right here
That's obscenely wrong
Is the opposite of what to do
Hey does anybody know how I would be able to share terminal
Make it so that other people online can see the terminal and by train
I mean the Castle
No no the tramadol the hardware camel dive fb0
From the
I can get a bottle of brown know what to do with the buffer
I think there is a thing on PS4
It would be on a separate computer
Ok so probably
Ok this might work yeah I think 0.7 with work
I think it's just a little bit too big so that's good so what were going to want to do right now
What's the advised to be the same
Hand
It's going to be all wrong
To take into account the where the agency is looking
So what I really need to do is convert the quote into a matrix
What do matrix
That's not exactly what I want to do is it
Morpheus if you are you go do it that would be that would be kinda need to be up for trying it
No I think I will use item up it does feel right
I will Star at fullstar up
Done I'm going to
What's TMAX
UB40
I'm just a security login right now
But I can screen only works attacked
No I'm trying to get this video I'm out puddings 2 / 10 / fp0
Yes
Ok cancel
Fb.con which is the frame buffer console
Yeah I want to hear the fp02 something so I can show you guys
It's fine
Maybe you feeling vidstreaming might be quite slow on the OPI
Only getting 1 FPS that's probably sufficient for the sake of this
I think it'd be really needed you guys for watching this thing finally happened
I have
Not ideal
Yeah you should just be able to open Dev fb0 and then like is
Nm-applet into memory
Start time for a bit even if you guys are nice in 1-ft
I'm sure that's fine
Goodnight
Apply poster 0.1
Ok so I guess what I will do is I'll pretend that might
Days are where they are in my head so one I would be at
According to this thing it would be at -7 cm
They said no it doesn't make any sense of it
No that's should be like that 14 mm 1.4 mm so
0.0014
Can I one can I two
Is it really 7335
I don't believe I'll do 30
Exaggerated but ok
Set for last I want to make sure we get our orientation right
Are what PSI is parsec
Arise - x
Why do you think it's fine we'll
You guys don't need a lot of a lot of FPS
I guess we're looking at
Looking Glass
Hey that looks exactly like what I want
What is the tool and never heard of it can you get leg
Can
At
CCS very far past
News
Can up
Turn off
That would be
SY1
Ok
There's a very low chance for this is going to work
Ok Nicky discord now click on it
Just straight up transfer like devafuser work
Compiler is out so I'm not going to
To do this right yet until
Until you guys are watching
How's pin-up mod
There's argument wolf pup star
What's a 40 star
Oh he's supposed to be doubles
That's going to have another
What is to the conversion of here
Oh this is going to require a way more than what I'm doing here we're just trying to get
Basic stuff together
I am not interested in the right answer I am interested in the worst possible answer that gets us what we need
My bill but I'm not going to work through this until we have some way I'm showing you guys
No no running the Sunday pi
We are not going to back out now
I'm alright at myself
Away
Hey wait a minute never mind to move caravan spray
After install ffmpeg
Oh
No no I'm just going to go this
Chappie that bad
Received right I'm JPEG streams
Yeah sure whatever I'll do it
Hey was soaking somebody says type data
Now we've already been doing the camera goggles it's just it's
It's bad because I get to see it first I really don't want it to happen I want everybody to see this at the same time
Not working JME
Not working
What do I do Jamie how do I make it work
The last space
I don't have a display variable
I want to connect to SD Dev
No ffmpeg we're doing it
Oh I see you're saying no I'll be awful doing it over x 4
I'm not sending straight to YouTube
I want to do rtmp
Rtmp
Isn't there some way to just do it like a peg or something
Hey
Address family not supported
Price training
Ffm before you feed URL
Maybe
Operation not permitted
Get to use
Get to use a fb401 than FM before
Does it have to be Dash
Wake me up at 10 p.m. doesn't use a dash
Connection refused
No I wanted to publish to a URL
How do you make SMP published
I'm sorry says
No I got the input that's fine but
How do you how do you make it output to something over the network
FM
To webpage
I don't want to stream from
I'm here honey no no I'm not
Darling Nginx this is like this should be like 50 lines of code
You know what forget it I'm doing it doing it we're doing it we're doing it at least
What after stream.cz include a CD
Age and main
Place fpzero
Tutorial bingo sought-after
Always John Kirby mine
Do it live
Off
No no no no it's not let Spotify Pro
It's not a vipro
It is a prototype but it is definitely before the regular on
Definitely
I'm even care about doing honest that's what I'm after
What is the map what now
Change map
Probably Bob la file size
X 12 1200 x 4
No we're not doing it we're doing it
Why didn't I guess you work before going off with the with the frame buffer vein
Moving on
Ok
So now that we have a potentially and now
What's pocket see what the very first value is map of 0
Ttd live survive
Stream
Scream
Stream.cz CC
Dash
Really I guess clean
Start cleaning
Let's go guys if you have never seen this you will be amazed
Look at the stain
Image rate
Bingo
Elmeg also to crazy files like JPEGs
Cold
ATV underscore image underscore i.age
Home is done
What would I do is we are going to
Halloween clue
Include something
Ok so we have that we're going to include
TV right daddy
Turn on we are going to
The pound to find before I use it I can't see what it is though
How to find that thing
We're going to write jpgs
Whatever filename was just go output right now to just
Splashtastic jpg
Tight so weird height
Define with 2160
How to find height 1200
Ok so there is no way this is going to work let's try this first
Just happened there
Yes haha
Are glorious
Wow that looks like absolute garbage
Don't know why it looks like garbage don't really care it looks like garbage
Tracery
How to 76 KB
Vauxhall Toomey
077 so whatever the thing is clearly demented that he can
Open it but whatever is there is stuck here at school streaming over a webpage
HTTP TCP server example
All see no colour is wrong
It's fine we're gonna to worry about colour or just going to be just just smashing through the stuff
Tcpserver
Who was Kathy all this junk up here
Yeah
Bust size huge
Whatever
FD all that
PC
Which countries was making a time but
Ok
Still copy some more John Coffey internet without any kind of regard for
Ownership
The summer dress from where are we going to go to set up the address to bind 2ru
Let's go bumper cervico down a little bit
I'm going to be raining in mjpeg server yeah
We're going all the way doing it now
Also give the sky credit and travel insurance
Start the way to clear a half of the guy
I got a city lines over to Somewhere not here
No I do have a whole thing cnh GDP but I don't want to do that I want to see if I can ride a hole
Mjpeg server and one c file on see how small it is cos that's more fun
Wayanad
Just do it
OK Google do next thing
So we have our map
The spy device
And then you'll see you do a motion tng right
Each other isn't it
Nice thing about mjpeg is that the browser basic
Forgetting to the sooners in displays at so let's go
We won't even write a multithreaded one it's just going to be one Fred one client whatever
Soft fine
Ring fine
Ok so I'm gonna clean off all TCP server and awful single-threaded TCP services give me the worst of the word
And then we're going to go I don't know it's cats jump it's going on
Organic set the socket or something like that the web servers going to tell us something but I don't really care what it
Received
Tile FC now
Car
So man receive
Received
Sarcastic size 1
So received I left the box office size
Off-plan flag zero
Ok
While
Thrill
Alright ok what I want to do is
Write the function
Thank you Sean Brett you are the coolest
Goals
Turn jpg
Ocean
Http
Looks like somebody hazard and python2 bad redundancy
Nope
You know what we can do we can just do another trick here Wireshark
Guess what we have running right here
Yes
And mjpeg stream
Hello
Ok
Stop
Dddd dddd dddd
We're going to go send this chance to me I don't care what it is
You might even hilarious you're too decent web server
I say hello there yet
And it just disturbs literally jumping back JPEG data
Players
Hilarious
There's no header
Don't even bother
You know what I'm not gonna bother either
Right wingers find out what it is
What is
Call
Sian Brett was nice enough to leave the template light below hand
What is
Out here
Exercise
Tp52
My GPA grade
Without car with hi
Const void data
Data years
Now quality let's just say I'll try once you Friday
Why not
Yeah you know what I would catch sink pipe but you can really get that on a stand
We will sink pipe and pipe I mean not even bothered
Sorry phone on stand
RC here copy
Jpg size
SunBites onion
Man down here
You have an example of somebody who really just says dashdash ipcam 264
Enter and then some content Young
Guitar
IDK m264
Add
Backsplash or backsplash and content-type
Image search
Jpg
Can't add dashlane
Forlan
2 peg size
Ok
Send
Tile ft
Yes
What is the command
To sand
MSG no signal something goes wrong
Send child at the check this one
Boscombe GP size and HD no signal
Connection
What's to see if this works
Oh no this is no multi-part magic this is just a bunch of terms that people strung together in order to get to work
It's just terrible
What's wrong with that line
What's wrong with this
We will accept that
Can't smell
JPEG size stupid so stupid site header header
TVR
From highly
The address for B
18080 / snap.svg
Hello
Contact 90
So you know what I didn't update the fire
Update the size
I know Harris don't start with dash dash
Does it mean won't work
Medium
Ok fine maybe won't work it out
How to make it work
I actually do get the header
I can't there some sort of really terrible
Magic going on
GU10 2800k
That's weird
Set lights to do that
Content area content type
Multipart x mixed replace
Boundary equals
Hey check that out
Electronic
You guys can see what happens
Alcohol yes probably
Lol Locker mythos
Ocular actually
My credentials again
KFC is that what I'm actually seeing through the headset
Yeah that's exactly what I'm saying to the headset
And in fact it's not updating
Close information and see what's going on
All the colours are all backwards but who cares about colours so you know what is even a better way to do this
Oh this we can just reorder the colours by like
Off-by-one in it
I want to see what happens because it's going to be fun
Reduce a random
Set reviews
I don't think so
The colours the same
You know guys I if this doesn't fix the colours after the going through the trial
That's actually completely wrong there
Very cool looking
Ask you can see the
The cursor blinking up here
You could see the cursor blinking
Put the order in here maybe somewhere just
No I think I want rgba
Time
One thing I really want to find out
Arm what happens if I do that
This is a load of attention
I'm really curious
Can the browser handle this
There is nothing in the content type that would indicators jpeg
15 by 2
Keep my we are on in arm so it is all sorts of probable that it's wacky
That's almost really actually
No it's so wrong
What colour is that it's red yellow Israel Iran
Looks like just implying it's good enough
Strongly suggesting that it might be mjpeg
Stream anything that's awful
Ok looks like you guys are going to be getting your foot colour order
Sorry dude
Ok so this is happening right now which is wrong
Because were supposed to be somewhere and looking at something
Definitely not worth seeing something to go print out the clothes here and see what lights revives telling us
Wait does it actually say Imogen somewhere
Oh I'm an idiot
Final ghost in 5-minutes to check the test
And tried tested p&g
Yeah I don't think browser is no handle motion Cian juice like that
So for some reason my stomach getting close information
Revert
JPEGs to files to JPEGs JPEGs
All the way down
Yes fpzero is an app straight onto Matt Dillon
Emma can that be what
Pause it as you can open up a file but pretend that is just a bunch of memory that we don't have to read things in or out of it
Can just go read data like an array is so it's part of the file itself 250g
Instead of having to like speak to you want and read out what you want then seek somewhere else you can do
Napit directly into memory and then you can just access stuff in the erase you would just feel like it
Emma Disney
That's that's really wrong
Why are we getting
Lights alive
That's right
Boss orange pytest' history grab
Orange hi test
We have to pass it to write parameter if you want to get the data
And we also do that
That is
Lee Ryan
By the way it's
Pretty going to be in the glasses to them now
It is actually
General effects on them
Working
Turn down
Oh my gosh
It is like I can walk around the thing it's just
Downer anything
So right now I'm saying it from one side song
Intensifiers
From underneath
The way to use oh my gosh no
Someone you loved
Route
It should not be doing now
If I rotate my head one way
The other way is actually rotating the object appropriately so that's really good
This is as Jackie is it should be oh my god
Survive on an Orange Pi while streaming of with the world's worst witch
Who are the care of you watching record apple
I can walk over here and see if I can still on hit the chair
Set the heart I'm cracking
All the way around the chair without hitting it
Only use the headset to tell me where I think the chair is
The chair
So this is actually working I am running
I am running at successfully on the Orange pi
The world's worst VR system
Ok I'm going to go put the
This might be the very first live stream where
Where we try to do something and it may have worked
What is the happiest 100fps
Yeah I'm sorry 90fps so that's working out it's just lights off
When is absolutely janky
What's a top
The thing was visible to everyone right like I didn't actually put it behind something I shouldn't have right
What is orange Pi podcast ok that's fair in fbstreams using a
Even though it's system
What's the thing even doing
Pause
This is a livestream I'm going to be releasing
Change the way this works I'm gonna go change fbstream
So it copies it to a butter first and then send ZL
What else I can do is
Happy Direct action should be with 32
I think I just written the worst code I've written in
Years and I had a blast
Hey this is a lot better now or not
You're going to do work
Send 8:30 pixels
No I call Mike ice papa is dropping the green channel
Aladdin the green channel
That way
We can do it that way now
You know it's starting to get fun this is this is little
The worst code I ever actually remember writing even though if
I don't even
I don't even know how it's doing whatever it's doing that's
I truly horrendous
This is
What is this chat how do I write what is this I want to do this bank somebody just send me another one
72a terminals route
I don't know what I looking for here what is
Oh snap
I am going to have to turn off the dri2 bug
Stuff that can cause all sorts of problems
Yeah let's do that
Dr on the bog with her 2ff that's probably not needed
Right now though I just want to get this thing working again with
What's right to me
Definitely
How to stop that systemd alarm from stewing everywhere eventually as soon as
Should get fixed
That's really
Really low quality
Yodel
Is it out of 100 I think it's one two or three
No the problem is it with you when you some colour is that
It's it's actually really bad
Appreciate it
Actually it's need
So what you actually seen here is your seen the colour channels bleed into each other across
The B boundaries that's why it's doing that wacky stuff they're because when we divide by
Or it's bringing the least significant bit into the next lowest register which
Play really do a really awful tricky fix bad in week by doing it this way we could say
And 0 x arm
ABC CCFC FC
It's going to do is stop the the best better than all registers when we shift down from going into the
Next upper thing is no longer that Dad is
And operator in there
Why did that happen like that a dark
CSCS
CSCS c
I'm having the wrong B I think
I am hitting the wrong B C
CSCS
No wouldn't be bitswap I think that I'm I was accounting for favourite
Already down but they may not be see what happens if I know I did
It might be
Yeah I think I'm eating the other bits so I think I want to hear I think this is right
Now it's still wrong
Ch3f ok news only
Anyways this could be you want exhaust them
He's right you can't do this while separating each colour last
Well
Turn off
You can do it up here
Yeah I don't know if this is right or wrong
Not apparently 200% correct but exactly how you do it
Ok so that's actually pretty good quality now
Why would I
Down as it's too far away and I look up it's so much better
You know what
I make need to
Yeah I am just needing the the resolution
Actually no we could have just scrap all of this and you guys can just look at every like for pixel
You don't need to see them all
Why didn't I just do that first it's obviously the awful way to do it
Sapphire walking down
Firework Down it looks
Really far away and look up it gets much bigger and that's definitely
So let's see what could be causing that
I would definitely stay the system awful cold it's very good results
Stop pretty much admin that was an hour of my considering now it's a streaming
JP web server that reads from memory mapped file and streams
It's pretty good for an hour
So one thing that sometimes happens is a look at some times
Next all of your your values to be on like orthogonal
Not orthogonal bad things can have it so that's one thing that might have gone wrong
Actually looking at this I think it's unlikely that
What's what's going wrong
Awesome
Printing a good time to let us commit that and we do
Hey darling have you Hooked Up the chat anything yet because you totally can
Oh that's a good question
And then I will
See how this goes
I am like always the colonel sink faltered
Power off icon
What's the temperature
UK
Survive sex
Actually electron Ash
I can't do it that way I have already ordered earlier today
Lipo battery
It's already been ordered it's too late now
Can't really read it because it is
Really terribly scaled
Oh Mum
What's the time headed to do
This is what I intend to do
Do not want to be printing out the post like every frame
Ok so I is that
That's about right yet
Why is up
Wow that's weird
Adds no copyright
Oo option using the
Position is it say it's just a direction it's not a on like a sieve
Active things so for up you would want to subtract on
Is better ways of doing this but we're just going to do
Just terrible way right now
Can-can off
0 - 10
So the problem it's the up that wasn't funny
Stop it was like
Appoint over here where is the up is supposed to be like a vector it supposed to point in the direction
Supposed to be unit length
Lidl super wrong
Let's go over there and take a peek
As you guys can't really see it I'll bring it up next time
Hey well that actually looks like a pistol stop
Stop
Ok so I'm trying to work here
How old is Stefan just died
I am outside
So yeah
How long was Everything getting a use the iPlayer on screen
Much better refresh
Getting me up
Touch it
Real
Pause
Put this back together and then
I mean I can just hold it up to my face
Actually know what I want to try first
Like
Like that's what it actually looks like for me inside of there
It's a problem noise I think
Google by the way if any of you guys want to help out with life survive
Totally a project that needs more people
Yeah
Give me a second can you stand still don't move cosmetics
Is it might be a little darling let me change one thing
You know what would be a better place
Getting back off from it's the point where
Right now you have to get the other other lighthouse in UB40
Ok now the lighthouses in bewsey Nice Builder
Try holding your hands for their back so I can get to the yeah that works too
Does it feel better
This is working here
Hopton I think one day
With the Charles toes are still needs to be able to be seen on the first lighthouse in ordered operate so
Back up to the point where
Intersection of lines
Filled in landscape which was really nice
Like the back corner
Oh I see you're saying you don't like
You try to make those triangles hold on give me a give me a minute don't don't don't move too much
Give me a
Tea
I can figure out how they do that
GTA
Armour stand
Make the small work
Big salty
Give me a second
Nothing
Text Holly
C words crashing
Don't forget to join alive survive group
I'm discord
It's just like way up there so
That has nothing to do with this
Posed
Hey
Looks like we still getting on
Do you mind if I make it
Power
No I won't overlap quite as bad
Hey ok can you get close to it
The chair yes actually
Put your hand in where you think the middle of it is
Much further hire
I'm not really sure how to file that
Yes so now
Tracking
As you take your right hand
Off and move it somewhere else you might be able to get further but not all the way
Am I now adjacent to the other side
Now that's
What's call Barbara Adam
Ok guys what else do we want to do in I say word on it
Probably just hang up and go home
Yeah
Hey you guys want to see how much power does things uses
So
3.4 Watts
You can run the vibe on a computer that draws 3.4 Watts
I'll be calling for done
I'll be down this is a fun Project
Final price
I'm like still getting chills this is something I only ever dreamed of
Thank you so much
Albino French everybody but like a happy ending
Making that push to the poser that was just that's just amazing
This is only the orange Pi one
Can the orange Pi still has 3 CPU
Which is absolutely mind-blowing
It goes
Thank you everybody for coming out tonight
How much is a running within an hour
Thank you everybody for coming out tonight this is being an abscess
Blast on I just I'm so happy with this
I hope that
Will get some more people contributing and we can make even more happen with lights alive
Yeah guys go for it take a straw Paul did you like the stream what did you like what did she like
What time Jamie on the discordant give me a heads up
Oh yeah you want to see it with nothing wrong
If I kill wife survive the goes to 5.5 hundred something milliamps
If I kill the streamer yeah so it really doesn't use that much right now
Imagine once we start using the GPU a little bit heavier it's gonna start coming to get a reply
Have a baby did this have a great evening guys