Hello I think I just went you guys can get in the
Chat tell me if my levels are okay this is about how loud I'm going to be during the broadcast
I think I'm set up a little bit better with it today don't know still don't see anybody in the
Can you guys hear me because it sounds great
Oh yeah I realize that the levels were pretty low
Yesterday and so when I got loud he got really loud
So we don't want to do that
Just pulling up a little bit of stuff right now getting my screen size
Set up
Think I just pulled
Everything's up to date
K
That looks good too
Potestas
Excellent working so it's about time to start the
Video here check the
Whoa there is
Is bunch of people in 15 seconds like how do
Do you guys know how much like there is OB cuz of the video to begin with
Okay so let's start video now
I say that because I shall start as like I say that because what I'll do is I'll go back and edit it so the video actually stopped
Specific intro anyway
So in a previous video I was hacking the HTC Vive controllers and trying
How to figure out what the various messages that come from them are now they're very well understood when you plug them in but
They're not that well understood if they're trying to communicate wirelessly and one of the highlights from last time
Was that one of the developers of the vibe hopped in and started giving away some tips in
Intrexon stuff like that some of the things that I'm just assuming that he the reason this is so much more
More complicated is because these things are using Nordic semi chip and bases precious so
He did a number of really really clever things to try to Pare down the amount of data is being sent back
Unfortunately it means that it's extremely difficult to figure out what he did so
In the previous video we we got a lot of stuff kind of torn apart and figure it out and if you haven't already
You probably should really watch the starting
Love it because it kind of shows really what this is all about and I don't want to go into that again
But I did want to show you guys was so that a VR thing that I had working on here
Now it has three LEDs and I can't earn each one of them on and off individually
And the they are right now map tint
Two different holes on the Vive controller so I can turn them on and off individual
And this is one where I have my environment ready I have everything ready to go but I want to make it more
So what I'll be doing is I have the the AVR code that I can easily change
And that's right here this is all just the AVR code
That can control lighting up a specific marker and I can have code that'll do this and I
That can light up two markers at once or all three markers at once and what we're going to try to do is we're going to try to light up
Combinations of these three markers to figure out what his code actually does and what those funky
He commands me so I have no problem with opening up a adjust
GitHub and copying and pasting a bunch of these examples into the jet so you guys can participate in real time
I'm honestly a little bit more burned out today than I was last time so you guys be great
Timmy Guy start taking initiative start to really think critically about the packet and and
How they might be going together so let's just start with first things first
The just so you guys understand what's in the Stream here actually first
Brandon are you in chat
So far you guys who don't know my my roommate inverse phase over there he is acting as
Moderator she's actually working on a a python track of a python like chiptunes music
And it says he is a chiptune artist and he knows python so he's been out here the last couple of days up till 4
For 5 a.m. working on that tracker anyway moving forward here
Let's let's actually get into what these different fields mean
And how about how we learned it so what actually happened
When's that comes back from the The Watchmen this thing right here is the
Is the messages
229 B messages it were pretty sure that we figured out exactly how big of that message we care about
And just Lop off the end additionally we think this is based on some of the things that Ben hits
Said that the last four B
Are the CRC of the on-air checksum so we can probably discard them
Especially considering I think they would be the Searcy of the encoded data
So I'm just going to ignore them for right now the other things that we found out
Bi-directionally encoded so from the back of the stream going forward you can look at the numbers and
And they mean different things so the last three B here are the time code of when nothing happened then
Start reading back this number right here is the length and this case of the pulse time
And this is the code of which led was was the one that was on so right now I'm only blinking when I leave
So it's code 48
Yeah we're in the other dc-baltimore area so it is Us East time
Knoxville to stay up past midnight maybe probably 12:15
Stay off tonight eastern time so that's about 3 and a half hours from now
Amish I think you should be able to get pretty far 4 hours Brandon
I'm going to call him Brendan but his name is inverse phase and
You guys like chiptunes I'm going to ask him to go like paste the link to his YouTube
Moving on does anybody have any questions right now about the data as it stands or should I just keep going into
To what we found out so far just see what some people think I am expecting
A little bit more feedback this time how many people are
Find the chat
Okay that's good it's not
Not as big but okay so what we know so far is the last for
Then the next 3 going from the back forward is the is the time
Encode and then comes this absolutely insane thing that then did what happens if
Is your going backwards is you look at a number and if the ones place or sorry there's a
One in the the 128th Place Saudi 1/8 or higher out front
What happens is you have to read the next fight over to find out what's really going on I'm so in this
Case we have zero X 0481 so I'll just show you guys wouldn't that
I would really look like so 0 X8 1004
Number and so what we're going to be doing is we're going to be reading it from going back
So the way when we would read this as we would first look at
0x 0 4 and with that indicates is that there'll be another bite
Because it's less
Is less than 128 and so we read the next bite
But first we do is we shifted over seven places so 200 47
I can't do that bummer
47 places that's 512 which is
0 x 200
What we do is we look at the next fight over so 81 so because
Is a greater than or equal to
128 if a terminator and so what that mean
As we can just order the enemy. So that's your X200 or 0 x 81 equals your X2
281 and that's the actual value based on some hints from them
Dan from last time what we know is all of these values that are here these the values that will be after the star
Barcode with by-the-way 48-star the LED codes 48 is the LED code all of these back here
Are just relative times so what happens is we going to pause this will start at time
A6 C5 D5 and then
We know that led number 48 notice they're all divisible by 80 also pointed that out
And so it starts at this time
He is on and it is on for this length of time which is decoded as 0 x 281
And then it turns off and then that's the end of it so right now all that are actually doing
And here is we are turning on or linking it to MHz about
Seems to work better if I go like much slower I'm thinking it's around 1.4 MHz I don't know why that works
Better but anyway I turn it on and off a 2.4 megahertz for a bit of time
And then I sleep and so that's how we get this the most basic code
This is really simple to read now that we know how to do it it does it is a little bit can
Using cuz the order of things is a little wacky but it
It it it is totally I won't break the Vive again datum
It is totally doable I bricked the Vive yesterday and it is
Bricked permanently sort of I was much earlier in the day was trying
Find Rudolph the configuration data but I accidentally had the set B set instead of
Set witch
Which which actually
Made it wipe out all of the hid data for the configuration for the vibe
You things just fine I could even read your headset but all of the config data that talk about the gyros in the exact location
Of all of these things was totally blown away which also I found out that
This is crazy with the who it's all sweaty from me anyway
Nation of all of these sensors is calibrated in the factory Sono to Vive the same and they know that
And the vibe store their config data I blew away mine somebody on Fox fired
I think his name was was was really really helpful
And and and and he was able to give us a copy of his config for similar Vive which after tweak
Making some values we were able to get going again I can't really tell the tracking difference but
But everybody online seems to think that this is horrible and that it's going to be terrible
I think I looked out and addition then shot an email to HTC to see if they can actually pull
A copy of our config from this Vibe as it was shipped which if they do that
Whole thankful back to 100%
And if not well it looks like I'm going to have to reverse-engineer the rest of all of this mess so that I
I can go calibrate this at myself
Oh really
So Adam this is my roommate he's the vibe
Has he has a plugged into his computer
By the way if anybody does want to hack your Vibes definitely pull a full report from the Vive using steam 1st and
Use the lighthouse tool in order to backup everything which you can totally do you can just dump the data
There's a directions if you look up I blew away my HTC Vive config on Reddit and there's a
Supposed there Adam I guess if you can like it moving forward
Bri have three LED and I have my source code here
EXC
And there's a command you can just execute at work
Moving on to the first thing I'm actually going to do here isn't going to change
Change the way the make fireworks and what I'm going to do is I'm going to say if I say
Make
Test. Hacks is also going to burn so if I
Just say make
Oh wait I want to say
Hake
So now if I haven't changed the code it won't update the
Dv80r so like saved now
It'll update tavr so what I can do is I can say while true do make
Sleep 1.5 done bomb and so now it's going to be rain that make over
Over and over and over and over again just going to go move that off to another window so I don't have to worry about it
Now I'm going to go
Rumsey the biking again and what I can do is I can interactively
I'm going to be able to take the code here
And I'm going to be able to tweak it
In real time
So
I'm going to be able to say change this so say I want to make it to the duration of the pulse is longer right now you see it's zero
0481 I'm going to say make it forty whatever those units are
Now if you notice it paused for a split-second that was when I save the file to change back to 30
Pause and it keeps going do you see how fast that is that's instantaneous and what's really going on
Soon as I save this file it's going and it's reflashing remove this over the other
Other window here as soon as I save the file it goes Andre Flash
Is it in that sit avrs are awesome for really fast development cycle so
That totally
That will totally work and see what Chad is doing
Okay yeah nothing really that clear
Yeah sorry well this is not going to be that long of a the stream this is going to be a much shorter stream
Cuz I'm going to have to go to bed by like 12:15 cuz I'm
Beat it anyway. Moving forward I can change these these data the theater right here
And I can load it into
And I can load it up in almost immediately
Okay so you guys are actually waiting and ready to get some data
Okay
240 hero 2:40 a.m. that's a bummer let's get some data okay so this is
Is the most degenerate case we see can I open up a GitHub
Allure are just right at out is now
Subject
Create a new gist
HTC Vive Watchman
Packing session
Codes
HTC Vive
Watchmen codes
Start off with
Tavr code women actually do is when I have some Panda Vines
Three as
4 LED 40 and
Play B-52 the side of the controller and we're only going to be operate
Waiting on that one so it's going to say LED
And we're going to just put this all together
So going to do here and then when I turn on LED 40
Wait a little bit I'm going to turn on LED 50
And then I'm going to try on LED 48
Okay so that should be what we need to have done I just delete that okay
I just saved it and it should be updating I was not why is it not updating
The compiler there is
How to find elk
Just so you guys know underscore BV is a synonym
Is a synonym for one that
And it has to do with the way in which AV rgcc handles 16 deaths and still having a hard time
What is it doing underscore delay
Underscore us
Okay so now we have three LEDs that are turning on and off
4050 + 48
Although it looks like I might have my order backwards so that's a little concerning
What's make sure that nothing really wacky is going on I'm sa48 50 + 40
4850 40 so now it's going the wrong direction
I must have
Messed up some code here let's check that out
Amy least get back to something sensible and then I will upload some some dumps
HT survive there is yes this one
To Lily somewhere in here
Just that was right I thought it was wrong for some reason but maybe I was just
40 40 50 that's wrong
40 Ino that's really wrong
4050 48 is that correct
Wait what's going on
4050 48th
Does anyone have any idea why these numbers are coming in in the order they're coming in on cuz I I would not expect this code produced that out
Michigan's I just tried swatting it and I think I
4850 40
So now it's right oh you know what I never rebuilt it that's what the problem was okay so now it's actually correct
So moving on now so this is a really basic dump and I will go
Post this to the just github just right now
So the way this goes is
I post my aviar
Code
Then I post what the HTC Vive does
Oh and
So that a VR code there
Produces
Following output
Donk
The output is
Post 0
However the 16oz l number of B
Iemu timecode MSDS
Then
All raw light data
Echoes events
Time
Colon
LED
Code Flash
Timecode one
Timecode to
Flash
Lady code
Notice stuff funky and coding of the numbers
And the fact that parameters are read from the end of the data
Going forward
We know we're done when the number of parameters red is
Is
Number of fights left
X
B w x 2
No
+ 1
Yeah that sounds right
Is it
See what is it it is
Note
Raw light data ends with
Free B
LSPD timecode
Gotye
CRC
Probably ignore
So see here sweet nor the last four week nor these that's one parameter to parameters three parameters
Four parameters five parameters and three values
So five
X 2 - 1
Yeah that's actually right okay cuz if you only have one LED on you only need one for amateur cuz you only need to know the LED turned on
The time code which led it was and how long that led was on totally do it
Okay let's create a public
Just
I have not placed a digikey order
Which by the way
Did you hear me
So I'm going to link you guys this public just
I see you I'm going to do some I stick it in the
Brendan do you have you don't have rights that it at least if I can add that
I can
Do I save
Okay people in chat are you ready to start
Adam which LEDs you want to have added
Civility order
We probably shouldn't be doing business though
In a live stream event
But any rate I have now posted the first bunch of data so this is a really simple case I want you guys
That's the kind of start looking at it and make sure you get a little bit more comfortable with
With what format this is in in so I guess we're going to go on from there
Is fading who's going to be looking at the state up
And in trying to reverse-engineer this with me
You're probably going to able to do better than I can
Okay good Paul so the first thing that I want to do in this is just something
I don't know
It means you can't have it pulled up in
And in and just whoever wants me to go more into
What the data means
Just tell me and I will go I will try to go back and explain it more and understand that I
I still don't know what certain codes mean so I'm I'm just I don't know right now
Tried different things to create those codes and we'll see if we can figure out what they mean
Nobody saying anything
Okay
That's fine I guess I will just start
Engineering the first thing I wanted to look at was if I turn on 48
And at the same time is 48 being on I turn on 50 so I can say or LED
48th and then I turn off LED 50 so backed up
LED 48 only
I mean okay not really awesome cuz if he didn't engineer possible we'd be done and I could move on
By the way I was up too loud the levels right I hope I got the levels
Okay I will add the note about
Parameter fields
Are encoded
Read from
End
Going forward
If value in Earth
MSB is
Is
Just in case means bail
Is is 1
Aisha rx80
It is done
If
Not then need to read next fight
I'll copy and paste the explanation from here
Stream brought to you by caffeine
I actually did not sleep at all Saturday night cuz I was to wire so
No caffeine for me
Any rate so I'm going to go
Update public gist
Now
Okay so if you have the gist open refresh your page
And it will be updated for you
So the next thing I'm going to do now is we're going to look at the data
If I do the whole thing so fight
Turn on LED 4
LED 50
Watch documentaries
Blank
Time for following
So anybody who's a tuning in now what I have is I have the AVR tape to The Watchmen controller
3 LEDs
And I have my AVR code here
And I can just save it and it reflash is it immediately so if I'm running this
If I change the code
So if I comment out this block right here
And I say save
It pauses and then keeps going
What I just posted was a really basic thing maybe I'll post this is another example
Call just to see how simple it can really get
Okay
Then the more advanced one the one I wanted to show you guys that I don't understand right now
Is this one so what we're doing is returning LED 48 on 50 and 48 and then 48
I'm going to save that and
Why does it not like that
Herpa derp
Okay saved it and now it's updating so now this is a little bit more complicated
It turns on
For a little bit
And then just for a little led50 on for a little bit and then back off to just 48 and up
Uses a code that makes no sense to me
I'm going to go upload that here so that
Produces
That
And then we're going to try also is swapping it around so it will be 50
48 + 50
So we're going to see what that looks like
Notice how they are different so
Do you not understand
What's going on here so one of the things been told us last time was to take note
Betty's LED codes were all divisible
By 8
I'm so what that means is there is now three bits left over at the beginning of the the LED code to tell us additional in
Information
I don't know what those B do
Helpful is asking about your workflow
And I mention that you're probably just up and entering on and they can run this tomorrow morning
And control so I guess I should say that again
What I've done is
Is I have it set up over here
With me cantaloupe so what's going on is the system is constantly looking for new changes
New
New ain't anything that changes
And if it changes then it will send recompile and send the new binary to the ER
So if I just save the hex file
Recompile zitra flashes and now this AVR is burning new code
Wish I could have this hanging here so you could see it but I don't think it really matters
I'm so now if I run this and do right now is going to save the save the gist
This is going to live over there now
Or not how about that
Yes
So does this give anybody else any ideas for things that you want to start looking at right now
I think some of the things that really Stan
Mario
Some things that stand out to me is you see the 48
And then you see the 52
But the 52 is
Has the the the one set in the tooth place and the same thing is for a so
Over here if you look when it goes one way it's 54 and then here is 48-52
Until 4 a.m. is actually just 48
Text
With the two bits
48 hacks with the two bit set so something about what we've done here makes the two-bit get
What are the things I want to check next is to make sure that these times are doing what we think we're doing
Somerset at 2 instead of being 40 microseconds each I'm going to set it to 80
I'll keep the first one at 40 and I'll make the 80 and I'll make it 1:20 and we'll see what happens
That's not what I would have expected
That number does not look like a legitimate number
Amber looks much much larger than a legitimate number
Maybe something is wrong in my code that would identify that
141 980
Okay so it is still working is I make this number bigger it makes that that value on screen this
Remember right here the length of appropriate Lee larger that's weird
Apparently there's a maximum you can get to think
Oh that's weird it's like
Wraps around
Oh I'm confused now let's start small
Okay so I don't actually do
Do all three LEDs at once because I can't control which
Or when it starts detecting them you get like conditions were like it'll turn on turn on by I don't know which
Which one really turned on before the other
Yeah I don't know what's going on right now why did you guys want to look at the the streams of guinea-bissau read the numbers on my
Clearly so that the 50 the the 501c
7 whatever I don't know why this is so 10 microseconds 183
20 microseconds 35640
Okay so is working 80
9100 Hoops 100
200-300 no 300 broken
222 40
To 50 to 60
Thank you thank you I got that
Northfield
Thank you okay how are we going to do that then
Okay then just to make sure that this isn't going to completely get hoes I'm going to have to have to
Put a loop around the outside
Okay we're cooking again Charles is not all dumb
To me if I take
Take twice as long here it goes from 40 470 something 298 something so I'm
Pretty
Pretty happy with that
Or
Okay we're going to have to remember this for later cuz I think this might might be important
I'm going to make a note of this in the gist that
That
Produces
This
But
13 produces
Nothing at all
That would mean to me that maybe what's going on there is
That maybe this values maximum is 65 530 around 6
Which is interesting cuz that means that maybe there's a way to encode more data above that
Cuz there's definitely date available cuz like lucketts 037 bb7
Is 64 951 so there's there's room for more information to be there and let's see what the
That actually works out to see if that's reasonable so calc so 60
5535 / 48 millionths of a second
35 x 48 millions of a second
That's 1.365 milliseconds
I go look up the
Where's the life and I hear it is somebody who documented
What the light emissions were so that would be text 2000
Stuffed is his system should never ever be running into an LED receiving data 460
5000 so let's just take a note that
Note that the numbers could be to be over that
Is the maximum think that there might be more data there that we're just not seeing
Because it's 65,000 the representation is 037 whatever and then another number
So that leaves plenty of bits of space left and knowing then there's no way he's going to
You wasting those bets
Just watched a Chinaman
Right now so we can make fun of them right
Like a surprise
What do you mean
Robin earlier I thought
Okay nevermind maybe Ben is watching so let's let's go
Okay so that's interesting let's go back and keep doing the tests from where we were
So this one is 50/50 + 48 + 50
Make this 80
Are you guys seeing what I'm seeing cuz this value here is definitely not
0 are not not what between the two numbers
I'm going to add that to the gist
Okay so there is interesting data so
50 + 48
But this bit here is high
Means that somehow between these two things
Is encoded the information necessary to understand that can be turned on and something and off
You should take that and
Okay
I don't know what to do with that that's very strange to me
Go back to 8080 and 80
Do weird okay
Potatoes definitely doing something I would not expect
Okay so it looks like the major values are the same but
The minor are not does anyone mind poking at the hero me just this right now
So hard to get it
Did anyone mind trying to figure out what's going on there and why my code is when that particular number
It's large enough that could be wrong so he doesn't mind like reverse-engineering that string there
And making sure that I'm decoding it at least as far as we think correctly for that there
This is just thinking because if we do 4:30
We see the length of time go from 5:43 to 3:24 to 185 which like to meet
That makes sense like 14 but
What doesn't make sense
Is
Why I'm doing the same operation LED 5048 + 50 + 50
And that that's going on there I'm going to go back to chat now
Are you able to edit and put it
What is what are they asking
The GitHub project okay I'll add that
A project in the description
Adjusting the description
It is very good that navr has got more than 10,000 right Cycles
Hello
Hi is this the George that
That works with Kevin
Anyway
Moving on
So if you guys don't mind let's let's if if somebody can just double check that for me the gist
And try to figure out why
Oh wait somebody's commenting
I don't know what is this a this produces 48 for the LED
Okay moebius Horizons what is your name in chat who are you
See I think I saw your icon somewhere
Don't know what's going on
Yeah just does look funny
Oh hi Paul okay
Okay I see what you mean changing next
Part of me really wants to understand about that time so maybe
That's just so weird I don't know why that's the case last bit set
LED 50 but shows no data something else
I don't know how about this let's just try turning on different LEDs so 40
4040 so we 48 + 40
Simultaneously a how do I explain that no I'm
I'm right now we're operating only with 2 LEDs and we're already getting dated that makes no sense to me
That would definitely have to figure out first before we start getting into the third LED
Okay so maybe the different LED low give you a little bit of data there
That's Led 40in Led 48 and LED 40 and produces 48
8:42 I guess I could do it the other way around 48
48v 840
Why does that not work
How much more concise
Syntax for just
Back to the chat okay so can you guys think of any new test you want to
To run right now let me know
Anything else we can think of
Something that's like nice and simple
Know what else we would be able to figure out here
Maybe if we do I know we can do can turn on 40 at the same time as Forty-Eight and then turn off
LED 48 but leave 40 on and then turn it both off I'm so let's try that
That's a little bit of a difference thing there
Are that some instead of being 44
Something going on here
Oh whoops there's bugs me go fix the bugs first
Okay okay
Now we can see that the code is different
Okay so now we think we got that working non-overlapping
Pulses
Okay Jeremy I will do that for you so LED which led should we do just LED
Lycee 48 and then 45
Like that 50 US pulse 30 pulse 70.
See what that produces k
Okay what else any other ideas next swap LED
Switch LEDs you want me to do the tests we did a few minutes ago like
This but with just different LEDs
So let's say 50 + 50
I'll be that
I guess I can do it other one yet let's do 40 and 50 at the same time
Okay come on guys need some more ideas hear anything you guys want to see
Daniel you had some suggestions
Variable length quantity on Wikipedia is good for explaining some Concepts
Brendan can you check that and see if I should add that as a
A link to the just
You mean you want the link no I just want you to check Wikipedia and see if it's worth adding to the gym
It's represent big eyes
Okay can you put the link in this thing I can pay today
20-20-20 so the time code is a big issue
Okay I can do 20 20 20 and 30 30 30 or 20 20 20
See what that looks like
That's 20-20-20
Make sure it actually isn't to save it yep now as a big note because
Cuz this is an analog system in here 20-20-20 depending on the order in which things
Happened that the 20 is going to be different cuz it's going to have a different analog value as it goes
So I will record that
Though for you
21 21 21
Ulta to 22 22 22 so we can make sure that it is behaving the way we
Okay.
Any other ideas from anybody I guess I will add this to the
Already tried a bunch of different timings they're available in the the document here
GTR code is sitting in the GitHub repository under the tools folder
It's already it's already there do you mean commit I guess I should
Okay
Dang anything else you guys want to stay
Oooo so
Sad we think that all of these times
Are the time
Are are the Deltas between the start time so it would go start time Delta
Star tile
Whatever happens at the start time like 10 transition
Before the next event happens this other thing turning on so they're all written as
Delta's
And so yeah that would it is probably understand
So it's going to be like offset by a certain amount
Where's my turn it on for many more than there's going to be the linear and nonlinear dropping the beginning
Do you suggest another time cuz I can certainly try it
I guess I'll try 555 and see if it reads at all whoopsies
Yeah it's not even reading barely at 5 so if I did
That might read
Yeah that red
Although that did not read the way I would have expected
That's that's interesting
I don't have a you are connection but I do have a tiny ice P turn connection
Interesting idea but it would be difficult to correlate the data
Well I mean let's just see maybe I can do that
I know I have a copy that I wrote Somewhere
Sure let's see if it has tiny 85
There is a copy
Can just use this
And came from
Here
I'm going to include a VR print
I can remember how
Set up STI
And then we're going to do let's just
Yes okay we can actually get data coming back from the AVR see you guys wanted me to do it
For something I don't know how I would correlate the data though
Oh wait the people are saying other things well now I can
Oh yeah I know nobody was able to decompile the farm where we didn't find any any good thing for that
Actually if any of you guys can go find a good decompiler for 8051 could that be awesome but from what I could
Tell nobody has a decompiler for 8051 that's any good
CM Laura can you check LEDs 40 and 60 on uniform timing I cannot test l86
50 it is not hooked up to my controller
And I don't know my
My butt doesn't fall asleep so 30-30-30
I don't know what you want for
Susan 8051 one of the Cypress chest one of the Nordic chips that has a 8051 core and Wi-Fi
That Wi-Fi wireless it's a really funny and interfaces use the
Crfs for awhile
I totally works
Or does it know something's wrong
Why is code broken cook broke broke not good
Oh you know what if I do this I can only access LEDs 48 in
40 LED 50 is wired up to the the SPI bus for printing so I'm going to
Not do that right now
Okay everything's back to normal
Paul how much do you want the LEDs further away from
Cuz it does mean pulling all the tape off
VK Tuesday if you don't mind the firmware
Encrypted
And that would be super swanky
Tell you what call I will I will do you a huge favor here
I will
I will pull this thing off and put it on another side
Number is only with the field of which receiver is
I do not know what he is asking
That's interesting
Oh okay
Yeah I don't know how to get this set up in such a way that we can test this easily
Let's just do that later
Type LED 40
Probably more Operator Operator in this context
LED 50 in LED 5000 LED 40
Van led40
Okay so he wants to see oops
Huh
Well if you try 50th and 50th and 40th and 40 okay
Then
15 and 40 than 40
Yes it does change actually that's really interesting it changes to exactly the opposite
Watch the controller's the Watchman is the nickname for the control
For the wireless controllers
You have any other recommendations for things we can look at right now without having to try to reconfigure the physical
Configuration
While you're absent waiting for an answer on that Ott wants to know if there's a way that you can get
Summarize
I guess he's been recording for a little while now
How long has it been it's been an hour and 20 minutes to summarize
Sokol for the previous stream figure out what these guys did and what the wireless
Communication was because the unwired communication is very well-documented no wired stocking Tatian is documented
Well after we found out what your the basics was the trigger and all that I did
MyON
Then we started to try to decode the light data amazingly been one of the guys who designed these things
I'm hopin to chat and started getting us little tips and tricks and everything and then after a little while he
Now start giving us more and more information
And we were able to find out a number things one is there variable-length fields to his perimeter
There's are red from the back going forwards and then the echo LEDs are red from the front going back
And the number of B inside of everything started the 8th
Point-of-use variable-length field and then we found out that the last four bites for probably.
Kcrc
Which means we can ignore the next 3 B are probably
Delta's between different events and I definitely seen the Deltas between different events as
Isaiah
I think that I'm pretty sure that's actually what the case is
So Paul says 10-20-30 on 4040 4840
So 10
On
And
I guess that's it
I know you guys probably want to keep watching that shrink down so I'm going to
Get here
MK
So this is what what Paul has requested
Tom
Yeah you're going to lose the stream right after this so
Call my gosh it's so tiny
See here
So I guess what I would do is
Copy that here into
Yeah sorry guys that that Inception thing is totally done now
10:20 p.m.
I hope you're not just messing with me fall I hope you're actually thinking critically about this
Yeah it looks like that just changes the last number here which is what I would expect
Ojai George we haven't talked in a long time
Oh so we already are decoding all of the
The button data and I'm handling that separately and I'm pretty sure I'm doing it right and I'm handling
I'm pretty sure I'm doing that right so I should be able to
That's the wrong controller I should be able to click the buttons all I want and it should have little or no effect on
What actually gets triggered so
Maybe there is one or two unknown things but as
Play I can see it sometimes it's flashing but as you know later on we'll figure out what those two
Some flag turn on
Okay do you have anymore tests that you want to do Paul on the bow okay hi Daniel
The timings for 4452 C470 to be expected
Okay so there's something really important going on here the LEDs can't be mounted perfectly with the
Perfectly onto the dots I've gotten a free good so don't expect the numbers to
Do you like
Unless we exaggerate the values a lot more
First static b i e not messing with you
First static Vice
What are you referring to
Okay so originally I did this by having lighthouses on cuz I figured how hard could reading this data
And I had lighthouses on and I did a bunch of dumps and nothing made any sense at all
So we switched to using a VR to send out the pulses to the the controller because that would
Made it now I can actually control it we can see known pulses
About what it is
And
And actually look at the outfits from that so there's another test you'd like me to run ivory
Really like to hear it so Daniel leave if you have anything else you can think of that would be
Really cool otherwise if you guys want we can move into three LEDs now
To give it a shot
May I guess I could just do a few more tests on this like
I'll make this 2010 4040
Message to 1048 exaggerated a whole bunch
That was perfectly normal
Trying to figure out the meaning of the LSP flag yet the LSD that lives matter a whole bunch
I don't know what they mean it would be super cool to find out what they mean
40 40 40 40 50 + 40 + 50 okay let's do that one again
4050 + 40 + 50
By the way disclaimer like not approach this so
There are people who are much better than me but I figured it was fun to try to do this kind of has a community thing so
And then I guess we could look around the other way
That is interesting that the one place indicates that the bit that's on changed or something like that
Little bit actually the 66 doesn't have anymore planned projects on my radar so I don't
There is one big one that's going to be coming out
This project I'm doing with the Vive is specifically related to esp32 project that
If everything goes well and we can get everything that I want hack hacked will be able to do it
No I think I was with 50 and no it's not 82-66
Combo maybe if we can get this all figured out
Daniel can you tell me some more tests to run
By the way in the future if you guys can use the the formatting like 40 or,
50 or 40, 40 that will make it a lot easier for me to type the code to detest what you want to test
Spectacular idea teaching fist first cat or however you pronounce it
I'm going to make it 4044t
And we'll do it three times
That's really interesting
That's a really interesting idea
I like teaching first idea here
Go with it
Let's do it one less and see what that does
Oh wow it even does it oh guys guys look oh my gosh
The number it's it's it's it's big it's a big number is its
27 B permit is sub limitation Hardware right
Cannot be more where the message
Just cannot be over 29 x long and it does have to do with the hardware or 27 because
Cuz there's that the partial header
So
There's that
And then this one also has a really big number
Which is super interesting
That was a really cool testogen cat you have any other ideas
I'm totally up for hearing it
Daniel we 40-48
Wait what
48 flavor 50/50
Okay I guess I'll do that
Sissy
How many people are in the Stream
Okay
Looks like
I don't actually know
Would happen if you exceeded the limit somehow
Activate 57 new orders okay got it
Okay I hear more people out there if you have any ideas come on
We're definitely yeah that is
Is weird what is up with that
Yeah let's let's do Saturday check let's just make sure that the LEDs are still
Directly LED 48
LED 40 LED 50
Thank goodness
Over the limit and see what happens
If you can position your windows so that they can see the real-time DIY with me
Oh this is
Wines are so of what I tried doing that okay
And it won't tell me anything
So I don't know
Well apparently if I try to go over something it would take too many
It just freaks out and stuff so don't know what to make of that
That is interesting but that seems to break it I don't know why
Oh yeah sure let's do that was also undo 2 weeks we go back
The interesting thing
That one that is super interesting there's something about that
Number that is absolute Magic
50 48 48 48 48 5048
What are people saying
Trip suspects that pushing it over Vietnam way it's different from quest number
Daniel he's telling Paul about some of the stuff
Was asking about those two controllers a butt
I wish I could remember where Mandy said
Last time I want to tell you where to get it
Do I need to restart my session let's see what the lag is like
Now it looks like people weren't support quicking wide
Because you can click Lively know my session is actually behind
Yeah like
OIC
Basically
I just clicked it but it didn't seem to do anything
Should I do it
If you guys can like somebody who has restocked the timing see if it's fact
The past
Any other ideas that you guys have ping ping I just finished
Right now
Okay anyway
Yeah okay that's good okay
What else should we be by the way I'm not sure if this is going to change
Somebody like that band that he couldn't get all this data down to a certain size and I think he did
Because this is stupid crazy things
Also Daniel and
Oh gosh I've already forgotten your name you've been so helpful
Ideas for really like to hear them
Suggested looking at the B Flags
That's how it works with the timings
What time does realities from fall
Increase the delay
I think it is time for three LEDs
Let's do 40 84
4050 4848 40
Oh I just got myself confused
These along here
So if you guys didn't just notice eye
I just changed the 2048 47-50 48th and 4840
48 48 48 48 48 this data right here is
It is interesting that it goes 4840
50400 that is interesting something going on where
48 code is saying like I will be on for this long while 40 is on for this one in this way
Long oblong and then that long that is
Cuz I don't make sense 48 is going to be on for about 48 48 million
As
Sir Paul what is your recommendation for code
Where do I get a lot of tests in cuz you guys can check
Tomorrow I'm only going to be doing this tonight I have work to do tomorrow night
Okay we can try that
So play us 10
Oh I see okay I have to
Oh that's interesting though
Oh no nevermind that's dumb
It takes about
What is 120 hertz per fast ones
So it's divided by 4 is 30 Hertz to sweep our room so B12
34 and that operation happens to 30 her think or know 15 Hertz
Daniel can you specify what your
Actually asking for like it whenever you guys want me to try anything be as specific as possible. What you like what
Change
It's not 60 hertz it's closed but it's not 60 hertz it's not 16.66 milliseconds
I have to drop the stream to go back and get I took photodiode collected actual data from the
Lighthouses in loaded up in a logic analyzer so
Josh Moniz something else we can try maybe I'll turn on several
LEDs
So let's try that
Dan 4840 led50
Then that than that
What in the world how what
What
No Shirley
Do they really a slow more like it
Any other suggestions
Do you think he was on the project so you saying it should
It was way off I thought
Part of me wants to go get that file it might drop the stream I will
I'm going to try to get it
Did they drop the screen
Please look at the live
What does it say
Waiting
Stacy
You guys didn't see my password come out did you
Wife beaters flat-screen prescription
Now
So you guys know what I've done here is a diode
Chelsea was this one and this one here was on the White House
One of the things that kind of surprised me with that both lighthouses actually send out a pulse every time whether or not they send
The lighthouse
Postcode sweet sweet sweet
This was 60 hertz
Oh wow I was completely wrong that is almost exactly 60 hertz
I have totally made a fool out of myself
What's look for the beginning flight
Okay it's exactly 60 hertz I don't know what I was looking at before that made me think it was
So I don't know whoever that was who was it that said 60 hertz
Yeah it is
It's pretty accurate
That I don't know what I was looking at but as you can see right here it says 16.66 or 65
6666 MS
Spot-on
So I guess I can close that now
All my CPU
Okay so what else can we test 4840 50
There I don't even understand how the even remotely possible to represent all of this
Data
With this few bits
That's just
Terrifying
It's just completely terrifying
I don't know what black magic been did but
What
Also excited about the sale a I don't own a high-speed silly device I own
Only own two of the chief Chinese knockoffs
I have access to high-speed one and the only reason I have access to it is because I had the cheap Chinese
So if sale a had actually done something to stop people from using the cheap Chinese knockoff
They would not have made the sale so they're all up in arms about people using knockoff they lays and I'm going
Going to say that they really have to stop at if they expect to keep on selling their expensive ones
I guess I can just try a different code like
Maybe forty 4840
This is very strange
Congo down
Oh man I got to reload the chat window it's all janky
Okay well I mean is there anything else you guys can think for me to test right now so like we're doing 48
848 50s
Oh hey did you guys notice that that the huge number just now jumped to
42 instead of 48
And I don't even know what to try anymore this is so crazy
Thing and see what it does
That's interesting
So that one right here
It's as though it's a continuation of data somehow
I don't understand how it can represent that or how we would know for sure unless the time
Codes line up just right
Okay well it's that's neat
Okay well we got to get some ideas here
But what else can we test
I guess I could do this and then change this to
By the way I'm thinking part of the reason I couldn't sleep Saturday night
It was because I was thinking about this and what all of these different fields mean so it's totally killing me like just
Being a puzzle I want to know what the state of mean
Hey a one-day just got set did you guys see it
Oh my gosh hold on I'm going to take this into the into the
This thing
Oh that's so weird for b51 those like the one
Choose B have to do with it handing off while the other one is on when the fits aren't set its
Something else is going on
Back to the previous
Four-wheel not I don't think four will read but we can try it
4 is barely reading
Text should read
Still not quite reading 8
8 reeds
Let's be safe to make a 10
I don't know man
Let's go back to a more degenerate Templar case
Back window
So I want to just do this 40 4840 4850
One other note if you look up here you can see what happens when the pulse codes Leach over into the next frame
I don't think we're losing anything in the packet limit because there was that one packet back a couple wear
Are it on
Where it just went down to the next packet I'll show you
So here check this out
What's going on it's going down to the next packet
14 what does it look like on actual Watchman data
Oh you know what I don't even have any way of collecting the Rawhide data coming from a wired Watchmen
I haven't written that I never did never thought I'd use it
Be too hard to get right now
How do you just make more events and see what happens
5448 5048 5048
Oh that's really clever oh okay so what they're doing if it would be something that would breach pack
The time code
So right here
This is actually just treating it as separate 4850 4850 4850 48
And then this one here is saying 40 was on from here until you know whatever the packet
And was so happy the wrong line
Or I guess I'll be the opposite what really happened is it was this one
No
Yes okay so if you look at this Packer right here the time code started before
This packet so the system was smart enough to know 22 take
The
The 40
Neither was common to all of these and then go stick it after this packet
Even though the event started in this time before this packet again so the things I just don't have to come in in order
It just I guess it's really clever about the wages stores them and sends them on Word
Going to be as hard cuz maybe it does a lot of the really hard
Work
I understand that I don't have
I just don't have any way of decoding it right now
Oh hey benzon here
Hi Ben
And then if if if the factory has has it it be really cool
Let me go let me go commit the current just
I think you can see just how many people are really excited to figure out what this is
The one thing that I want to say is I never I cannot fathom what it took in order
To write something that could look at the light pulses and figure out how to
Put these crazy things together
Other ideas for different.
Maybe this one right here
What
I mean oops and I realized what I did
Apartments
Check that out guys the
The Forbidden set
And that one
Maybe the forest B oh my gosh wait are you guys already talking about this
Before B might be the the B that that that the turn off
When the thing like 49 is 48
In10sity is 50 + 1
Nevermind
Building 44
So
Play let me change the numbers of the timing some so I can make sure that ice I'm seeing what I'm seeing
Yeah I know I'm still lost although hey this does prove that it's Delta's I mean despite the fact
Actually show that it has to be deltas
Orbit here and the fact that it affected something that was all the way to back
Where is the one day I think it only affects one understanding
Turning into 4948 5244
And that would have meant that it was looking to back instead of further back I don't know how to
It's hard to put that into words
Been in chat can you tell us what it's like to have a bunch of people
Call trying to solve a problem that you already know the solution to a puzzle
The puzzle looks like and where all the pieces go and try to figure it out
That's a good point I really should tweet this out
I guess there's no information on my Twitter that you guys can't
Actually you know what I don't have the URL for this life pecan somebody pays to life
YouTube flashlight flashlight
Cnn.com
Saint Laurent / C / 4/5
Reply
Oh are you serious VK Tuesday
I think it's worth
So Ben says it's pretty entertaining
What's the LG Q
Dlco
Okay
Back to work
Okay so let's see here what would I change next to try to tweak that b
Oh hey sex we got a sex again
We got to fix again
Let's take a look at that
Put led50 on for the whole time
Omica
That's sad
Mike can you please tell us what the what the toy was or is are you under NDA to tell us what it is
Oh so you want 50 on okay Sophie
I want to make this 40
Say what
Mike answered you
So if you are interested in seeing the 6th so I guess the sex
How I done goofed something else is that the right one
49-42
Jesse's led50 is on the whole time
That is very strange why
So how does it
What is it doing
You can ask for a brief description of your Hardware software setup
What is 6000
Never heard of this
Sorry I'm right now just looking up something that one of the guys in chat help program
M60 accuse I've never seen these
It looks pretty
Was it like for game
It's pretty neat that they got little displays and he said I got there Wireless
Hey 5000 is that
Did hack your stuff
So I would say special
Micah
Sorry yeah my cat looks like
You're supposed to get back to work
So what did you say okay it's time to show
Okay very briefly hardware and software setup I have a watch
Fan controller here that I have taped on with the
3 LEDs
On different parts of the controller and I have the code setup here so if I save it
Keeps running so I can change which LEDs are on and how and basically real-time
Immediately
And what I've been doing is copying and pasting the output from The Watchmen into the gist thing right there
And as usual
That is my
Girlfriend
So you wrote an article about it
What
I'm not sure which
This the picture here
Oh wait we really got to get back to work I'm sorry
Micah saying the SDK that repo includes the hardware simulator
Ron's emulated binary translated firmware oh so you actually like wrote that code
Survive right now
I'm going to hopefully you get this working more and then we'll have lights or 5 so can actually read all of the lighting Gator from
And hopefully in time we will be able to pass the data off to David Chapman's algorithms
In order to locate the position and run the Kalman filter and all of that to figure out where exactly everything is
I'm a little bit curious if it's really necessary especially because I'm interested in that because
Cuz I noticed when I had the headset on and I could do certain things that looks like it's using an IR to do the correction in the
Headset but but I just want to see what happens if we try to use it
Common filter instead of and I are eventually
Get this Poky Little laptop right here like little second gen I5
Painfully slow to be able to actually run five games all Scott is integrated graphics
Games I mean like a Vive games that I write for it specifically written to be fast and Tiny
We really got to keep moving though we're going to get some more data here to figure out what's going on
I guess one thing I could try this point is we could
Do that
And then f****** I'm curious what happens if
Oh hey guys check that out that day changed
Let's do this one
I'm really got to figure out what's going on with it transfer problem for with the lighthouse
I don't know what's going on there
Can you look at the band hand and see if we can make use of that Brendan
Slippery out there
Its first 12 and 1st
From band
It's
First one to end first
Savannah saying it's quote first one to end first
Post a policy cyborg movie
Do the the least significant didn't know
First one to end first
Oh my gosh what does that mean
Why is it so hard
But
Copy paste the wrong thing
I'm I'm going to go back and look at shortly but
Hi you don't know when it will and you can't report it until it ends
So they come out to me order that net
But I don't know if you saw earlier when we got it stacked up enough that there was one LED
It was on for a long time while we were doing other stuff and she came in and said that like
We're done in the next message down so that the neat idea of the way that you were able to to make that
Like
Walk down to the next one but they come out in the order they end
That says him beginning to end and then it says the date at mediately
Wait a minute does that mean wait a minute does that mean
That could mean that the kind that were receiving is the time code of the end
Not a no-fault we know it's not time to go to the end because if we go back up to that packet that was on the other line
The time code started before the previous
Packets timecode
That was
This one here
S timecode is actually less than the first
And so we know the time code in the packet
Corresponds to
The start
Edge of the
Event not the tailing Edge
Of the event
I hope
Must be painful for you to watch
Just watch her squirm
I can't explain lsb's in terms of his current code
He got to fix the time decode first
No I'm watching my gosh this computer is too slow
Wait no what what
Sahuarita one the year it starts at the end
Put the Stars not at the
Got2b of the start event because I started the LED and then let it play and then it came in later with an earlier start time
Find select the time has got to be the beginning of all of the events right
I'm sad offsets reversed
Yes I can no I can't correlate time
Accurately
When I say event I mean transitions or on or off or anything like that
No we we are I mean I don't know bad if you get a chance to look through the
The copious amounts of tests we run to try to understand what's going on
Also I still don't know what's up with that big number in this test we got here going to go be there
Let's let's keep looking
Are you right now we have been here don't don't go off in the middle of nothing right now
I don't think that we're running into anything like that I think we're a lot closer than r l e
I don't I think that I would have thought that at first but not after
Everything everything we've seen
I'm still having a hard time
Wrapping my head around what Ben said what kind of want some confirmation
Let's look at it
Read it again cuz I am trying to like to alt-tab between everybody all this much
You can report it till it on I don't know when it will end right that's why
Yeah there are two end-to-end
We did know that all that was from yesterday so we come in the order
At the end of think about the LEDs
So I've been riding them in the order from this way this way that way
50 riding on that way instead
So I'm reading
Can you guys think of a test that I can caulk where I would turn on One LED and then turn on and
Different LED and then turn off that led on a different one in order to determine if
Like which order they're actually in if somebody can like write the syntax again for
Saudi I guess we should be able to tell that should be
Temple should be
Can you check the chat Brandon
44-year 4844 Lucas
40 40 40 Lucas if you can just type in the time chat if this is what you were wanting me to test
48 / 84
4040 + 40
Wait
Do Marker
Daniel Lee
Just warning you Daniel this is going to overlap if I do it there's going to be no way of actually knowing
Oh I see what you're saying
She's been like that
Okay Daniel Lee I just added your stuff
To the baguette
There is a correlation between LED 40 + 10 + 6
Therapy
I don't see it
He must be looking at a different dataset other will be
Correlations between LEDs and certain numbers though because the timing will be consistent among those LEDs
Does anybody have any idea what could have meant when he said I needed to fix my timing code because I just don't know
I mean the same as what's what's up there
Okay I'll try 40 + 48
Oh no overlap Oso
Okay so what's going on right here I'm
I'm also seeing a massive number right there
Like I have no idea where that came from
Like seriously what is up with this why is there 283,000
Showing up right there I mean I guess I could just
Can you go back and start looking again
Also I think he means that the timings
Correlated sink 1 trillion with utilities oe mean I really could be looking at the LEDs
In Arduino if it's reverse order yet
But enough of the first led you read it was not necessarily the first.
No no no no no John we we want this to be all in good fun we're trying to do something fun with
Hardware
On that possible tie what do you what do you recommend
You guys like using that or Note 8
Station
Don't ask the chat what is 2 to the 1818 is 26
50144 right pulling out of thin air
Maybe
I certainly don't know to the 19
If you can make a recommendation for what code you would have checking
We're getting we're getting close to the to the cutoff sign here
What is what is the next 10 min
Set 10
George II just don't know
Don't know what you're after
Oh are you serious
Wait a minute who is the one who asked what's 2 to the 18
Is that one of the other valves that I missed the name
Is he one of the other valve think he was ya know why did I have to poop
I'm sorry
I still don't understand, what do you want me to test you want to do this twice
Like that
Oh that's
Weird
I did not what
I don't
Why is this that output
This is crazy
In the world
Why is
More suggestions
Is the fundamental time because wrong he also asks that maybe
I mean I just said it to the 14th so let me go back
For they to dk20 there is
Earlier on I don't know if you were here when but at the time
That number's up 255 35 so the fact that it's more than 50 55-35 means
Yes I know that there's Flags there but I've no idea what O2 the 18
A bit too which is a bit that matters for us
So the two-bit could be in the LED code or it could be in the time code if shifted
Like timecode pushed up
16 deaths I think
Yeah
That's interesting
So
That live around for quite some time when Charles did not realize the important question
That was being asked
Hold on
Ben
I am I would not be surprised if what you've done here compresses the data
Better than any normal compression algorithm that one would typically be a
Able to use like this is some very clever stuff to minimize the number of fights that are being transfer
I do wish I was a little bit sharper right now I'm definitely getting tired
So then we had just discussed that
Who says getting there I'm guessing he was referring to me when he went
The whole thing about 2 to the 18
Tapping into the twos bit of
Or whatever it is
Instead of
The to spit of
The LED code
So what did I miss
The time between one set of 3xd of marker and the next is too short
Combine two covid-19
Yeah or a bit in like
And it's only going to take it's going to take
Talking to you like a lot and you don't have to store another by telling you that it's up there
I hope a bunch of these folks are like really thinking this one through like Paul and
And everyone else cuz
We're totally going to have to dig this went through cuz my brain is pretty fried at the moment
So let's see what conditions can we put it under in which case the two will appear in there
Instead of in there for the to spit for whatever
If I don't do that
Maps 40-48 with the Tuesday stuffed there
And I bet you if we flip the order of those then it'll appear in the other one
48 48 48
No it didn't
A great what does that mean
Oh and about the whole timing thing like which ones happens first
How much if I leave this one on set that 2:40 then it'll appear in there yet did okay
Why is the two-bit set now
Well I must put up with me like tattoos b means these two
Things have nothing to do with each other and that it's not actually carry over from
Okay let's wait a minute no nevermind yeah yeah
What's going on here guys do Marker 1048 + 250
So 250 corresponds to led40 here even though it happens
S sequentially in time so it's like backwards from from the order that you expected
So what in the world does that one did in the Dare do why does that happen
Cuz like look guys this going to copy this over there you guys are probably
Anyway so
But that's like super interesting
Why is the order reversed
Okay going up some
By ticking Fritz the Cat
I'm just reading what everybody saying I haven't got a chance to do that in a bit
What
You can't go why
Albert thing would that do Marker LED at4050 I mean we can do that
ATR 40 and 50 are going to come on at I'm not going to
And off cuz like there is a slight like
Like the way but I don't know what it is
By Paul thank you for joining please look at it tomorrow please please please that would be super cool
Call cuz I'm pretty sure I'm not going to figure out what's going based on all of this
The basics
Sequences misinterpreted the order that I'm reading in or what cuz I'm pretty sure that I'm not misinterpreting it because
If I end up with extra bites or anything like that that I print out a warning and so far I haven't seen any
The warnings
So that's the other thing
When I the whole reverse thing Paul if you can just stick around for a second
I do want to show you why I think that that's not the case if I do LED 40
LED 50
LED 48 and LED 40
And I do 20 30 40 50
Keep that then I guess 4050 4840 4050 4840
So I don't think that they're reversed I think they're in the correct order
Does not what was his name is saying but it doesn't
The negative one at the very end placeholder I put in it's not in the package is not there
It's just a thing I stuck in
El William if you want we can work together
But to be fair I do kind of want to work on mine
Who knows we can just eat work on our our own and then just share the knowledge
At any rate is I was saying I'm pretty sure that the order is correct cuz like 40
Is first 50 is second
48/3
+ 40 is
The last one and they also go up to the time here goes up
And feel like in the degenerate case it's clear that it's 40 on 4309 off 430 150 on 45
25 off for 2948 on 4691 and then offered 3:15 and 4
40 on 4 873
On and then it turns off cuz it's the end of the packet
You catch the B right sequence wrong
No
B what
Why is the negative one at the very end for example
Oh no the negative one is is the mawp I think I said
Your order only comes from the first few bites were talking about the rest of the day. He says
Diid use various plotting programs when it makes sense to but right now
I mean like when I come feel like moving the thing around I'm totally going to do it but right now we're just trying to figure out what the Rob B R
William let's go take a look at your code
EBenefits
I'm your sequence of numbers applies the first few bites but the assignment
The timestamps might be wrong
I'm taking notes for myself so I can read these tomorrow
I don't know standstill here if he is is it okay if I like actually post the text of everything he said
Along with the thing
You guys want to like work on something and then like link
Something that would be cool to like and
I need a thing of water I'm going to just do a quick commercial break
What what really
I can't click
What
Extreme is totally live
Bummer I just don't have access to that button
Well you guys are going to have to just sit there without a commercial break or anyting
I'm going to leave it there
What what is
Just in general
I still don't have an ad button now
Oh well I don't know why that is
That's okay
I feel really bad because I feel like I can get into the Zone more when I when I'm the one who's working in focus
Based on the problem but when I'm like kind of
Hurting everybody I can't really get into the zone so I feel almost a little embarrassed
So dull right now but
I guess that's just how it is
I think you guys are having more fun with it this way and I'm having fun too and as long as the problem gets solved
I guess I'll be happy
Hi Paul
McDaniel
I don't know
Videos
Creative Commons ads from the 50s
Talk about it that's pressive
By the way you guys should totally
Brandon said talk about expressive so it's going to totally do
Two people from the comments
Expressive
They have like
Animation
This guy
They're this thing he totally made an ad
Look at that add
Look at it just all cool and look who was Francis
Okay back to work
Does anyone have any ideas right now
Look at the Twitter pic
Did you
Notification me
Wait Alan Yates
Oh yeah
Alright
I'm getting so distracted
Follow there it is
Tk20se
How is that Allen
Bk2 Z28
So Tuesday is not really on you but he send me a picture
He tweeted picture
Maybe to send your Twitter mentions
See
I'll see a picture though
Oh
Oh now I see it
Call yok
Puzzles are getting so ridiculous
Oh well you know what let's see what that looks like
I'm going to save this picture
Oh my gosh okay I can't wait to see what then I'll put
Turns into
Kemal
Hey hi, thank you for using is all good
Okay
Time for us to go see
That picture actually does for us so I'm going to take that picture I'm going to go
I'll put it into code in Cisco dled
20 Led Led 50 or 40
LED 50 boom there than LED
50 or LED 48
And then LED
50 Min nothing sets first transition off
Second transition of first transition down
Second transition
S transition down transition down
Okay so this coach should be
Are you guys seeing this
Cuz I'm really confused now
Transition one
Nothing
53 is it
Going
Want o
The one needs is associated with the first
4848 only on 4
For a little bit does not associate with any other events
NY 53
No I want to figure it out here cuz I think the 53
The one means it's one the event is one away from where I am and then the three would mean that
123 away that's one event
2 event back 3 event back
And it's an implicit one so it's the amount that it changes so
Well let me at least copy this since the text file and then
Okay you're right. It does make a little bit easier cuz you can clearly see like 867
The 151
That's such a good test but it's
I don't have enough brain cells still firing to figure out exactly how to decode that but the 41 means it's 40
Forward them out
And then
Oh me so it's 40 then 151 later
Now the B20 so
Where in the world why the 552 there the 48
Okay so that's on but then the one
Which Delta a different prime number for testing
Yes but we're getting there
Everytime You groan like that
Pittsboro Matt's dog looks around and groans back
Somebody just read me the thing about everytime I groan this dramatic dog groans
By the way you guys do kind of have a bad voice synthesizer playing back everything cuz
A phases here reading things that matter
Okay fine what I really should be doing right now is like
The numbers round to approximate numerical values that match up with
Please tell
So I think that would be
Better use of my time Lego speed this up some and then it'll lineup better
Okay so what I did hear just you guys can say is I modified the oscillator clock on the
Maybe our one of these is approximately 10 times the total number 48 millions of a sec
I can fit these are representing so 12
8 that way not a 125 7-Eleven is that
The next prime I guess
Okay
What why why is there a why did the Jews bit just turn on and
To the d-18 thing
What's what is that doing there
Polyps
Go back to
Okay
Oh bother with that
Average iq
Never seen that one
Back to work
I'm going
Adam Gary just got back and asked how it's going and I'm sighing heavily
I have no idea why there's a to like
What is that doing there
Why did it switch from 41 4853 to the codes
With
With that
Maybe it's a different ways in which they can index the
Oh my gosh
I do appreciate that you're trying to reverse-engineer it
I mean you never know if
If if
If if Ben is not feeling particularly
Charitable and
I'm in we can't get it then we might have to resort to it
Oh I don't want Ben to tell us if he plans to tell us eventually if we don't get it
So weird
Following is in reference to
Iran Twitter
Just for the sake of having this as a
Do I have permission to post the the text file that you provided like you're not you
Provide a bit like these tidbits of conversation in the in the
Just that I'm going to be having cuz I don't remember all of this
Oh
Wait a minute then are you telling me that you
But you did the compression in the fpga
Cuz
That's
That's insane
I am okay with using fpgas is glorified shift registers and capture compare but
Really
What
Oh that band that makes it sense with the
Why be reverse-engineered also quickly because when I plug it in to the USB it gives didn't
Simple format where is why I have it on Eric is it in the Ludacris
Allocated format
Can I ask you guys something right now and I hope you'll tell me this
Is everything we're doing right now all going to be for not because you're going to drop some firmware update in that's going
I completely lock us out
Statement there scares me
Decoding that number in
Incorrectly anything
SP2 coating that number incorrectly
No0 f49 F4
Siam to coating that according to the rules
It's very strange. That doesn't line up to anything
Well we're not going to try to lock you out
But we're going to add features someday that will break this without caring that it will break you
So glad you guys care the good news
I only need this to work for my project for a little while three months
Moved on and working on a different thing then
Everybody else who wants to use this though they're going to be very sad
But I don't need to do my wireless protocol I I have my own I'm going to be
The same as I've been doing on like the 3D localization video and a bunch of other other things being able to
Faster sampling rate
Oh different Harbor okay yeah sure I get that fine you're going to change that because the different Hardware I'm I am
A okay with that if somebody else wants to use their Vibe with my system they're going to have to go do this reverse engineering
Themself
I don't really want to go too much into what my particular project is for them but it's
A whole lot of steps to get somewhere that's not actually that cool but I think it's going to be much more the adventure
Aaron trying to get where I want to be we really need to figure this out guys like
This thing here what is up with these B why is this particular field so high
Like what is going on there
But I just checked and yeah like yeah actually decoding that right
I think
Yeah I guess I can put into calcaneal say
Yeah I'm decoding it according to the rules Corral
Broccoli looks like
Yeah I really like that idea of having the extra I love you not saying how many parameters there are
But knowing how many there are based off of the field that is
That's pretty cool
Anyway
Guys do we have any idea when I moved from 70 microseconds to 80
Not microseconds 80 time units
I just realized something dumb I think I'm sending this thing out at 4 MHz
Not 1.8 whatever
Note MP4 MHz caviar is running too slow
The number is right here but the problem is that the number is
Call kind of stacks together
And there's like no good split at the 16th Mark or anything like that
Like if I do - 262144 as what's-his-name suggest
My gosh is a negative number
Why did I not think to try that
Oh my gosh
Okay let's do that now what
Found something new
You could have negative time Delta's
That is weird
Although that number doesn't make any sense
That number is way too big so big
I can't be the right number
Cuz that would be too big
Pat V
Boop
Took that long has toothless 3 or 10
38 + 50 +
I know it's not 10:00
* 10
Yeah that's way too big
Nevermind
What is the significance of it being negative
My delay between batches is a very long time
And how is it
Compass not negative
Okay well so like look if I don't do negative here
That this number right here like I look at it I have ones and zeroes like
Pretty evenly strewn all throughout the number I can really think of is maybe it's like
I don't even know a complete mess of ones and zeros there's no
Not to look here
But I don't get it otherwise it's a messed up of ones and
Gyros
I'll look up what the delay between the two packages
It 10 ms between packets
I already did figure out it if you
Trip if you want go look at the gist I have at the bottom of the just one packet where it doesn't update and one pack at work does
Does trigger
Jeremy
That again
I I did see that
But I still don't understand how to be a positive number unless it's like the actual time shifted over
Oh that's exact number
All your following we will be
If you want to know more precisely
Somewhere here
You called Arcane pop and honor of been calling this type of compression Arcane compress
I can survive underscore data. See
Oh yeah bad whenever you get back or if his back now already it was 10
Ms between packets
Yeah it's not normal but I don't think it matters does it mean I guess we can test that will test it how about that
So now it's 26 some big number I don't even know
Let's go increase it to 11 MS
Oh it is why does that matter
Why does that number change based on the can light
Difference what do you know that I don't trip what do you know that I don't
Why
Hahaha
No
Oh yeah you're right it probably isn't
11 milliseconds
Why
No it is getting a little bit of a DVR clock is totally it's not
I don't really know what it is I didn't even bother thinking about it but as he pointed out we can't calculate it now
It would be
He says
280,000 actually would be better for me to use the other number since it rounds to 10 nicely
How did he recommend of-40 86
Five Point
Why is the AVR clock higher
I thought the Aviary was clocked lower
Help oh well I guess DVR clock Tire it is actually operating it like that other frequency the 44
MHz inside the 1.8 I don't know whenever
Enable the PLL
No
I never able to PLL it shouldn't be that high
That's totally wrong though so whatever I was going to comment that out delete it
Okay so
A 5.3 mean 5.8 Ms Right
Let's pretend
So if you want to divide that by
Yay yay come out it's not about
Santa's enjoying all the controllers acting is logic analyzer for finding bugs and reverse engineering
Kevin called it
That is true
I really wish you guys all the people who are watching right now had
Had one of these to play around at home with
By the way you guys have Vibes and you're not doing this right now
I just said it to like the 16 Ms time why is this
It shouldn't just be giving up eventually
15.4 okay fine I'll go a little bit longer
What is the point in having something only
Why
What's 17 Ms why are you still holding onto the data
Like
Why
Georgia Sally Mac Westport
George are you adding it's alive vibralife survive
Okay that's cool thank you George
Specifically David Chapman the guy who's doing the other work on this has a lot of interest in doing okay
Opengl windows and see until like he has a solution right now but
I'm printing a good weight if you can send me a personal message with your email so I can hook you up
You up with David Chapman I think that would work out really good cuz he's a dad who likes using OS X
Dakota around line 57 and isn't correct
So different from real data that you're seeing strangeness but the finger decoding
I didn't even think to look at that
Pretty much too tired now though to make any changes that would be significant
No I know your coding is representing reality because like it's a linear transform in
Somehow the Aviary just clocked that high like I get it there is a famous quote which is
99.9% of all Aviary uark problems are actually clocking problems
And Akai the other thing is once the system once I can handle the
Data from this I'm totally going to just go fire up the lighthouses and see if I get David at 3
Go back cuz I do have the the main headset dealing with the data on that way
Make text Jay would probably explode mychelle why would it explode my shell
Oh okay
Don't even know what to check anymore
I don't even know what the change like at this point I'm so lost this going to take
Thinking and looking at numbers and it's already 12:12 which is getting really close to my stop time
Oh haha you were going to have somebody copy and paste the backslash make Dash J
Yeah that would explode
Do I have any man though
I don't see anything
Do you say line 357
And I wish I had thought about this earlier we could have had like an official recorder somebody who is
Is actually like tasked with like taking notes
Turn around her what was the thing somebody said got it where is the other it is
PK Tuesday which I've already forgotten his actual name I don't know how I forgotten cuz I slept up in
Twitter Alan Yates
Alan Gates
Oh my gosh if I can get people playing with live survive I would love to have some extra eyes on that
Had to really get that fleshed out so I don't have to deal with all of the stupid bugs in it myself
I really don't even know what to change to do this right this thing parameter is par place to Delta
No I know it's wrong now but I'm still trying to figure out what the the correct thing is
So like this here
I'll actually know what I can do we can use the prime thing again
Do whatever that limit is will you just now found out we can flirt with it I don't know if you guys care
I think it's a little weird that it's
Watering
Maybe I'll just copy that just in case
How you're having problems with Watchman command codes
No I have a day job
I just spend a great deal of time making my projects in working on making YouTube
Videos nobody could be a professional the YouTuber 20K Subs would take like
I know it easily take 500,000 Subs before you could really make it a professional job
Unknown Watchman code 32
Oh that's really weird
Tudu tudu tudu I'm going to close the Stream
But look at these values and try to
To figure out what's wrong with the Delta a Delta
Beko din
Survive
Data. See
Does anybody have any further notes that
Yeah I do have a patreon if you guys do on a straight-up do at the patrons more for individual projects though
I'm so something like this would not fit into the patreon
So let's just say we're going to stop like actual Deming for tonight I taken all the
What date I'm going to take
I'm going to commit what I have here
Okay any other notes that
Yeah I know it looks like to field mashed together but we are pretty sure that it is the amount of time between the two frame
Games
So no actually that was covered a little bit earlier Ryan the the the numbers that
There are reflecting reality in that regard I'm a pretty sure that's what they had indicated in when I change
Change the delay between the the packets or whatever ignifica Nelly
Really is that like a 17 milliseconds or whatever between sending the
The messages
I hope I've gotten at least a couple other people interested maybe
Maybe some of you guys are going to go download live survive on Lenox Heroes X and
Push push
Support
I've stuff and once this is solved I'll start doing more development on the side that I need to in order to get to the price
Trying to get to
Anything else before we go anything you guys can think of it you really want to see I like some combination of
Have lights on and off or anything like that
I really don't want to get into the final goal
It is
It is really lost Ian I don't really want to find out for something I don't think I'm going to be able to succeed
Yeah
For some sort of specific reason having to do with
I'd be willing to talk it over with with specifically developed as offline. What I'm trying to do
But
I don't want my
Gold two
Really want to dig into that.
I have used in the past but it would take the device
Filter
So that you could talk to all the 5 pieces of hardware
We could probably mess up the drivers for use with the valve stuff
And so it would be complete pain you have to keep going back and forth and back and forth and back and forth I'm disabling all the
All the drivers re-enabling them so that you can use your your Vive with steam
Instead of Life survive
Direct message on
Open fire
You can direct message people on Twitter
I didn't know that
Message