See I wonder if this is online
There it is
See does it show number of people yet is anybody in chat
Anybody anybody in chat
Are we live or we
Still hittin
Screen is continuing
Some reasons picking up
Elhae somebody's in chat
Do the cat reattached you have to click the fly out again oh really
Yeah
Welcome. We just disconnected OBS disconnected
Okay there we go okay okay I think it's online
Now do you guys I have a shrink that window so we can get to the editor
Get to attract ice are we online now
Okay
Get to the editor the chat window like maybe just leave it up over there something
Nadia
That's weird weird setup here I've got basically figure it out
Yeah
Cast want to cover your screen thing
I don't know how many people are viewing can we see that on the other window Maybe
Cracked ice discount
Ohio case we got a couple people online where does it usually say that
That corner Maybe
To make any sense
Clearly we have at least three
Let It Go Let It Go
Okay I guess we'll probably start for realsies eowyn in five
5 minutes maybe 2 or 3 minutes
Now we might as well amused by pointing out our Strange set up here
You can pick up the camera look around
We are at a cabin in the woods in Virginia don't know if you can
Over there
But it's just like
An A-frame cabin
Mindy's with us
Random people on the internet
Yes we've got my desktop here
Which is hooked up to the Internet through my cell phone to somewhere under the television and providing internet
Charles is laptop
And then Charles's laptop is VNC my desktop is via and Seed into Charles
His laptop and then my desk is doing the broadcasting and controlling the chat
Chat while Charles his laptop has been theoretically made free to do whatever the heck Charles is going to be doing
How do i chat in my own live stream
Oh hey
Oh you can totally read it in okay let's see make sure you can read the others
About to get too eager at 123 what is
Hell you guys okay with these levels
Yeah that's definitely convenient that way I don't have to keep the chat open there
Let's see here so yeah we're streaming live
From the middle of a cabin in weight from a cabin in the middle of nowhere Stanardsville Virginia
The closest store is like 30 minutes away
Down and unpaved horrible Road and yet somehow there is still enough
Average cell coverage to stream here
So how many people are in I can't you can reverse these so that you can see that then
Can you cut off most of the the video thing
Oh okay
No see that's not going to
Oh I see what you're getting at you just want to see
Yes
But I'll bet you can't off Dragon Windows what does that even mean
Turn the window and then drag it beyond the top of the screen so like only a little ribbon oven
That works
Hi Mom are you guys just to see you know Mary Laura's my mom and
And she is invited her to watch this live stream
Should I stop should sleep sleep I'll watch the
Aerie my mom is watching watching the stream right now and just everybody and chat if you want to say
Say hi I Charles's Mom you can do that
My mom just you know it's only it's only nine or ten people seven people right now watching so
It's not a very big stream tonight
Yet
Okay
And let us know if it's getting nasty or audios cutting out to
We're not entirely sure how well this is going to hold up for long
Being a cell phone connection at all
Also the other thing
I forgot was going to say now
I won't words
I can take anywhere since I want to be there going to be useful
That's interesting I wonder if because I've been streaming so much YouTube doesn't advertise it
What do you mean
Like it's less of a novelty no
Oh yeah you guys were here how did you how did you notice that the started did you like
Did you get a message on your phone that CN Laura was broadcasting or did you just see it kind of pop up on your YouTube
Feed curious how people find their way here the last
Tee times we had between like 40 and 90 people and people are just like us
Pop-up button for tweeting
Is YouTube homepage so
Another HTC Vive live stream
This time
Trying to determine lighthouse
Location
Okay
I just tweeted out
Ohio George
Is it early enough that you're going to able to stick around till about probably 12
45 I guess isn't we're going to stop today
The Texaco originally in the tax section YouTube cool
I take it by you being here right now it's
I don't remember you were in like the second one right
Cold
Anyway I guess we should
Mouse
It's fine acceptable
Gorgeous OK Google stream is finally set up pretty well now
I guess I can start
Okay so this is okay
Restart from here when we do the playback error the edit it and then this is where it'll actually start
Now I'm not going to clock it
So if you guys are paying attention we had some
Some fun with the dhtc Vibes Watchman controllers in the last two live streams
Trying to decode the data but this livestream isn't going to be about the coding data since it's already pretty much clear
Text what we're going to try to do is determine and I don't think this is actually going to all happen one
I think we can get a long way into it we're trying to determine the location of those lighthouses
Relative to this headset so I'm going to do is I'm going to put this on the floor and we're going to collect some data
From the lighthouses and we're going to see is it possible to figure out where they are
And that really matters that's the first step to doing all of this actual localization stuff as soon as you can come
Calibrate the locations of the lighthouses it becomes really not that hard to just do the rest of
The solution to figure out where objects are going around inside the main room now we're still a couple steps away from that
Not even when we have this it's going to be a while
But this is a pretty big step so through a lot of this I'm going to
What I'm going to be doing it actually Andrew Andrews my brother he's getting a PhD in math
Collecting data and I'm going to be giving it out
Two to the link in the description it's going to be on GitHub under life survive under issues we use
Adjust before but that was a bad idea what we really want to do is we want to have it in an issue and that way
Track for forever the movie taking the data and then I'm going to be putting it there and you guys can have
Pack alongside trying to do solve this problem and chances are you're going to find a better solution than I
So going back to my brother Andrew is getting a PhD in mathematics from Rutgers University so maybe I can get
Even temp take some of this data and try to give it a crack
The Arctic
Where in the Arctic are you Frank big
Also can one of you guys find paper and a Sharpie for me
I got Sharpie I think there's paper in that side room
Good paper not sad paper so this is going to be a little bit more
Making heavy and math heavy than it is going to be active reverse-engineering so the first two streams were much more like doing
What is this do this is going to be much more trying to collect the data that we need and then trying
Analyze it thank you Mindy North Norway
Hey we have somebody from North Norway it is what time is it there
Perfect will you be able to see this if I hold it can you hit that light on or something
You can put it on the box and then I would light up
Then you can take the top off the light
Take the top off
Oh hey perfect you'll be able to see the sheet of paper
Annoying at the whole time we'll just have it on for whenever whenever
We actually use it I guess you guys can see that color binary counter
And are you going to be up for for doing some analysis here
Our first batch of data like yes if we can figure out how to get today to write maybe in as little as an hour or something
We might be able to get the data cuz I I did when I first did to the hacking of Life survive stuff
Was just more less implementing some of the stuff that the guy over at near all over
Over at Lighthouse redox
What he was able to determine the document so pretty much getting pretty close on that one
By the way
And so I do regret that unless you guys understand trigonometry this is probably not going to be
All that easy to really dig into but
I don't really think it's going to be that much harder than than basic trigonometry
How would I link this to someone link youtube.com live
Okay so let's go a little bit into what we have here
So is part of a little bit here sorry about that
Actually series motor mount
Better okay
So
I have a file here survive data. See and this is what actually gets all of the
The data from all of the different devices
And and I say devices I need anything between these guys the controllers and the
How to display and all of that so
That's what we're going with right now and this thing when it receives the data it then passes it up to the next
Level so the very lowest level right now which we're going to be changing a little bit later but right now it's called survive
Add USB and this handles talking to the USB bus to get the data
From the actual devices at the lowest level
Survive data then processes that date of the raw B the 10 or I guess hexadecimal
The octet the date of that is coming from these devices is process it into something higher level and then survive
My process is what takes that process data and actually does something useful with it so right now inside
Side of survive light processing if you guys want you can go check out this on GitHub is it get hub.com
1/10 lore / live survive live survive if we found out a lot of things
We'll call it last time
At least I'm not calling it the veve right here is
Survive underscore process.com
And everything that we're going to be doing today I think is going to be coming in through survive light
Process
And so we have survived object which is a head-mounted display or a Watchman or I don't know I mean
Maybe there's actual light date it'll come from lighthouses I I don't know if there is or isn't a which sensor was hit
A code associated with that sensor
The time in the sweep and the time code so all of this is already decoded a little bit for us
We say time and sweep and timecode what happens is the there's the the lighthouse
House
And
Maybe so what we actually
Can you give me a how do I can't stay
Okay so what we actually have is we have a lighthouse and the lighthouse takes a sweep
A plane of light and sweet sit across the scene
And it does this by having laser scanner that are spinning around and around and around
I need one of those things around at almost exactly 4448 millionths of a
The 2nd which is about 120 hertz
And
What this code here does the tell the difference between a light flash that happens
And when it actually sweeps past I think
I don't know I haven't actually gotten updated to find out if I did that right but I will go get
Give us a shot and we'll see where we end up
Right now inside the code on all I'm doing for survive light process
If I'm just printing out l meaning it's a light
String which is the code name of the device ohmd or are what I call them
HED HED is the head mouth display a timecode and this is in 48
Millionths of a second so you can see it's a very large number see what it is it right now
So it's Counting
Or whatever it's counting down its assigned number so it'll go positive negative positive negative
But it is counting down right now we can see that it's got a light ID associate
Do with it which is actually a sensor ID on the head-mounted display and that's jumping between all sorts of
Different value so between light zero like 15 sorry sensor zero sensor 15
And it gives the length of the Nepal
The deposit code to let's go little bit into what that data looks like
The data here done by the lighthouse redox group omigosh it's amazing that they were able to figure this out
But what happens is at the beginning of of of a frame so to speak
She's actually won 120
If as the lighthouse actually flashes a pulse of data
And it's of a different lengths of time and so
What we actually have here is a chart of
Skip's and rotors and data and in all of that and it's the time is in text
Or hundred
40 million to the second
And the amount of time it was actually on so all of these Lighthouse displays going poop
And then scanning the laser scanning the other laser and then this Lighthouse over here is doing the exact
Same thing and that's how it how we can get both get data from the lighthouses and no
Know which sweep to expect so inside here inside this data we can see the flash from one light
Lighthouse
Which is right here she knows it says code 10 but that case we don't get the flash numbers we get
What was the code received from Eric saying is Spencer for received
Laser sweep
And the length of the flash associated with that laser tweet was 10
Units I'm going to have to go fix that so it it lines up with the way the lighthouse Reef
Redox folks documented it
But that's not going to be very hard so let's
I guess that's a good place to start so instead of having the numbers be like 8 9 10 8 9 10 76
It's whatever
We should probably make them something a little bit more same
And I think that would mean all that was really mean to starting at zero instead of something really high
Yeah sorry I'm going to have to
Just keep going in August maybe about 20 minutes and we'll we'll do a recap of everything
So I'm going to do is I'm going to look for survive life process in here to see what I'm actually doing with this
Stata
Sucks you have a pulse if it's longer than 18 microseconds then do this
GLE
So total photo time
Find my total photos oh that's another thing I forgot to mention in order to get a really accurate length of time for
For that pulse code but I'm actually doing this I'm averaging all of the lights are all the sensors that see that postcode imav
Averaging that length of light amongst all of them so that if it's like
We can get at the actual length of time and we can average
To figure out where the time that that pulse actually started exactly so depending on the brain
Brightness be single start triggering a little bit earlier or later but what I'm going to do an average that between all of them to find out
Where did it really start now I think about it that's probably a terrible way to do it I'll probably be looking for the first Edge
But I don't know we'll see how this all goes just some ideas thrown out there and this is Steve-O
Where we end up asking why you don't program and C plus plus
Discussion okay well I will be very brief with this what
Well I mean do I want to send him the yoop is terrible video or do I want to
Specifically in this particular case we're coating this project and see to minimize
External dependencies and really get explosive Hardware as possible there is a long-term project I'm gone
Going to be trying to do here don't really want to get into what it is on but it would require the code be very
Very lean and I seriously do that and see and it's much harder to do that if we plus-plus
At any rate let's let's go do this now so I'll set time
A code a code - equals 6 + 58
Cochiti between 0 and 7 now
7412 54105
Okay are a code this column right here now looks like they might actually be lining up to the
The lighthouse people
No this is not this is not for the the hackaday 1 KB challenge
Actually I'm checking out of that not doing it because someone has already somebody has effectively won the
Add hacked A1 KB challenge if you haven't seen it
Iowan TV challenge with the one
If my computer loads it at all
There is there's already been a submission that I'm sure there are other people who can beat this
Submission but I can't in so I'm just I'll keep supporting and whatever way but that's way out of my
My way out of my league somebody made an entire operating system that fits in one kill
KB and it's it's pretty functional
Bi was actually very crazy functional
The
Okay OS
Somebody made actual operating system with a text editor and it can compile programs assembly
Programs and it can save files like a compiled to file and you can run the program
And it works and it has like a font in the display and everything so these folks
Yeah I'm not going to try to compete against that backpack to the
So we have L meaningful light we have had meaning it's to the Head mouth display
We have this year which is a timecode in absolute terms of when the The Sweep actually
Hit the light and I think that's actually what we have I don't know whether it's like Leading Edge your trailing Edge
We're getting from the address for Lighthouse data
The code
Which is able you can look that up right here on the lighthouse redox and the
The the time within that sweet that that could happen
So I guess one thing we can start with here
Just so you guys can get a feeling for how amazing this Lighthouse beta is what I'm going to do
I do
Is
Going to put a prefix in front so we can actually like identify it
Crapsey 40K
So what I have is I'm looking at a specific piece of data during a sweet and
And so I'm going to move the the the headset display
And you can see Elias that's vertical
And you can see just a little bit of motion
How different the data can be
So just by moving a few inches
Even with the lighthouse all the way over there
That can add up incredibly like just the date is very very stable and even just a little bit of
Motion gives you very high fidelity it's the what's going on that's one of the reasons I believe that this is just
The future because instead of a camera or you get like a certain number of pixels by certain number of pixels pixels of act
This thing can tell you to Within
360 / 48 / 124
Aoo 0.08 locate it's about 0
0.001 degrees of angle so if you treat like the
Lighthouse like a clock
Add a sweeping that light around it can tell you where that light hit that that the sensor
2 resolution
Of 0.00
1 degrees now it's not accuracy of 0.001 degrees it's a little bit less accurate
But it's still unbelievably good versus something like a camera solution which
That is what a curious uses right really funny camera at you and you track
It totally works that way
Better
So I'm guessing you guys may want to get your hands on some of the state of right
Although you won't be able to do that much with it other than create some pretty pictures I guess that's
I'll do first is I'll take some data for you guys
And then you can at least take a look at it and I remove the sea
So that it doesn't get in the way there
And initial hmd data.
Txt
Nope not yet
Do you guys want spaces or commas
Like
Like it with your data like if you were going to analyze stuff
Do you want to
Like Analyze That using spaces between the data or commas between the data like everybody's religious about
About this but I don't really care
So what you guys tell me if you want spaces are commas I'll go take a log file for y'all
Either or
Pick one and go
Subway Surfers
Camas Mindy suggest
Have no we're not doing tab
Okay
SSV o space
But I can do that part for you if you want okay well
That's probably enough data to be your assistant
Let's see how much data that is 765 KB in data
Look at all that data
Okay I see how we need to do is we need to
Delete this last line right here
Okay I'm not a zip this up
76% compression
You can't quite a cheap Benz level of compression for those of you
Hi to miss the last livestream the compression that's done on the data from these things 1
MB of data spent sent in 12 seconds that 1 MB if I compress it with gzip which is a really
Leaving compression algorithm it goes to 96 GB
The stream that been the guy who wrote this his algorithm
It gets it to 69kg be so he's able to compress better than when you believe is the best
It's amazing because he cheats
Okay so I'm going to go upload this right now so you guys can get a better
Do you think I don't know
Rico Rico can you explain if you're being legitimate with the commas compress better cuz I've never
Heard of that might be true
How do I upload a file to GitHub an issue
Boy how does that work
Oh you know it
Attach files by dragging and dropping
Initial hmd.
Something.
C4 versions of the chat here he's really weird
Compresses 2182 KB show us being on the cell phone connections we are that's okay
Does you guys missed it the reason I'm doing this project is because I ran out of data on my cell phone why didn't completely run
Would like
I was using a ton of data
Trying to get all the dependencies for the open
Guests open Notes VR stuff for the the Vive ridiculous existing
So
This is some initial data
Yes
Columns are
Charles has to talk out loud while he types otherwise I can't type it makes working in a professional environment
Very strange
L head
And then we're going to do
Actual
Time
No
Of a second
,
Sensor ID
Pulse
Code
,
Delta from frames start
Okay guys if you guys want to go get that and download it and start poking around and read it into your favorite viewers
Now is the time to do it
So what did he say Taps depressed most Dragon dropping upload was it supposed to say
Did he ever tell us why commas compress better
I did not say
Oh he says spaces compress better
So if I don't do, and Stacy is correct
If it's just a sore just, but I did, and a space so
Actually your your period is more than
One pixel on our screen yeah we have a really bizarre screen layout so that'll happen
Count the spaces no I'm not going to take out the spaces to some people are going to be using see to read it
Bonus points if you see Derita you can probably just open it up in like Notepad
Find replace also
Anyway that's uploaded the next part that we have to worry about is getting the calibration data
So I can say that we just slept across sensor number 7 but that's completely meaningless to you
But we can get a lot further if I say I took the cross sensor number 7 and its current location
Yes here wherever here is or 8 is here at 9 is here
And we have unfortunately wipe the config data for our Vive
But Fox something Dev was nice enough to give us his but it is an older V
By the way if anybody watching right now has the Thanksgiving Vive
If you can please please get us your config file so I can try to get a config that's closer to my
Yet so you going to explain how to do that to it's the lighthouse underscore console light
Underscore console exe is buried somewhere deep within the files that were installed when you install
Revive everything and you can type help and find a whole list of things and you
I think the command is like download config space some file name make it up
And then like she pull a copy of the config file which has the physical positions of a
Everything off and save it as a bin or something like that and then you can email that and that would be
Post a link in the
In the description description I can't do that
Don't go find the link on Twitter or on Reddit and then posted in the 20
You want it do you want it in the description Michael descriptionmichael specifically if you have the
Config for the Vive where this cable right here is one cable instead of three separate
That's the end
Your differences that I know of three-in-one table instead of having three separate cables that got 19
Nice low diameter flexible cable and they came with really good
Wrist straps because everyone was buying out all of the the Wii wrist straps for this parenting
And I was sold out for a while
What is happening
The five is happening
Remember what exactly
Oh yeah here to survive get config
Okay so the way I blew away my config
Was I Will Survive get config when I wrote it I totally wrote it wrong and what I asked
Play ended up doing
See if I can find it
Is I said he'd get feature report time out and then he get Beach Report I'm out I have
Had this set the set update feature report instead of get update feature report what it actually did was just
Bluewave very first 64 X2 Mike intake Destructor which is Jesus so there's no way to reach
Cover the contagious scripture my config scripture was completely blown
And as far as I'm aware they don't keep it around the factory
I think Ben Ben Jackson the guy who wrote that this algorithm was kind of star
Are the show the last two times I think he asked the factory Ford but totally did not
Did not work description Charles yes
Just say like itchy
Okay so I'm going to make sure that I'm not setting the
The the token here I'm only going to be getting for this one so
Update feature report
Get update feature report and its control class
Direction is in and when it says in it means into the computer
Instead of out from the computer so that means that if I run this code it's not going to blow
Descriptor again
Not that we don't already have a temporary one that we put in place from the fox guy
Enable getting the descriptor and we'll see if we can pull it
Cancel it that's cool I'm going to be posting my config descriptor which is kind of close to what we have but not
Exactly which by the way even if it was we do get one from the Thanksgiving it's still going to have some
Very minor manufacturing differences in so far as like the exact location of all of photodiode
So there's no way to get it perfect
Microns
Send it to you just post in the throat
Nopat in the Reddit thread
Write wishing you had made the Reddit thread
Sending it to see okay
No I don't want to email there it just posted in the thread and then we'll
Arrange the habit
The Reddit thread
I will show you what this config is like in a moment this will be the first time I've tried run
Running the getting config on this thing since we started I hope it doesn't explode
Okay mate
Too much data from packet for config for device 00
That's right
Tails try 01 Udall
Could not get survived data I'm case that didn't work let's try 10
Hey something happened
Hack what does tag mean something else
Okay that actually looks really promising what it says it got config data length 34:8
83 which is probably about right because what actually happens is there's a big config file what you guys will cease
The back of coffee
The wrong one
And
They they cheese if it's impressive so it fits inside some memory in there and then when they download it like
Whenever the valve VR software downloads it and just expansive
Expands it and the size 16649 looks like it might be
About right so let's see here make sure I didn't do some
Kind of silly dumb
Print out the size and the pointer to it
Boom
That looks like it's a pointer but that does not look like the right data
Set 20
No okay
That's an interesting thing there's one annoying thing about sea
If you don't Define a variable and it's on your stack it can be random
So if you ever worry about that always set your variables 20 or some known value
Don't leave them uninitialized
So I decided to zero and indeed it does not get updated
What the tag dileo's about
Survive USB tag
Okay 16649 Neal why is that returning Neil
Got config dataline 3043
Now we know we're getting here
I'm making a new buffer
Stark Stark and 20
So I guess I passed in a double star into dysfunction
Almond what that means is the pointer to a flanker and what I need to do is update that pointer so that when I'm out here
That is I can just
Passing a pointer to my pointer
And then it will update this value with the right value
Gorgeous gorgeous we can now read a config file from the Vai
5 headset, so what this would mean is if you were to go use live survive you would be able to read your config file
The state has not yet parsed so we're going to have to do some parsing on it before we can make it useful
Are we going to parse it I did a little bit of checking out things ahead of time
And I didn't really do much in the CD redist folder
I actually already had a copy of the config that we put on it
Test. Config bomb if you want to see what a config file looks like
You can actually check into GitHub repository so I'm not posting likes the things
Things that are into GitHub
I'm so if you visit github.com seeing Laura slide survive
Inside here
We can then look in the
I never committed it
So there's a really small that I just found a simple Google search might be the best might not be the best if you guys know
Better tell me
Easley parsaei TR
ER but yes specifically I am trying jsmn
Is my audio wrong like when I talk
Is this laggy for you
Like it's my voice not does my mouth match my voice
That's a good way to do it that's not as dumb
Yes I'm actually going to try Jasmine that was just the first one that I found
People already
Tilawah
I'm going to be using Jasmine or Jasmine is licensed under the MIT X11 license so I can use it with
I've survived which is also license under the MIT X11 license the reason behind this is that we
Do want live survive to be able to be used in commercial products so whether or not we will or won't
But being able to have it license is a really important thing
I'm going to go push test
You sure can't see my password right
Good okay so now it's been pushed
I'm so now under the Regis folder there's a file called test. Config I just so you guys know this is the one
Already had as an example one but what I'll be doing is I'll be trying to do this with the
The one that's built into my headset
Which is actually just another copy this file so whatever
At any rate the way this works survive get config
Is it
Runs and actually the Stalls were coming get rid of these notes that are wrong
Is it it reads the speed Beach report a bunch of times and then it gets all of the Jesus
Compressed data and then I use inflate in order to fill out the rest of the thing so there is another
Dependency that I have now
And that is zlide but
Considering virtually all systems have some form of zlide decompression
This should be fine
It's not going to be like one of those 500 MB map packages or anything
Maple
Call knowing what is it again in Linux is equivalent and it's just like it makes that sound
Uncompressed eating up your precious hard drive
So let's see
I'm going to
Edit open at config a totally open I can look at it everything's fine so whatever
She tried doing is parsing it using Jasmine so I guess I'll have to make a new thing
Laying here
You know what heck I'll do it right here
Make sure that the return values will will actually make sense return -5
-4 - 2 - 12 those are all negative values that means that
If it fails and will return and negative value if it succeeds it'll be a positive value with the number of fights
My cat says little person called pup I know puff is awesome
Nazi is just great because you can totally run that on like an 80 are it's actually optimized
Totally runs unlike 8-bit microcontrollers it's it's great I love Bob
Are you sure
Frank who has an opinion about what
A way to view the Jason's famous nice to meet you to see
At any rate
I'm moving on so right now if I have a config and all is fine and we'll do this else
Return 0 if it fails
Okay so if it passes now and here we can then print out the
The data that we have to make sure it's still good ct0 Khan
And make sure that all is well with the world
It's not what I wanted
Y'all want to do right now is I don't want to print out
The Lighthouse State so yes I can print that out and it totally Prince it so I now know that I have the Jays
Sandra's coming from the headset so if you want to try out a copy of Life survive on your Linux OS X or even
Probably maybe Windows if you have allied with the filter installed that would be really awkward because
Both valve and this thing would want to talk to the Vive which should be
Weird
Eric the OS X server Linux let's stick to that for right now then you total
So right now in survive. C.l. reading the JS file
Let's take a look at the in the sample Jazz file that comes with the sweet
So the the config files contain a lot of data about the accelerometers and
And the gyro
I say a lot of day by really mean to bias so that means at resting position for the all of the three orientations for the head
What is the 0 for the accelerometer and this is
Important cuz otherwise it'll think that it's going to be drifting one way or the other
I'm Elias if you own any furniture cuz you're always doing it on the floor furniture
Address for Chumps yeah about that no we have plenty of furniture here but it's just difficult to do
A livestream with furniture
Anyway
Just
If you know what is it bothering you
The fables the internal everything that's said I don't understand what George's
Fang
Any rate the accelerometer and the gyro and all of that stuff is calibrated here and considering.
Accelerometer basis bias for a fox's headset was negative or positive
1572 is 15% off 0 which I have a hard time believing that are
Headsets that bad but we're not going to go to calibrate our headset today although I do
Like to calibrate our headsets soon not going to be able to do that right now
It contains a lot of information about the the eyes and how that's all set up it contains
So references to these files which I don't really understand what it is but if
If you use these files
When you update it for your particular Vive I totally works so like when we receive foxes
The headset his config we had to update it with this configs
Amora analyzes that MC files which we were able to find an atom's computer so thankfully that didn't get blown away
And then here is the important part for today
Under Lighthouse config there the Channel map
And inside the channel nap or after the channel Map There's model normals
I personally don't know how to use right now but the most important thing
Is this right here
Model points not imagine model normal could be used to like throw something out that you know
Does bad like if you're getting a reflection from that Lighthouse off that wall and it's hitting it or something like you know you can throw it
Like
It's pointed in the wrong direction but I'm not going to deal with that right now that's hard
What I care about the hardware needed for calibrating I think it just needs the sauce the right song
Yeah I don't know people are saying if I had the hdk that's okay but I would have to execute a non-disclosure agreement
Valve
About that and I'm not not going to do that because I still want to be able to work on all of this and give away all
All of the information I find another person quite a while ago said you should really just return the Vive and get a new one
I has we should I knew enough to know about that
The cool kid hey Mom
Yes this is going to be technical I'm sorry Mom
I think Dad might understand a bit of it but it is it is very
Very subject specific material
Anyway moving on this this file right here contains the config file contains all of these points
How many Star points relative to the center of the headset which I think is
Is right here but I don't know for sure I haven't actually plotted these yet I haven't looked at it yet but I'm going to go Parsi
Please I'm going to dump out
PSV for you guys so you can easily import these data points
And once it was a habit that way I'll be able to load it into life survived they rate the idea is that by having the state
File I can know exactly where each one of these thoughts on the vibe is
And what I can do is I can then correlate the sweet times and all of that to this guy that's all hopes and
I don't know if it's kind of work yet so I guess what I should probably do first is try
Try to extract from this config file right here the the date of the XYZ
The XYZ the XYZ
To test. Config. Jason
I'll rename it to test. Config. Chaisson
Too late he's already doing it Alvin
You've Won
Dawn
Been there too late Don
Okay
And so I'm going to see if I can parse that that day to help now I admit I have done a little bit of prep
At work so in the general folder
Sorry in the weirdest folder I do have a copy of Jasmine. H and Jasmine.
And Justin was again just a parcel I found by just quickly Googling and I wanted
Obviously Google minimalistic C Json parser and the answer is
Five libraries that are to open up these Json files and then there's this one
Which was 315 lines law which
Is like
An order of magnitude smaller than any of the others so I'm going to use this one
It would be that way
Code is
Over there
So I have
Mindy feel free to ask questions
What what
If you have any questions or anyting yeah if you're too
Do you know Ryan
I don't know if I knew Hydra cut
I just don't know that particular okay
How can you add some fire to the wood to the fire
Anybody knows it what time in the last livestream I said I am just a midget on the Giants of sheol
Holder's I'd love to know when because I can't believe I said that that long I don't know who Steven is
Who's to Steven's mom Steven
BK Tuesday
Let's see if I already have open scad I'll do it if I don't
I'm not I'm I'm I understand right now I'm not on a limited data plan but
Oh no let's look at them curious how big is it
Open up in this one speed right now
Oh that's actually really small small small I have
I barely have an excuse not to use open scad
I'm not familiar with it but I'll get it in case
Who don't know DK Tuesday is one of the other Developers for the HTC Vive
He kind of Hopsin last time I didn't know who was for a long time there was a bit of a joke
Nevada
That Ben was like Charles still hasn't figured out that he's Alan Yates
So high Alan
Are a time to go through additionally some the homework I did before was I downloaded the
Example test program of how to open up these config files in JSON sartin Jasmine
And I started poking with that so I'm going to just basically copy and paste wholesale
That example into
What I'm doing yeah dude look it's so slow here the Internet is just
I don't know how or streaming right now that's what's using all the bandwidth
12:00 12:00 kb per second of the bandwidth
Okay
So in here
Instantiate a new Jasmine parser give it a bunch of space
Passing instead of Json string it's going to be ct0 Khan and Len
Party was landfill well this code is basically directly
From the Jasmine example
And I'm going to say if it did not work failed to parse Json
Abort
Did work but something was wrong object expected actual choose the right
Right
The right error codes
Frank had a few questions when you have time
Franklin oh
Does the lighthouse export 32 raisin the plane cuz this 32 points in the lighthouse config with both points and normal
Which could probably be used to extrapolate that to raise and therefore the lighthouse position
My goal is to be able to use the Physicians of lighthouses or not
Positions of the lighthouses but to Define this headset as being 00 the origin
And be able to figure out where the lighthouses are
Based on where this headset is
I'm not a math guy
I'm hoping you guys will be Spartan figure this one out too but I'm going to give it a shot cuz I have an idea as to how I want to try
Try to do it
Okay Tuesday here says when we publish all the lighthouse implementer course
Info that will be included
Okay well
I'm still not going to be signing that NDA right now like I don't think I will or whatever the steam
The click-through license for the HD queso
I don't think I will have access to that
I am actually camping we are camping at my parent's cabin my mom is in the chat right now
Their cabin in the middle of the woods so
That be too convenient
You could pick it up though unlike look around do you want to win when you're done even packed
Well I was a kitchen like you could like pigs
Video with my camera I can play it back but that's about all I can really do
We just got to balance the camera on top of the couch right now it's Terry if you want you can totally take video
Like we get to slope one and play the video
Kevin Hart
Kevin hack oh yeah cabin hack
There was some joke about trying to take the stream out at the on the on the trails and hiking around but I did
Just don't know how he would do that right now we have a really convoluted streaming setup right now
I will not be going
If I'm lucky I'm not going to be going back to Rochester ever sorry
At any rate
Broadcast
Sitting rate what happened is I I look at the Json object that are being returned by Jasmine
And then I look at the first one make sure it's the right kind of objects just object which means it's like a
An unnamed thing and I'm going to eat a rate as it again this is just example code straight up from Jasmine
And I just tweaked a little bit of it I'm going to iterate over all of the things inside of the Json file looking for Mom
Model points and once I find that I'll try extracting its Data Tracking
Track deck
Okay got that
Here
But pretty this up some since it does not need to look terrible anymore
Okay now looks for model points and prints them out let's give a shot
And see if this thing will
Bull Run
Wrong file
Not compiled
And I owe you know it's not party Jasmine stringless part of pt0 conf
Oh you know what I forgot to include Jasmine
I'm looking I'm trying to find where
Where do I have my includes here by
We're getting closer only two warnings line 59
Turn turn the little thing down on the stove
Left all the way just do it quick so you don't burn yourself ohyeah turn the
In the front of the stove
No it's not that hard just flick it
Tobias aonic like 500 lb
For this life
It's it's really nice and warm in here
Yodel stove yodel
Yodel
Including files Reedus
Jsmn. Oh try that
Json EQ not found
Copy and paste art
Okay
Okay one more are left or one more warning which I'm going to treat as an error because I don't want
Have things get all broken
You've compiled
I liked it's something what to do I print it out the
Beautiful okay
So
I'm using Jasmine right now and I am able to actually extract or no
Auralex Jasmine number
Not Prince that junk out right now
Parcero in
Jason
Percent is that how it works I don't actually know how to read out the the
Thanks
Is everything going on okay and chattered language lessons
Your mom's been talkin to the the Norwegians
I was just afraid that my mom would just leave when we got like really specific
Details
AMC
Numb Finland Sweden and Norway here and Germany
I haven't seen any argentinians today
For keeping your mom busy Charles
What did she say that
Don't see anything for my mom
But it's been buried
Brazil
What did you get to see how long she would
No we did not place that's to see how long my mom would stick around for that would be mean
Okay back to work
Let us Just Turkey
He
And copy C ttk
Shinobi
T0 Kant
Cross BK Aerostar
,
Kon last ekaro
T
When is equal to t k n y a c k start
TK's height is four or Atlanta
CTT -1
Okay so Jasmine is kind of a cool way that it parses JavaScript are straight-up script
Parks is Json files because he just read through it and they do look kind of like as it's going it'll produce this
Table and and 12 tables all said and done all that actually stories is pointers to where
Are the different tags and different things live so offer anyone tag like say I'm looking at
Specific
A specific things like under reduced under test. Kindig. Jason if I'm looking at
Say this particular value right here
He tells me where the first character of it is and the last character of it is that way I can just go look to it and
Read it out and it doesn't have to keep copies of all of this junk around
But it does mean it's a little bit awkward cuz I have to go copy the string out and some other stuff
Lm10
EL Online
CTT
Let's see what the state of looks like
Broken why is it broken
DLS 19 that's a reasonable length for a number a number is allowed to be 19 B weide
T
Mom I will be uploading this video of but I am going to edit out the first part when we start the Stream
Other than that unless something happens during the stream that would be
Major whatever I generally I think I'm going to be uploading the streams as is
Did you say something else I think you can totally chat with these people about
Anything you want that's the fun instead it's it's called a live if it's a live event so it's
It's like people can actually get together and just chat and talk about you know both this and everything from all over around
Somebody says line 96 hydrocat
You just save me five minutes
Bingo all thanks hydrocat okay so now we got all the data
I don't know if that's the right number of elements so it doesn't look right
That's right I mean it looks right it's got
Starting it 20 and going all the way off its
Got the right around
Which point in reference as a lighthouse coordinates to
What do you mean that's just what Frank is a star
Meli Meli
These are not Lighthouse coordinates yet these I'm right now just trying to read out from the head not the
Display the location of all of these dots relative to its sweeping Crossings
Basically a Time
That's what the data that's on GitHub gives you the time that it's at inactive
Write it down on a piece of paper for the
Team effort here thank you
Give me a second
Exynos 400,000
To get you a whiteboard
That big like camera pointing down that would be
I can hang this one from the ceiling yeah but I can't zoom in on the turn on the light
Okay so what we actually have like data is it's done with these lasers that sweep around and around in a
Around 360 degrees just around around around and it takes 400
Thousand tix4tonight of 360 so one of the things that we were marveling at at my house
Is the fact that if you're in the center of the of lighthouses point-of-view like the
Put the dead centerforce looking down here and your object is right here then it's exactly 200,000 ticks
And we were just like wow those valve people they like their round numbers that's really awesome but
It's actually really cool because it it it just happens to line up that way this is just for
1006 all the way around because it's one sorry all the way around
121 120th of the second so all of the the laser scanners are operating at 8
Exactly fit exactly 120 hertz and they're all like phase-locked
So there are all each one is I guess the
Can each Lighthouse the one laser scanner spinning around is exactly 180
Degrees out of phase with the other one I think you're right I think so I think it's 188
Don't think it's like 90 90 90 90
That's probably right I don't actually know for sure that what if it was just spinning slower to see
This one goes 90 and then this one goes 90
Anybody who's more familiar with this they might know for sure if it's actually 90 90 90 90
Or if it's 180 180 180 180
Does it make a difference
Jupiter at least right now we're trying to do this to find the locations of the lighthouses so that we can
Then figure out the location of objects within the vibes point-of-view
And he's doing this without using the existing libraries for communicating with the vibe
Because he wants to basically
I don't know how the lighthouses communicate through each other I do know that there is a developer
Currently in chat who with
He would like to say something about that he totally can but that is actually
Be of no concern to any of my goals so
They have two house would they they stay in perfect sync with each other
Osprey Point
I didn't think about that maybe they they are dumb says that
Use RF okay it just directly between and light pulses
Another interesting one is the lighthouse redox people were able to find out that
The flashes that they give are specially coated neither one and zero in the data domain
And they make up a list other interesting packet in
Has a thing about that on chat right now
Mills is Mills has his explanation is
Did the
Oh nevermind I thought you were the guy who did the lighthouse redox I was going to be like super excited
I show the lighthouse on the camera here
See here the camera corrected
Say what
I specifically I'm trying to not get in
Situation right to sign in the nda's or anything like that hey you can kind of see it
I'll go the other side has power in the back
Oh hey that's really cool
It is not helping little bit of the structure in there
Yeah so what you actually can see is the laser scanner across the bottom
That kind of follows the camera from left to right
And the laser scanner on the right that follows it top we talked about like
Keep this little
Sitting here versus that little thing down there not the big bag of Lights bright
Flashes to synchronize everything the bottom one is the one that scanning left to right
Says you see like if I'm all the way over here
Can you see normally can't see through
The camera like this you can kinda sort of this again
Yeah I know the lighthouses are so elegant
It's really nice
Could you guys hear me clearly
The lighthouse as far as I know oh yeah there you go Arnie give you the answer
Sorry I think you guys are starting to see why I think the five is so cool
Sorry
Down here and keep coating so right now we are going to have to Parts this data and get it
Endolite survive and I'm going to go export that so that you guys can have both the timer
Data and the position data that I'll be playing with oh my gosh we already an hour
And a half in
Store. Okay
Fun with this rate I was hoping to be further along
Been a lot of sidetracks makes me sad
So I'm going to have to open survive Eternal. H
And I'm going to have to add to the objects
By the way one of the chips that I'm going to be using in conjunction with this
Is the esp32 and from what I can tell it actually does have floating-point support so you
Even though valve has been very careful to use doubles from what I can tell everywhere
I sure will do
Maybe I'll make it so could be doubles or floats
Sure let's do that to give everything away
Gave most of it away
My mom wants to know in one sentence what this is about
Figuring out how to do all of the Vibes backend stuff yourself
On a bad computer
I want at all
I want to
Valency by myself but like without using
The people who made the Vive stuff
Make the Vive work on really slow computer
Is that a sentence
I think I mean I think they're still wondering why do you why do you want to work on a computer
Number one I have a really old laptop
I want to use the bike with it
And by the way we do have access to like a really fast Windows computer right here but I want to get at work on my laptop
And number two because I have this grand plan
Of also using an esp32 with assistant
Esp32 from espresso
Do you guys have some ideas I don't actually have a solid plan yet
I talked to Tina mobile
Okay so basically I'm going to be
Doing BR things with the VR headset
Fast and without the help without using the stuff that the people who made the VR headset
Made
Sort of like I'm still using the headset but I'm using all the firmware they put into that you give it up okay
I'm sorry it's so hard to explain
Why wouldn't balvir htc desire
I don't know how they work internally they very well might be able to do this way faster than me
But
I don't go into situations
Assuming I'm never going to be able to do anything cool because I was going to go into situations and see what happens
At any rate
A lot about cosmetics
Right
Frank
Really cool looking things do you need a really high-end computer to render the really awesome
Graphics and interact with it right and no
Something that kids like look like a horrible Atari game
And from the ground up
And also one of the other side effects of that is many times when you do get something that's super fast and really lightweight
Then everything else benefits because parts and pits of parts and pieces of it can be used to really
Make it run faster for everyone just provide light
They are the things that receive the light and they
Measure exactly when it comes through in the light comes at a very regular interval and
They can do math to basically figure out where they are based upon what
Sensor sees light when
You not know about a parallella board
Sounds like a VR
Perambulation device
Ambulation
I don't know what a parallella board is
But if it's anything even close to an esp32 I'm not interested
Because I haven't esp32
It's an fpga development board as cost money
I'm not dealing with it know if I can do it while on a on a $2 microcontroller I'm doing on a $2 microcontroller
I'm not spending anymore unless you have a magical source for refugees that can do this there's like two bucks.
Touching it
I think you better just get back to it it'll never finished
You're OU I need I need to just do this you guys can just talk While I Work It says you guys are pretty familiar with it now
Which one did I steevens Simplicity but why aren't you using something more
Advanced
I don't know what is get it
Sounds familiar
This is
It's small and small and lightweight
Do I need to go figure out how to actually put the state at into the right place
So
CTX Arrow
I think Mel has got it now
And so the golfer today is to figure out the math necessary to figure out where those reference point
Points are once we know where the lighthouses are we can then Trace back to figure out where
The headset and the
Handheld controllers are
Assume for right now everything's got 32 locations
So what exactly do we mean by finding the lighthouses
So right now we just know basically times that light hits things
Andweknow theoretically the time of the sweeps
And so you should be able to with math basically figure out
I guess it's a whole trigonometry problem basic
That we basically can use
X
Light impacting Those sensors to figure out where in some kind of 3D space
White houses are
Does that make sense
What I'm saying but doesn't make sense
See each other I know they're there I don't know
I don't think that they actually know where they are
Anything or do they just talk back in Forth
Other so that they're not both interfering with each other and I believe that there's also a signal that spelling disc
Timing of what no
There's not actually the long flash as far as I can tell is what tells this thing all the time in
So you could theoretically if you knew exactly the location of the two lighthouses
And where they're pointed and everything
You would even be able to tell where you are in the room without any communication to the rest of the vibe at all I think
I think someone else had said in chat before that specifically the lighthouses do not communicate with the
Dcn anyway
So only the controllers my headset communicate to PC
Do the controller's communicate with the headset and then the headset
Everything together and then send that to the BC so there's only one USB cable for this whole thing
Whereas the
The rift right now heads up to 3 if you got the
And then one of them is power
One of them is video one of them is data and audio is going to come through that date as well and then they
There's actually an audio device in there it's generates an audio signal which comes out this one's you can plug in your headphones
They used to have a cable that was this big
All The Way We Were among the first people to get one of those and we didn't even know that
Really lucky
Apparently that was the day we bought this
The day they switched over to water the controller send data to the headset
Wireless that is wireless wireless mouse apparently they use wireless mouse to type trans
Receivers for that sort of thing
Come in now
So have we tried changing the Arts or having collected data that we've liked had the
Lighthouses at 1 high the moon like a different I don't think we need it because we know
So much about the details with the spinning so I think simply have
Having one of these devices sitting in the middle of the floor whatever should be enough to do everything we need
Because it wanted sweeps it'll be hitting multiple fractures so from here
Raise theoretically from the center of that thing out into the scene and hit just like
Reverse it I guess and then based on that be able to try to move I'm going to try to move that thing right
Around in order to try and find an orientation in a position which would match like the theoretical position
Abby's dots from where it is trying to move it around until I can find some
Orientation and everything where the data I'm getting for when those lights got hit
Matches
Where I went at the data that I think it should be heading to hit all those
So like
If this headset was the lighthouses in it
Just needs to know like
If it knows that the lighthouses are spitting it at The Tickler frequency then maybe it only needs to know
The difference between like with the timing of Wendy's since it's facing
This way this is really going to get hit like he's undercover here going to get hit like
Bam
Bambam and so it but if you turn it this way then they're going to get hit
Rite fans
So from lighthouses point of view
It would mean that if it was oriented this way and it was coming through is going to Bam Bam Bam real quick
It would mean that the lighthouse would have to be at this position relative to the headset
We just need to know that the lighthouses are in a consistent time and the only thing that matters are the difference in the
Temporal difference in Wendy's receive signal
That's why doesn't matter what he put those cuz the only thing that matters because this this height
The orientation this way because it's not just me
Always in One Direction
Right and so if it was aim down more
Then that would mean it would appear that it was towards the top of the frame physically lower it would also appear
Another question if it's rotating is it going family member here and then bam bam bam down over on the other side
Do inside the lighthouses the speed B when they spend they go away
Decide
So like the one that goes in the up-and-down traction you're saying it only goes it's only Circle
Killer and when it's pointing in the back of it I guess either have the laser off or it's just not doing
Are you sure it's a rotating emotion and not just a sweeping motion
Align
I don't understand
You could have a light you have a line of light that is going in a circle and it's rotating in
From the lighthouses point of
View the lighthouses right here it'll go
Like this
So the whole plain of like that's sweeping the whole thing right
Sweet
It is it is rotating around the lighthouse like that but from our point of view it.
Doesn't light up when it's going on the back so
It's not going to the plane of projection
Projection not
Parallel to its plane of projection
Yovino not parallel no is coming out from the from basically the center
Quote
Float
Actually looks
On my PC since doubles are not slow for me I will use a double
Survive internal dates line 7900
Are you guys watching chat for me so I can keep working
I don't know I think that by explaining it to you they understood it better and that's
Exactly half of this battle
Do we know if the the lighthouses have a
Actual rotating laser or is it a laser when a rotating mirror
We're not entirely sure it doesn't really matter okay
I'm sure that there are many people
Who do know that
I do not
Oh you've added something to the issue
Have you
I will pull it up
Commodes
Oh hello
That's kind of neat
This is he says he took the config data
And he figured out what position all the things were in yet
Bullet funny with the three at the end
Peter on the light again
Yeah that totally
Where the one in the middle
Are there any of the middle
There is a camera on the front of the headset but that does not look like a sensor
So yeah the hell yeah
Yeah and this is oriented in the right organ is orientation
Was just asking about that actually I don't actually know this but we
I believe that the camera is only really used for the The Chaperone system right now which was
Did the camera showed up just before they release this thing it hadn't been in any of the prototypes or anything like that and the
The idea of the camera was that it would
When you get near the boundary of your playable area it would show you a little bit of the cameras fee
Process to look like a cool blue outline we can talk a little bit
Buggy apparently and it slowed things down and some people aren't using it
Are you seriously
From the from the the camera on the HTC Vive
Let us know if that does bad things to our stream by the way cuz we have a very very limited data Ray
How do you tell if a nice things don't go together
Okay I'm going to keep coding right now cuz we got to get this data pars okay
Diane save I saved
BK Tuesday says the normals that he had in his thing look weird
And we turned it off didn't we
But yes it's not the camera
Sorry it's right there
Cameras back on
It doesn't cast to the screen here
No actually you know what I can make it cast the screen but then nobody else can see it
Well I'm blind
I don't think I can
Charles has the Vive plugged into his laptop right now and that's how he's getting all kinds of data from it and he was just able to
Connect right to the camera stream do you want me to I can totally weird you out Monday I can open up my laptops
Hold on
Windy out here for that I'm going to
Jack in and put this picture right here
On her
Charles's face
Okay moving on okay
Text us to compile bugs
I'm going to kill it now
Oh but this is stuck at the video from a 5 is coming through a BNC connector
Change my computer desktop computer from a laptop and then it's going out
To YouTube through my cell phone so it's
Has an excuse for being blurry
Yes4all if you were asking if Charles has a degree he does and
I have a I have a regular four-year degree which took me five years because I am a
As they call him the math dolt cuz I was not in college because I failed calculus
1 + 2 + 3 + 2 + 3
But I did get a master's degree in computer science little while later and I did okay by then my I got that
Sort of not nearly as well as my brother I don't know if you still watching
My my brother got the the math genes in my family
Why is it wrong
Sodium nice
Is that right
Pay 96 National encouragement for all of you people who think you're terrible at math
Computers
It's okay
Nigra have to work at it
I didn't give up and I work my butt off even though I knew I was failing with a with an F
I I've worked my butt off but I was able to get it eventually
So you guys were saying something earlier about not not sure if something was like 9990 r180
The synchronization of the sweeps of lasers
I don't know whether Charles was talking about between the two different things or just
90 degrees out of phase so if this one goes sweep
Like if they like this one goes sweet
One has it's 90 degrees out of phase and those are 180 degrees out of phase I miss one so it's pretty
Strong though or think they're all one
Think they're I think it just turns them off when it's not using up the I think
Cuz you don't want these to be getting light at the same time from two different ones
Canadian FaZe
As in like sweep
And then the next one is it comes around sweep and the next Wednesday comes around sweep and actually comes around sweep
They might I don't know
Light from both of them
Cuz if you face it this way then this is only going to be on their Frontier
And this one's only going to be getting information from here like how would this weekend information from that one
I'm sorry say it again
Sorry
Oh Jupiter is talking about his own Vive being blurry and yeah that's definitely
Distance between the eyes is a little dial there what I would do hold the Vive in cannae
And I want to get to alexys
Question or something there but so when try to get your Vive 2
Not be blurry like that you want to make sure you adjust it up and down properly just shifted up and down on your face
Until it looks best and then try to fix all your straps there
Strap here
And besides wraps
Then you want to try shifting side to side
And how I describe the see there's a dial here on the side which will adjust the lenses in and out and it can't
Take you awhile to get that right so what I was doing was
I was looking at my right eye only and seeing if I needed to shift it this way or this way I knew that if I
I needed to shift it this way
That what
That I needed the lens to come in and so then I would dial into the lenses would come together and I would check the same thing with the other eye
Basically should be pretty clear really
Bother texting me little coating trick I thought I'd show you guys a one of the annoying things about csvs
Just like you have to put like commas between the elements than a new line at the end and it can get really yucky but
A friend showed me a while ago is this little trick right here what you can do is you can say printf you can print out the now
Number and then percent Siemens print out a character
And so I can print out F and then I can if it's the last element print out a new line or if
If it's earlier on I can print out a, like that
No right here I wouldn't have one day CSV
Kind of works
Correction or something
I should probably copy that into a CSV Allen has more words for you
Charles start with One Sensor One lighthouse in moday
Until you understand the sync system
I'm sensor1 Lighthouse movie
I don't understand the differences in the modes but that's what it says to go in when you only have a single lighthouse
There's a mode where you have a single lighthouse
I don't I don't understand that I haven't tried it yet cuz we know I guess you could do it with one lighthouse
That's really hard to do but
What is your gift to lighthouses
He's figuring out how close or far
The thing is you have to see
How big or small this thing appears in the blight houses
Field of view I'll let me go upload the CSV right now though
Where did I.
I guess
Moday means it doesn't take turns
If you don't have this one and then that one
Boulder
Why why would I want
I mean when I analyze it it's going to be less but
I can just
Throw out the packet that are coming in from sync Pulses from the other one
Seems less
I don't know
Michael says if if you mapped the perlite house per device Spencer strike events in
An image using the sweep relative event time step is the relative position of the pixel
My 8.1.5 equals dead center
The resulting image is equivalent to what a constellation style tracking camera would normally generator
You can feed this into a conventional PNP algorithm using contemporaneous images from each lighthouses
Thanks for an optimized pose
Okay you said a lot of things that are more complicated than those boring see programmers mine is going to deal with
Michael's messages
Okay
So right now we have that
One thing at a time
Help Benz joined us
My bad
He says the but Michael was saying as how the original tracking system work
I'll let you know I'm not getting seeing pinga pinga things I'm getting it cuz I want to steal the GUI
By the way if you guys haven't already seen see anything it's the coolest thing ever
Try to advertise this to everybody
It's free it's on GitHub and
Google Google
And oh well I guess that's really bad
Alan says that is a bad approximation but a good starting point I don't know who sing that too
Our life in pain isn't working
Oh well don't care I just wanted to get it to get the
What is it called here
OS generic
And I want to get my hands on her all functions
When Noah uses seeing ping
Does he
Oh hey I know thank you for using CN paying don't forget to develop it further now we just need people to be you
Using
Color cord
Yeah color Corey I got to do that video explaining how color cord works that's going to be
Salon in the tooth
What is an idiom mean
That's a very good question what does long in the tooth mean
Watching can you tell us what long in the tooth means
Okay
I'm going to do now
I'm going to in
Yahtzee
I'm going to go open
Window
Michaels
Written down all of the stuff that he told us in the
In the vibe subreddit so we'll have that for a record for later if you can please
I'd like these big notes and stuff to the issue on GitHub that makes it easier for me to track later
Cuz everything will be inside the live survive GitHub to remember I think we're going to turn live survive until way more than
Library that can do this but like a Tome of Justice Collective fun of
5 Adventure having album says you need to zip the CSV because GitHub will not
Except seattle.vs which is really weird that is weird
We should have used ssds
Too late now
Chaos if you can open the hmd file now or the points file
I don't know
The RPMs of sensory rather the light sweeps in the
Monogamous
Transportation I think it has to be 120
By the way
Howdy
I would really like it was 15
It would be it would have to be 120 cuz if it goes 0
And if this is 200,000 ticks and that's 400,000 takes and then back to zero
You divide 360
Rotate on their perspective boxes
60 revolutions
Eventually it gets to the point it says any check object decided tracking volume is hit by a laser at a rate of
120 hertz
So what you sexy
Okay so
60 I'm guessing is what that
Figured out he says yes 60
Is it really
That's what we get from Doc okay Lighthouse tracking examination 100,000
Okay then why in the world is Center to 200,000 ticks
Or am I just supposed
200 + 200 + 200
Maybe
Oh
Yeah okay that's possible
I have to keep going I have to keep going here
Before I get too tired
10:30
Your coffee no ice cream
Actually we do want ice cream for ice cream
No
That
Maybe someday
Yes Jupiter we were actually pointing out the insides of the lighthouses earlier we understand
Physically what's going on in there you just don't know everything about the timing in the
Spin rate and everything
Who's asked me if we looked inside the lighthouses
I don't know where the beam is plenty of time to think flash I don't have a high speed camera
The only thing I was looking at was its 200,000 Cycles roughly between
The sink Flash and when I get hit by the beam I was assuming it was cuz the beam was like roll to the back of the camera during that
What time
Oz where is the being pointing at the time so that the
While one
Steve
Yeah YouTube won't let you post links
If you want to post anything Post in the issue
Can you like post a sanitized link like
Change the.com to a natcom or something I tried that it didn't work
They're onto you
Goal
She had a Spam problem so I wish we could just allow it understand
I understand problem the first like life thing I did I have it such a fan problem
Okay
Leaving my mouse on tablet go back to see if link health is good
Wondering
Okay
You need to find some kind of coordinate system for the base station X
That's what I found for the lighthouse and just pulled out the. In. Org
That wrong
I can do that wrong I wrote this Library I still got my things wrong
Portents of the future
Yeah I had tried that before Albin just leaving out the ww.w and everything before it but it still complained until
Kelly took out the. And.com
P.com
Remember
Homestar Runner
A very long time
Jupiter asked which games you recommend a very interesting one just popped out called super Kaiju its kind
Kind of like
The
Space pirate trainer Regis shooting at targets in front of you pretty much
But
You
You have to play against another person who's doing it at the same time and so you each try to shoot these targets to get more points
And what's the point you spend them on these cards that you draw him a debt to attack the other player
It's hard to describe and there are not a lot of people in multiplayer yet so get it
I need more people to crush
You don't want one sister to receive light from both
Lighthouses plug that one
Right don't worry about it
Came in and both hit one at the same time it would be like around a while
Exactly
Effacing
Start way
That way
Lansing
This one is only if you were back in that corner if you were back in that corner and they happens to sweep and hit it
Same time that would be
And so it is possible to get yourself in some kind of geometry that that would happen and so they just
There's no reason they couldn't so they just sent them to be timed so that won't ever happen
Sweet sweet
Yes Jupiter I do challenge you to a duel
Put it on and look at Charles's face again
Yes I actually have one of the
I have the original Oculus that I got from the kickstarter and then I got the Oculus that they just gave
Gateway for free which I was very impressed that they did that and it's good it's so much better than all the earlier ones but then the vibe came out
Goodness it's definitely a lot better but I haven't actually sat them down side-by-side and compared them
I do need to do that
I do think it looks better just off the top of my head in here but it
I I don't really remember the one thing I do notice right off the bat as you don't have nearly as big of a problem with the god raised with this
Where is the Oculus
Whenever you had a dark area with a really bright source of light you get this weird Ray cast
As if they didn't put a Nancy reflective coating inside the inside the thing I don't entirely know what that is
I don't know whether they fix that later on I lived on a lot of things since so hopefully
But that was one of the big problems I think the Oculus
Had
What wavelength this working out
What wavelength of light
It's at least around 8:50 I think 850
Nanometers
Although you know what everything I said technically about the HTC Vive is going wrong and Alan his correct
Are we on a first-name basis
Like all you can do is be like here.
I like Santa that you can never see my face
That would like a high-speed IR camera
Ashley Charles did you ever post that are video I never did post the other video
A camera that he took the internal IR filter out of and then you put an external everything but I are filled
So only IR gets through and he pointed it at the lighthouses and it looked pretty neat
Gives you good luck in the inside them
And 835
One of his one of them the LEDs and one of them's the lasers
Are the two different
No no no
Different times
Well I took photodiode I looked at all the county Dory I think
Wait till they have to be the same frequency cuz we only get
The time data from that
Something like when I get data from there it doesn't differentiate like this came in at this time
Lasers 835 LEDs 850
So it's just a matter of like the technical the lasers you use happen to be 8:30 okay
Presumably
Watch even that be wrong
Yeah I'm looking forward to that microhex we're trying to find a good way to support the cable in our house
And it's not right now just leaving it on the floor is really pissed anything up in the air keeps getting hot
Toddler hands when doing stuff
LEDs are going to have a wider Spectrum or lasers or narrower doubt there's a difference in functionality and detection
That would if there were a few guys use two different wavelengths that would have totally wrecked up
A whole bunch of my plans so I'm really glad that that's not the case
I will happily Google that one
Ben Jackson
Oh my gosh I have never had a problem with cnfcu why is this not working
I was thinking of
Getting like a Unistrut with the little track followers in it and then kind of hinging it to the Eunice Trotwood
Hang around you have a couple track things with the cable like festoon to cross their that's a little bit over-the-top
If I'm actually going to go quite that far
If we ever get our company a better office then we'll probably just set up a permanent thing and there was like a Gantry track roller
The difficulty with that is going to be the inertia I don't want it yanking off the
Vyve
Okay if you guys see whatever I'm doing wrong I'd really appreciate it cuz like right now I'm crashing on
Printing out!!
Alan says early basis were 6:50 and 8:50
Nanometers
Okay is anybody in this
Would you mind going back in like copying and pasting these really key things to text file
Like a notepad like anything like when he was saying the early bases were 650 and like that's really
Cool like this cool information like the lasers or 850
Bread bread
I wouldn't write it down on their copy paste into Notepad
Okay
Wait but why why does weighted telling me why it's broken
Says main task survive in it now lock
Survive and yet survive c76 invalid write of size 8
Survive. C line 103
So another really cool to Liz valgrind if you ever write stuff in Sea and you're running into problems
We're like my things crashing I don't know why valgrind will tell you absolutely gorgeous Lee
By the way Charles you tried writing a text somewhere you shouldn't have
And it tells me it was on this line of this file which is really crazy
I'm so glad that the Dahlgren does what it does it actually blew my mind for a number of years
But it turns out valgrind is an x86 emulator
That runs on your computer
But whatever you call system calls it calls it to your host system so it's an x86 emulator running
Hang on your computer in a virtual environment
On the host system so it's simulating a computer to tell me what I write somewhere I'm not
How to write
Really cool
Surviving it line 103
Lost connection
And reconnecting
Piano 850s internet connection successful
Make sure you start copying the stuff out I am working on it okay
Do I have an unlimited data plan and I have screamed
Tens of gigabytes friend's cabin before but you never know where it it when it's going to change
Whistleblowers silenced
Play the Falcon whistleblower
What wires what is he joking about
I don't know
Thousand took him out
Do you actually know the guy who made valgrind cuz I don't that would be super cool
Writing 95 + 95 is when it Dido it's cuz I got to
An allocation it's cuz this should be at the end of the flu
Generate under gets into a ride
It's not visible red
Finest kind of Isabel
Wait a minute
Oh you know what did the bass turn off when I turned off the other one
Cuz you haven't said it into moday how do you set things into moday I haven't actually I'll bet you there's some head string I can
Can send it that somebody's figure it out but I don't feel like dealing with that right now
Died right he said something about valgrind
Ice cream
What
Know that we did actually lose connection to the stream that's why I dropped
Okay I was just saying the valgrind is awesome because it's an x86 emulator that runs on your computer to pretending to
Be your computer running code
With
Connected to your like your actual computers Colonel and it all just does its thing and it tells you where your bugs are
Okay so looks like that bug went away nobody looks in the manual Jupiter
Do you actually have the manual
Fortunately we have valve people here to tell us what to do
Thank you Val people
Does it say on it
Not yet emitting infrared
Oara
Maybe sesay and we just can't read be
Oh that would have been an ass
I think it's an uppercase a
And then a large lowercase b
Chop more wood while it's light out there is there's a fair bit of wood that's chopped over on the woodpile
I see it
Hahira
Is a challenge anything about it cuz I took it off a while longer
I was going to challenge them to get Half-Life 3 out before I get the the vibe reversing
Okay I guess I'll just say it I was thinking about challenging the the valve people to get high
Half-Life 3 out before I get a fully functional HTC Vive
The environment working
Adam
I don't know that's a firework
Firewood
Colorful
Did you put a sparkler there a 1987 sparkler in there
They are 1987 sparklers
Wow
Holland you want to move to take the bike over there we'll watch it
Get a closer I just went out sorry guys you missed the sparkler that Adam through into the fireplace
It was very exciting you really miss.
I'm closing it now
I can help us provide that I'm going to close it
Okay
Because
Hack Pixel why is this not working I have used CM paying like a hundred times before
Can you can get ice cream now
Maybe I kind of do but then it's going to melt produced like water
You should eat ice cream now before it gets later
Refrigerator
Yeah your ice cream now
All the water died
Okay Adams going to try to get the water at the cabin working again
Duty is important water duty is also
Nice cream
Yes I want ice cream
Try flipping the table little
Not getting anything
I'm coming on
I'll check the breaker for the down and up
The green one
Turn off the water heater first
I'm sorry people in chat there's nobody reading chat right now
I'm busy
Why are you so angry
Cuz I'm doing things
Robot
Somebody said they'll have to drink ice cream
It says hello
Hello she says hi
Girls you want ice cream
Sure
I want to do work in the people here at those three to chat and Waters not suppose
Posted break
Hey the light turned on
Someone just quit the light on
How to text speech in that order word
Well he did something he just couldn't do
Oh so don't use water guys
Oh
Can somebody check to make sure the faucet out there didn't get turned on turn on the lights and then go there on
Make sure that the faucet in the front didn't get turned on
That the faucet mini knows where it is
Right
Oh that's not good
I need
Your place out in the sticks while there's a lot of there's a lot of sticks
Reflectix you mean trees
Is all the are all the faucets off okay can somebody walk out around the
The left side of the cabin and just make sure there's not water shooting out from somewhere
Like the side of the cabin like on that side
Like outside walk around the cabin and look for water coming out somewhere
Hear water moving
Is it like
That's just concerning
If Adam here's the back there I don't think that's what we're hearing
Yeah the toilet running
Oh okay toilet
Oh okay
This morning what happened was the fa
Outside Pro Shot even though it was open so during the night it slowly like
It is melted until when I woke up this morning I heard the hot water heater like the element
And I had to let quickly turn everything off so
Okay can you get back to the duty where you do the thing with the chat
I do the thing is done
Charles does want to do a Vive VR programming interface
So you can register programming environment SEC tinycc is the coolest thing ever
Mermaid because you can like write programs and you can save it and you can recompile the program
I'd like use all of the same date it was running with and keep executing with new code in one frame
You can just like Eddie code on the Fly and it just keeps running and can I get a spoon
Please
Wilderness preserve the water through the night that means no showers but
Already got mine
Stinky rub myself all over your bed
Paul says he looked into that but couldn't find any documentation for how to do that with feces
I have an example of me doing it in no Euclid if you just if you just Google no Euclid
Indian lore I have a video where I demonstrated and the code is available in GitHub for that
Separated out to its own module so you can copy and paste the Tsetse tools out of that into any project
I would love to meet Pascal there sorry for Bruce Ballard before I die
That guy has written so much cool stuff
X-rayed and like you can use a toilet but don't use it very much
There's an outhouse outside that's unlimited use that is unlimited use the Outhouse is unlimited use
Basilic crazy things in it
Mom got rid of all them
Year-and-a-half two years
But it's like Outdoors you can kind of just princess pees everywhere anywhere
You can just it's the woods nobody cares
Places to ski in the morning
All right so what I'm doing cuz I'm exposing to buffers I'm going to be using them in survive process
So I can in real-time visualize some of this data
I guess we wouldn't be allowed to like pee off the porch.
No peeing off the porch
We should do a livestream of drive all the way up all the way
The house
The final space okay
Will do that
Do that next time
Figure out how to do it though
Well just serve wifi with my phone and don't have to
No no
Read more down for the GoPro
See this is how you do it
Double the sugar
The Jackson wants us to call something jnk
I believe I have that
Charles are you using the IMU for data track data for tracking will I will be using
Emu hopefully but hopefully David Chapman is going to be helping me out a lot there I'm just talk about Jay
B&K stinks okay. And it's this table right here is what they're taught
Talking about
But I'm not there yet
Need a second monitor why do I care about Jane Casey
Euro 10 J&K yabi
JK JK
In my other desktop
Yeah
Because they're not because I have a laptop
And resources
Don't worry about it stop thinking about it just go
Are you seriously using that as a spoon
Nope
Oh man what is up with the J&K thing nevermind it's not
But I thought it was why is that
Okay this this logic is probably wrong but you can just
You don't have to yell at me right now I'm unconfident to state is wrong you guys
Hopping hoping someone working
Everything is a spoon if you're brave enough hay
Or not
Or something what what's going on
Oh you know what this is clearly oud move us around
Can you make the other window visible so sorry
And you can see what you're holding at in the screen
A little lower
Okay so it's kind of I clearly have that wrong though
Let's try zero and one
2 and 3 Maybe
Oh that's super wrong
That is super wrong
Where we looking to right now
Trying to look at a readout of the positions being trapped
And infirmary have any do this again so what I have is a library call draw draw
Which allows you to take like any c program or C Ghostbuster anyting
And windows Linux whatever I want to open a window and I want to draw some points want to draw syntax
I wrote it many years ago for I don't know if when I was in college
Quadro is actually distributed inside of the endings you can just use raw draw and with
Really simple stop just
You say seanachie setup you give me the window name and window size
And then you can call handle input
Clear frame set the color get dimensions
Straw bunch of pixels drossin text swap buffers weight
And it just keeps doing it over and over and over and over
If you know what I will do that right now
So instead of dots I can do
Tutak rectangle
Can you make a chart its own color so that we can keep track of what. Is where
That's a good idea I will do that
Can you move around so make sure this works
Still not tracking you why is it out here
You know what I think because the top of the screen is 0 instead of the bottom of the screen it's
Hold on here
Survive process
Divide that by 1000
And that's 240 -
Barely in there ready to move the lighthouse off some
Or
Now
Get closer to it
Take note
I guess you are not from
That is really hokey what's going on there
Try to make it to all of the things visible to the
Okay
It's not working anywhere near as well as I would have expected
I guess okay what's color coded something
Yeah but it's still it means that they're not interpreting the data right
Say what you got on that
Ice cream is more important
I want to leave it up here mounted
Oh cuz I can't see
Perfect
Okay now they're all map to different colors
Okay
Only this one right really close to get really close to it
Okay you can lower the The Thing song
Lowered a little bit
Do you want to hang on
Little bit
Maybe a little more
Stop
Okay it's not really talking right now maybe back up some
Adam can hold us
I don't know that started tracker again somewhat
What's going on why is that begin that way
It's tracking her but only sometimes
Yes definitely a lot better and further away with that
Yeah
Then also one thing to notice if it doesn't receive an update for a long time it just keeps the. Wherever it was
Salad someone clearly got a mess with here
SMS with the handheld controllers at all
Are you may be that much easier for you to do this when we could do
Maybe help open suggest taping all but one sensor
Do we have
Paper that yeah let's do that let's let's keep trying
How to do it this way first there's probably something obvious were missing is probably not that hard
Alan says now the disambiguation explodes
Does that while ago presumably when she was up close to it I didn't see
I know the five does not come with those those stands for the lighthouses Charles got those 9 a.m.
Amazon
Oh wait why are some these codes - 1
Is it only the negative one the only negative value
Yeah it looks like the occasionally
Points are jumping to fix blinds away from the top
And left of the display is -1 signify is that life A2 that I'm looking at right now
This is live data
And that's life
Okay as it showed a negative right now it's this column right here
How does your framer disambiguation
Disambiguate for
And you can just ignore sensors and software
Just drop out
You know I'm thinking with disambiguation or what he means by that is the he probably talking about the
Something that looked at the length of time for the really big pulses the really really big pulse
And then figures out which code it is that does that sets the ACO that's the one that's going now
Negative for some reason
So take a look at that code is he recommends
Okay so I have
The light object sensor 80 - 1
Michael says that's what it is I'm an idiot I actually I wrote
That sends a negative one on a person
Is that really what I did
Here
123's the third thing
Okay so that is the right thing
That makes sense it's only the negative one it's it's only negative one when it actually does the first week flashed indicate
Like the Flash
Okay
That's okay that's really weird too because I'm looking at the data and it looks great
Like
Look at all of this wonderful data
It's just pouring in
Why isn't it updating this I probably have something just wrong with my display code
3212 sting
Suggestion here
When you get close
Get wide wide enough to look like sinks
?
Know if you were really close the rotor I guess they would be wide
I'll print out the actual the sweet time for that
Frozen's you're right in front of the thingy and we're going to get data with me running around in front of it you think maybe
That works too plugged in
Where do you want to put it sure I'll print out somebody's time timeline
Maybe over here
Oh you know what I think the disintegrator is doing the right job
Because if it was not doing the right
Rats nest of cables causing problems here
What did I'm plugged in
Oh yeah
And there goes my phone
Does it feel good
Yeah that was also Adams arm the other Lighthouse you realize
Yeah that would have thought though
I'd rather step on Charleston cyber the tire
Okay well I'll see do I still have connection
I do still have connection
So is this again
Back there
Alter running low on battery because it can't charge and stream at the same have a
Oh no it needs to be connected to the computer to provide data
Percent locked up
Three remote sings I think the disintegrator is working okay
Also if anybody knows how to actually go through old chat records on YouTube
Audi super sweet okay so maybe if you want to move around a little bit
I can't really see the screen anymore
I mean it still broken
Pass take a look at that
What's going on there
Ben says that the HBK does include a tool that makes the open scad model someone uploaded
I don't know what that means wait a minute are you going to dig me cuz like if somebody else uses their hdk to do something for me to look at
No I'm sorry made a reference saying that I'm just I'm I'm worried about
Like a
Somehow being
Owned by Valve fi
Use any aspect of the hdk
Okay I'm going to cancel this right now
So you shouldn't really close to get really close and then we'll see if we can have him big Unity
Is today
Do you going to go there that's too close maybe a foot back okay stop
Okay
I'm going with yeah I would not be able to tell what's going on be able to disambiguation it so
Dominican step like another
Foot or two back or three or four
Okay that's probably a good distance
And yes the daytime seeing would indicate that is a good distance
Disambiguation Arisen totally wrong though
Greater than
I seriously come on come back you can do it
Okay try moving around
No no no it's anything farther away but it's still closed
Hey now it's working
I was closed
It's still weird though
Huh
Also I don't even know it's Thursday to come in up here and I don't know what's up with that
I can't
That's okay we got some more info there
Cast my comment that are get rid of that
Here
SA
Okay try now
I still beta come in up there and I don't know what it's deal is
He had been reiterated that the dump close
Laser sweeps wider than sinkhole
Probably what
Problems up close
Yeah sodium
Hi Mom
But I'm also curious what the deal is with these pulses appear
So she should stand back until your code is a lot more sophisticated
I have no problem with him calling you
Don't even go farther back just gotten back from Thalia code is a little more
Oh yeah and Allen
They need a Time angle tracking disambiguous
Viva pulse but it's at the wrong time that I know that it's not a pulse but it's rather actually part of the laser sweet poke
Oh that looks cool
I still don't understand what's going on with the data ending up in these Corners here
Kind of. Kind of leaving trails
You know what I can put this inside your eyeball and then we'll see what
Yeah and then I can see where I'm actually looking
I don't even know
Oh Oh you mean if I put the camera inside your eyeball
Whatever it is
Okay so what am I looking at here why is the data coming in over here sometimes
How to learn to program without Nordstrom's, Google and YouTube and colleges
Before I even started to even think that I understood anything about programming it was
Over a year
Definitely
And that was hot with having Donuts tutorials
Does it only come in weird places when she's
I'm sorry hold on I really want to figure this out
That we have
Okay I'll kill it
Remove
Block user
Does not just block it for you
Remove
I mean that's that's new
Hayki move around some
Tell me to go in and out or just up and down looking on the wrong side of this
Okay try now
I stopped
I really need to just display other data
Okay try now
Still not working those datapoints that's like
I need is more.
It seems that the scattered points are ones that haven't received data but we don't entirely know why some of them are shoe
Shooting to the edge of the screen
Yes clearly something is dumb in my code here
Don't know what it is though
Okay try again
Stop
Moist towelette asks why we're doing this and that's perennial question
Copy paste to a to answer but
Yeah we don't even really have a good answer okay move some
Oh okay so the really Bizarro data is
Is where it mistakenly thinks
A pulse is actually a sweet
That's easy to make not be a problem
How good luck Arnie
Least it's Sunday tomorrow
Hopefully enough to work
Turn it down more
I won't be getting around some of it
Though it looked kind of choppy on your guys screen I do want to show you this is like buttery-smooth on my screen
Okay so what do you chords are is the the
From what I think is going on I'm pretty sure I've at least kind of December still not right though
Something's going on
It is a couple that they're doing and also what is that
Let's see how far I can get out
Wow Guild of you is like huge
I'm going to take this off and keep it so no I don't think you're going to get any date out there
I'm not really reverse-engineering now is a day or it's a little bit different
A step
In the reverse-engineer slowly go back and let's make
Really was tracking it okay
Crazy
I didn't get a hit my limit because this couch like
Wherever there got in the way
Okay so now that we've gotten a little bit better disambiguation
And figured out like which pulses were which
I'm thinking it might be time for me to do another dump
I'm so just wondering is anybody in this Channel right now that's up for actually trying to do some of this data analysis
Cuz that would be super sweet
Now we probably don't have a date for the next stream yet these things just kind of happened
Okay so I'm going to label these as l
I'm going to label this one as X
I'm going to label this one is L and this one is why
Okay ru
Wi-Fi disconnect from the hmd without shutting it down it gets all cranky okay
I don't think motion is right at the right now I think the headset just sitting still on the floor is probably the best
Rapport
Can you closer
So if you just dropped the height of the
Diamond like so it's more Street on
And then
Put an ice cream bowl under it
Are boxes just point that at this
You have to loosen that stuff
Try scaling up what values
Are such a
Scaling-up Oso you can actually see the details of what's going on in there so that it's easier to see the differences
Sensors
Okay I can do that so it looks like it's
Body-wise are about 160,000
The exes
About 180,000
480 -
Oh am I doing wrong
Oh actually shouldn't be 480 - for that
Taxes actually minus
Yeah I don't see why wouldn't it be
I don't know who endgame is a company
What is a big company no I mean if you want I have the others
You'll be fine.
Is it happening
I think he wants to show her
My YouTube Channel logo
Oh
If you are worried about the shirt
Well I just know for legal reasons
Hoist a ladder
Asks if we're
Reverse engineering software bit or the Fitbit physical or we're doing all our own software
No idea here
Figure out what the physical B are doing so we can write our own software for it by rmean Charles's
Strawberry cookies
Not right now
Thank you though
You're welcome
Michael suggest bringing reflective objects into the scene when looking at the data see how it changes its interesting
I don't want to mess with anything like that right now
Sorry trip
Matthew asks how did we all get together on this group project
We've all known each other through various business ventures and through
Through
Let me know how you know.
I would assume magfest his magfest Rings many people together
You haven't been to magfest to go
Okay guys that's what it looks like when you can just move it around little itty-bitty area
Hot date is so rock solid
I know other than it like losing tracking briefly
Play ephrem occlusions
And like you know whatever
Do you want to just put it down now
Oh okay that works
Concentra it until I thought of plaintiff
Exploding
It's hard to get it to look like it's not changing. That all
Because it wraps around the headset you can tell we are tipping around so we can see the ones on the battle
Yeah let's do that. Oh yeah
So you can see them around some
Stop tracking the data that's over here on the side of the headset it's towards me right now it looks like
Yeah I can't because you're there
Instead of
So I guess monitors though it keeps it in his last known good place
Yeah I don't have any
Yeah that is my tool
Aliens
Wait how did this work
Okay whatever now it's right
Alex we're not we haven't I guess technically yes we've isolated the perspective of 1
On Lighthouse but this is because we've started back from the very very
Bottom of how this whole thing works first figuring out how the Vive communicates its sensor data
Then figuring out what that sensor de to means and now we're taking that sensor data and putting it to some kind of picture
And then the next step is to figure out where the lighthouse is in 3D space relative to the vibe
And then from that we can figure out knowing that the lighthouses ficked where the five is
3D space and then from there we can do interesting things not to be that's the goal
Get be interesting things phase
Track me at 5
Misspoken Charles
I have you heard it for him
Oh great treat great Franco
Cotton gray cotton Greg are you Greg cotton are you here is that
That greasy
I don't know how long ago that was. We're still on
That's exactly what our issue is been and it's just
I know this really matters
Just kind of fur appearance's sake right now but it is producing pretty pictures
Yeah for the sake of like that I just want to sit here and marble for a minute
All of your data
On this nothing was asking
If we hide sensor points that aren't updated right so whenever we were rotating that thing around it look like it was
Is leaving the data points and like
The last known space but they were and then whenever they disappeared from visual they just don't like
Stayed
And the last
Play so they're not going away right now
I will soon
Michael in my experience with camera bright based tracking systems in a marine environment
For Navy purposes
I'll take the lighthouses thank you very much lighthouses are way better weird your marker go
Sorry I'm horrible it's right here
Why
Why anyway
I need reasons
No
Andy can you get in the way of the light
The way of the headset
Oh my goodness
Move
There we go
Okay that's totally not what I would expect it to happen but
Oh I'm dumb
What I'm doing wrong why just fading to White that makes no sense
When you get in the way of Fades to white instead of black
What's heading to White
I see caller right and then when you hold it they fade to white instead of black
White and then black
Oh
I got it backwards it's 100 -
Yeah that should do it okay try it now
Visible
Yes okay
I think we're at the point where we should start collecting all my gosh
It's so smooth
Oh and it glows when you hide them
Oh my gosh if we just keep getting this distracted we're never going to get any further
Is fun why are gooeys fun
Because they're pretty
By the way Mikey are you alright
Okay I think we should get some more data
Haha I look so cool
That was interesting
Whoa what do cuz it's tracking in the one dimension but not the other
That makes sense
This is down in the corner of its field of view
Do we have only wants to come by
I keep going lower
Running for no fade
Wait they're voting for no fade
Oh why do you want no fade like
Knowledge of when it's there when it's not there
Well if we don't say it it just
Sticks around for forever immediately disappear
Immediately cuz like Witnesses
The updated the visual display is not locked to the update of the data points so
I'll make it fade really fast though like 5 frames
You're doing 100 there
100 frames
I can't right now
Your turn omigosh we can see you wait waves and front like wave your hand in front
That is nice
Unwittingly
Okay
Knowing how close to the base station it is that's all I'm aligning its 02 straight on as you can
If you wanted to play with play with it right now
That's basically done by measuring the distance between these points can you move it closer and you'll see they get bigger
Method of the width between the broken
As you get further away this whole image will get smaller and that's how you would calculate the distance
It's not actually measuring time-of-flight right Springs of one thing I don't know if Alan if you're still here
One thing I was curious that looks really cool when you Valeri Al-Anon one thing I was curious about
One of the things from the lighthouse redox people they think that you have a fair bit of analog circuitry that kind of
Resolves the length of the pulses and I'm curious if you think not having like the the diode in
The greater the whatever you called on the output to prevent a whole bunch of pulses but instead if I were to interpret that and software
If I'd be able to get better information about when the edges begin and end just a thought
I'm toying with trying to do that but
For all I know with everything else that you guys keep doing the super clever you probably figured out something way better than that
If you can get behind me you can see the screen off sink
Ono is this off sync though
TV
The one of the things a little bit weird here is the DNC picture that you see here is actually the insteon on
John Adams computer
To my computer so everything you're seeing on this is
A little bit behind
What reality is Lighthouse you should totally
Then if and only if I'm going to implement it on the esp3
Does that mean VSP lighthouse
Call maybe maybe we have a different definition for the term ESP Lighthouse means
Right that's what my tsp lighthouse
I'm trying to figure out how I can play the drums
But it doesn't really have a nice lovers I can use for like my finger sticking
Add time
Got to get your unpaid expressive advertisements
Context you mean it
What I wanted 200 no I do not want to take the analog values at 48 MHz coming into the
The photodiodes I did want to look at is just the Amplified photodiode thing with a like a Schmitt trigger gauge
So every single pulse at the 1.8 MHz I'll be able to actually see the individual pulses
This video is not brought to you by espressive I just think they're that cool
It is actually brought to you by unity Technologies
Units hyphen named before Unity with a thing
I don't know actually 2005 before Eric
Yeah I think that 2005 was before unity game engine was the thing you were called Unity still hope he gets bought
The new name
Easier to tell over the phone
Is this someone else's
So
You need the envelope timing or else the performance will be terrible
Envelope timing
I think you guys have a word for this
That is not in my vocabulary for this project right now
Found in 2004
Tell you what I'm going to go record some data now and I'm going to upload it so you guys can all get the data
I thought sitting try to move a little bit to get some more LEDs and you Michael asks what are the second and third integers
Following the timestamp indicate
You seems the first one is sensor ID
But the second one is unclear
Okay so whenever I received a sweep like coming from the the laser on the
On the lighthouse like
What
Suggested a much worse name for a new company forwards
50s
I want that
I'm going to take this I'm going to update the thread with it
Probably just so you know
This right here this one thing that you asked about the 012344 a lot more information about that
What is over at the Lighthouse redox if you look under light emissions
So that that Wiki there has the information on what the jnk pulses do
Which is based on
I think was Ben was saying something about that actually matter in a way that I'm confused by
Cuz I would have expected it to been rotor
So I don't know
Oh no I see ya 3000 or 3500
For 4,000 or 4,500 it just ran into funny order so they aren't they are actually the jna
MK pulses
JK
Let's take some of the state of for you guys
Sensor analog Hardware is very important for the system centroid resolution
No I understand that
I do understand that the center Hardware the analog Parts going to be important
What I'm wondering
Company name
You only live once
Oh
No More Words
Uppercase is that is that what you were thinking he meant literally four words all uppercase
Okay
Then says it's from the Rocket Jump worst Wi-Fi password ever shorts ketchup something
What I was thinking
Was like the top diagram there looking at the the individual on-and-off sat the
Hold on
Was looking at the individual on-and-off is 1 / 1.8 MHz thing
I can see that very clearly
But the idea would be to actually look at all of the ons and all of the offs
When you receiving the high-frequency data and that would include during a sweep
I don't know if it's actually legit like idea but that's one of the things I was thinking I'm definitely not coming
Get that for another couple weeks
Island
Like Ireland
Okay right now I'm recording some new track data. CSV for you guys so this is the same as before
Keonda
Oh yeah now it's a single Lighthouse and it's pointed straight at the vibe the five is tilted and turned a little bit and all
But the goal for clearly we're not going to get to doing this tonight but the goal for the next couple days
This is going to be to take the days I'm recording now and the config that I have which is kind of Wrong by the way
Play Alan and Ben if there's any way to get our config back with like itself
We want our config back
Any rate taking this data and figuring out how to
To do that
Final Street
Stream
Bandwidth YouTube allows final stream secret BBC cameras
Oh that would be neat we have plenty of bandwidth at home we need to do that
Oh like multiple channels that be weird you have one that's just constantly streaming what the Vive cease
As you like swing it around what is the device serial number
Where is the bottle you have no idea how much we want this
Msconfig back nevermind okay
Well we've got your serial number
Midnight
How are you streaming
Oh hi Mark
Freezing
They're using my phone Verizon has really good coverage up here really good coverage I get there
30 MB down 14 or 15 up but now I'm only getting two and a half
But that's funny
I'm just wondering is anybody in chat right now who's actually willing to take a look at the state and try to help process it
And by the way bonus points if you do it in C in a way that I can speed up
Actually wait no it doesn't even matter if we're trying to find location lighthouses this could be in like any language because once
Is the calibration is only done once once we have the calibration we know where the lighthouses then it's
Easiest pie from there because once that date is provided I'm pretty sure we can use that dated then to go
Figure out where the vibe is and everything else
I was leaning over formica shouldn't be leaning over for the mic at all and totally hear you from there okay well I move away from the mic to breathe
So
Well they can hear you breathing in anyway
That's not me breathing in
Somebody asked a question
Is Java acceptable for what
Don't want to take Java code
Cuz I don't want to have to cuz not like you even have Java
Oh yes I'm just asking I guess for the calibration but you know python
Someone was asking what the config file was and what does it do when Lars says that we Act
Accidentally are device yes we accidentally the whole device
Okay Paul II macaroni with you no no
No Java
Do I have mono
Do you want I have mono so if you do write it in c-sharp and you use like only the most basic
Basic things all except C sharp
No Purl nobody will be able to read it and understand what is going on
I can at least read C sharp
LOL
Okay Mack 33
Oh wait what
No stop just seriously guys CC Sharpie no PHP
Python that kind of thing
Preferably C or C plus plus preferably State the tasks
Typically so this is what what I'm hoping you guys will be able to do over the next next week I think I'm going to
I try to make these live streams on the weekends though I won't be able to make every weekend I think I'm going to
Avoid them during the week is that was not as much fun your goal will be able to take
This new tracking
Okay
Whoa what
Is going to be able to take this new track data
Which contains the the
X and Y or a J & K
Codes
For the headset
Coming from a single Lighthouse so the idea is that if we look at this picture
Let's do that again this
He said and then brought up the picture here if we take a look at this. This contains is the
The X and Y are the J&K codes for where all of the LEDs are
And that leading sorry of where all of the LEDs are and
Take this config file although it's not perfect
This initial hmb data. Whatever it is away that's the wrong thing
And
That's one hmd points
No I want to click on it
Why can't I click on that
Uploading
Whatever I'm going to just upload that again
Buses are curious why there's one extra sensor on the right presumably in that
That image scroll up
Such as you talking about
Not the one you made the months
Did he delete it
Oh here it is
I don't see any others
Alex Wright yeah
So
This is the
Dated a tracking here
Any rate your goal will be to take this data in the the new track data
And use the initial hmd data in order to generate or to calculate the location of the
The camera on the light so
The goal will be to based on the lighthouse data or specific times
Look I'm not good at this
Figure out the the position of the lighthouse
From the position or the timing that we get and the the
Whatever it is the
The positions of all the photodiodes on the hmd
Actually get the coating that tonight but that's definitely not happening
Anything else guys you can think of
Actually like
123456789
10 11 12 13 14 15 16 sensors on one side
Yasobi 16 + 16
It's not being directly head-on with the camera is all
I don't know what the normal to be used for I'm sure that Ben and Alan can tell us more about what
What they're used for I would assume that they're used for occlusion as in
If a given sensor is pointed away from a camera
We can ignore it so then what that would mean it's like if you had a mirror or something reflective on one side
Side of the room and it was reflecting the pulse code it would be able to throw that out I'm guessing I don't I don't actually know if that's the case
That would that would also work for a while
Going guy when I mention using this for Naval purposes that
That would be how you would make it not show up when it bounces off the water
The lasers
Just some ideas that I had about the state of
It's like saying like the top picture if you're if you're spot-on like if your angle and everything of where the LIE
Lighthouses pointed
Matches up with the dissenters and you know you have to move the lighthouse Inn
If say it's off to one side you're going to have to slide the lighthouse down
But to make things a little bit more confusing
Just like this
And
And say the problem is actually rotation
It actually looks the same but it is going to be different because you're going to have more than two
Points to resolve so that should help resolve the difference between
A rotation and a translation
Can you guys think of anything else or should I mean I'm not going I know I'm not like awake enough to try to
This is going to be easy
We down like that
There are pretty lights and stuff
Yeah ice cream
I want to question a lot of questions
Probably
Love the same questions when people come in
We're only using the light sensor data right now
Right now the goal is to use the light sensor data to figure out where the lighthouse is in 3
3D space
Ck2 says this will not be easy
Alan I know this won't be easy but I tried doing this before with the webcam
And I discovered how awful that was
And I almost got it to work
So
This can't be anywhere near as bad as a webcam
Because
A webcam has Barrel Distortion and everything else messed up
These lighthouses
Are beautiful
There is no Barrel distortion
There is no none of this mess
It simply tells you the angle
In basically X&Y coming out of the lighthouse where a given thing is
And that's beautiful
That's so beautiful
Is it too loud
I don't think so okay
3D space relative
Harassing where in three space would you say
That you'd be measuring the lighthouse relative to
Collective live his dream yes it is to pull out my hair
I'm sorry what did you ask
Coordinate system the lighthouses would be measured in based upon this data
How's the lighthouse would be measured so assume that
Is I think the degenerate case would be assuming that the the the points on the hmdr
Global space
So that this would be assuming that the headset is at 0-0 and pointed whichever way the headset is is pointed
I'm in global space XYZ first second third assuming that
Figure out where the camera is and where it's pointed and I guess I could use a quaternion or oil
Miller angles wouldn't quite make sense it would have to be like a simultaneous transform of both X and Y in the Euler angles
Which is an Oiler angles then it's just X&Y microphone
Then I can talk to you guys hear ye
Curve of The Bean
Be referring to with the white whale
But I just don't think it is we're doing I don't think exact enough stuff that we need to worry about that we're not doing like molecular
Spectroscopy and have to worry about these little tiny things we're just trying to get like
A general data down to probably what like a centimeter Maybe
Well we're going to have to get the lighthouse position well may I get to cm
What is centimeter be good enough
Englewood matter a lot
A lot position I guess it would matter a lot but not a whole lot
Stop like these right light waves are NM AR-15 right and it's a very least like
Gitaran the data I don't know if you guys were watching today too but it's not very much Jitter like
I don't know if it's really that accurate
But I think it is
One thing I did want to mention is that a while ago when I did the the the pulse codes to Black X
Am I did spend a little bit of effort trying to figure out the math to
To getting the the time codes divided right
So the offset from and the the DePaul time
I'm trying to get them so it was actually like the center of the the hit not the edge
Edgewater back to buy being in the center of the hit it would be Wednesday the single Sweet Thing by
Until I could be starting here in ending here I'm giving you this time right here in the middle
By doing that it means that
Won't be like
Oh yeah to a certain amount and yeah it'll just be like no it's
Rye tell you the times now it's it should I'm sure I'm a little bit wrong too
Katalin Street
Yeah it's Alan here is thinking that we are going to need to worry about I think all those small differences
But I think for our purposes
Of the final
Projects or projects here since we are going to make it super lightweight worrying about that kind of Eric Russians good
How to make it heavier right
And so if we just say this. Is good enough for our purposes
I think one of the biggest things I'm going to have to focus on here is is lightning
Getting this off the ground in awful is way more important to me than making it good so
It doesn't have to track read it's just got to work kind of and then hopefully other people are going to
Maybe even need willing to go back and try to actually fix this and do the parts the right way
I'm trying to get more of a framework out of this as soon as possible
Rather than the every single detail
Exactly Shogun
Powell yeah I really think was we get enough data we can just kind of normalize a lot of it
I mean there might be inaccuracies but I don't know
Isn't divided code open source
Is the Viper code open source
There's 50 sosv Vive Libre that's open source
But
Actually it's interesting you know you guys we might want to just copy off of some of what the Osos VR Vive Libre people
You are doing
But I
Alan says you can get it roughly working with approximation approximately working
The osr Vive open the website
Svr
Right now we don't want to be good right now
As
Is we'll always points out
There's a thing that's a thousand times better than good code and its functional code
I don't know maybe there is a S5 control
Alan says they're just wrapping openvr beliefs no I think that's most VR
Survive is rapping openvr
But I think that osvr Vive Libre is actually trying to read the data straight from the 80s
Straight from the vibe
Cell
Lie cuz iOS VR Vive Libras actually doing things with like live USB and connecting to it and I kind of got
A lot of the info that we used to open up the connection how to do all that from osvr Vive Libre
Oh yeah currently they are only actually doing I am you tracking but they have a lot of stuff in here
That I don't understand because there's entirely too many lines of code
And I just I just
When it's when I start seeing like structures of
Auto sample pointer
Stuff that's in headers and yeah I'm not a C+ plus programmer anymore
There was a time but that that's long ago
I've never used the Tuple in my life
I kind of have an idea as to what it means
But
I guess I do know what it means but
Yeah
I'm not going to
Dig through this
This project is not intended to like make boatloads of money for the next big theme thing
Could we
Please
I mean like any money
Let's try to like make the the the funky Hardware that we want to make first
Yeah
Wrap it up
Encryption
Fgb hrl says this sort of stuff it's just strange situation talking
Allen is this stuff nd8 I mean I take it bailed doesn't care that much if this is opened up right
I'm assuming you would have encrypted this channel otherwise
I would love to hear a statement from from Allan or bad on this
But I'm I'm so appreciative that they're willing to play ball with you know somebody just wanting to have fun with this and mess around
Wait one minute
Latency of the stream is really good
How
In one box that I'm unaware of I'm not under any nda's at all with valve
Or or HTC or anything like that so
I don't think this is a problem
Alan says quote
What you are doing is fine by me
I'm going to copy and paste that out
No no actually would be in the Stream are you can write the time in the Stream that it was
What is the stream say TimeWise for you guys like look at it I think it says that for every 1440
Can somebody else right in the fish at what time the stream is at for you guys
Its 4:48 but we started recording and stopped recording and started recording it stopped recording so I don't know
It kept that the whole while
I'm pretty sure that's what it actually is
Live Oak
Okay don't worry about it when it gets all edited for Life release
Oh my God
Maybe it's that means
They just capitalizing doesn't work
I don't know
I don't think it's good it's not doing what you're doing and then I
Tried to do something else put user in timeout
Okay so there's no way to actually know sometime
Okay
Restring 45 hours last time
Yeah also one of the thing I think that is
I don't know if a lot of people are going to go out and buy Vibes because of the stream and this particular project but I'd like to believe that
By the end of this there's going to be a couple people who got fives that wouldn't have gotten them otherwise
Okay I think we're just we're done right let's just
Close up shop anything anybody have anything else specific to this project please take a
Discussion in issue number 3 on the
Live survive
Issue Number 3 is where we will discuss reading in this tracking data and trying to resolve the position
Of the lighthouse and orientation of the lighthouse
Relative to the HMV being in 00
And determine the lighthouse position cuz after that we can determine the lighthouse position
It's
Hard but it's the next epiphora we can actually start tracking things with the lighthouses
Hey Alban
Awesome get the Vive
Frank Russell darkness and potentially
Okay so looks like valve is selling some Vibes because of this awesome attitude that they're taking towards this
I'm sure more than a few
Not just here but everywhere
Yes we get IDs for each sensor position data without hmd being connected
So my my end goal that I'm not going to be very specific
About would require while I wouldn't require but it would be really convenient if I could get the
Mission data from my own things
Without the without the agency being connected so I'm really hoping that that that's a feature
That stays
I should wait no can if I turn off the hmd will that
It does but what if I build my own Hardware
Looks like the lighthouses still blinking blinking
I can see the little laser is doing their laser thing
Ben do you really believe that the work we've done on the wireless controller is that bad
Water diet
Knowing has been dead the water has not run
Cuz we're managing this Charles
Yes it's just
Having a hard time
Generating pressure so it's not staying on because that switches horrible
Although to be fair but did stay out of my burn out the motor so
Maybe.
So if I understand correctly it still impractical.
Program the lasers to always attempted blind to the user
Class
Fast to lasers
Just throw in the lasers to attempt a blind that users like a hardware thing you'd be able to produce something
Check to make sure the toilet is not like leaking leaking like
Alright alright
Would like to use lighthouses in for tracking arbitrary objects idealia and I have both setup go to real-world site
Can you just turn off the toilet right now
Pop-up to lighthouses in Saipan
Why do bats what we're getting into it's Angelique routine
Running continuously
Killing the water then
When you replace the toilet did you replace the flushing mechanism as well or did you
Use the same mechanism for the ancient toilet cuz it looks pretty ancient inside there
Why are we doing what
If the shut-off valve I can lift up on the shut-off valve as hard as I want it does not show
Shut off that's not good okay s means we just need to keep turning off the toilet and today you need to manually turn
Actually you know your dad has like five different toilet pieces down the thumb instead
I'll wait
I have a story for everyone
Oh my gosh guys what is happening right now
Done with the silliness so
Are you doing oh we're done with the coding yes let's see you can handle this
Because we're getting so guys we used to come to my parent's cabin to play rock band and we have a projector
You're up there
Andrea project onto this wall over here
And we would just play Rock Band like all weekend long and one time
We forgot the drum pedal
Oh and
Now get this
I was like oh no we can't play Rock Band cuz there's no drum pedal I go to the shed downstairs and sitting on a Shelf
Is this there is not not this I put this together there is a spring
In in the Shelf there was on the Shelf there was the spring the washers the screws funny little
Metal plate thing and this copper wire and a hinge it was sitting all on a shelf to go
Together in the last person that was there was my grandfather before he died
So my grandfather
Like more than 5 years previous to put all of these things on a shelf all together for me to make this
Rock band pedal so we can play rock band at the cabin
So
I don't know I just thought that was a pretty cool story
It was meant to be yeah yeah it was you wanted to do guitar didn't you
Guitar
Guitar string broke
Baltimore Maryland
ESP 8622 nobody's supposed to know about the 8622 yet
Hey maybe next time we do like our along streams we can have like Charles commercial breaks where we do like a little music break
Well I wanted to have Max play the guitar but
I'm working on I have original stuff
No
Okay. Or like a public domain so like that one
One more thing
Strata
Probably the only person who's actually giving me any money or material resources is Unity Technologies
My secret source for the USPS I can't tell you where my secret
Source to get all of my esps is I'm really sorry
Lighthouse tracked guitars that would be pretty cool
But that's not the idea that I was going after I'll tell you that it's not what I what my angle is
That would be okay
Could you imagine actually seeing the drum set and the drumsticks while you're doing it in VR
Okay I guess I wasn't as cool as I thought it was
Emma I might even see something you're saying some some piece
Nope not doing enough PJ won't touch it
Sorry John John Moriarty also works for Unity Technologies and no we did not bring the cool
Find the cabinet might have gotten damaged
We see if I can pull
A picture of those the cool sign
I know the girls will be so much fun with it rock band t r i know right that's what I care about
Mickens and unity Unity 3D
People open Facebook here
Oh did I already do it
NPR
IMAX
Can you check on Monday I'm going to pull up the
Bathroom bathroom
Give me a second here oh boy there's a lot of people talking
Music pr project o
Music VR project
It's a concert stuff
Manistee literally was drunk thing I don't you try it I'll be fine I'd love to do that
How do I reattach the
Would you guys want like
A retiring on air drumming or would you want like actual physical 6 in your hand and you like
Hit the air like I'm a rock bands like if it's very physical like experience I don't really know how this VR thing would work out
Aerodrums
Might my actual goal isn't showing the picture
You definitely cheats on how to use a finger rolls instead of
Rely on the pod
Where is I'm trying to find another picture of the sign
Drums without a story passed the interesting bits
90s
Attacks
Attach 625 controllers with tape
Oh I know no that's terrible that's why I'm trying to solve this
Controllers
Actually just email
My degree in computer engineering I am kind of qualified to be a PGA Pro
Programmer and do vlsi work however I absolutely hate it so
I have definitely done a lot of verilogue in school I have not done a line of verilogue since I don't intend to change that
Jermaine requires haptics to be done properly which is probably super obvious
No I don't
Things like rolling are impossible Buzz rolling is impossible without a tie open rolls are one hundred percent possible without it though
Because you use like your fingers here in order to feel like control an open roll
They're on the floor behind the finger yacht call and get them
Down behind the
Nope there
Stick with sensors
And you could put haptic feedback if you wanted it but
Yeah I like tactile feedback it's what makes them so enjoyable but
You could do most all of it except for Buzz stuff
I guess trying to express like the different types of runs like sandstedt clicks would be kind of hard to
Perfect oh no
Hindi points. CSV. Zip did not go
Please Charles watch one minute we don't really have a lot of bandwidth to spare otherwise I totally blow it up
Pull what up their drums video I really rather not
Right now streaming
Your mother's dead pretty much
Also just might be like entirely different types of instruments you might be able to even make this br.
Imagine what theremin hero is going to do when this gets to him
Don't you guys haven't seen theremin Heroes Channel at the pretty cool Channel
But so as far as Air Jordans go for what I know I don't know
Ceragem sing it
But there's a
Was the camera here
There's a rolling to relight can you use this this part of your fingers to like make it bounce
You going to go really really fast but like I don't even have a
Service here to be able to create that noise you can't do that without the hafter without
A bouncy rubber rubber surface or a sneer service or something but
And open role is totally possible
Without a surface
Why can I no longer get the points data
You guys see anything wrong here
I did a lot of drama in high school
It was a lot of fun
What's going on why can I not why is it not happening
Oh my gosh
What is up with this there should be model points in there
Lighthouses still one?
No no the lineup shouldn't matter I'm just trying to pull the config again because I realized I didn't upload the HMV points
He blew it again I did not just blow away the config again I just did not but I did not do it we
We have a backup config that we've been using we can use that but I want to know why it's not reading it
Why is it not reading the config
My man Catonsville high school required a lot a lot a lot of pot paradiddles between snare drum and cowbell sound awesome
Quick recap
I think we're going to be done soon so we can do the recap as we're wrapping up well right now I realized I forgot to
Include a bunch of the whatever the this file that didn't upload
Right here
Battle that apparently I didn't upload and I apparently deleted or something
And for some reason I can't seem to get it anymore
I'm not sure why
A reasonably large marshmallows anyone
I could not fit know
No show the camera
We have giant marshmallows
Okay that's enough
Why am I not able to get those hey wait nope
I am I not able to get the data
What is going on
No the data still there
Model points is still a thing
Why am I not able to read it
What is going on
Why is this broken
61 of them what's wrong
Is VR Minecraft the same Oculus Rift
Adam do you know is is VR Minecraft the thing
Yes VR Minecraft is a thing I've not yet figured out how to actually get it working
Adam said he could not figure out how to get it working oh my gosh that's a lot of errors
Oh that makes sense cuz you know it's their thing
Hololens is not VR
I'm actually navion AR stuff for hololens more than anything but it's expensive
I was even in line to get one I like applied for the developer one whenever it was so close and they're like how you can get one and then I saw
The person I was like no I can't
Are people actually watchmecode
Five craft
In the Stream
No
The only way I can get my pool
That laptop
You can scroll up
Are over
Are you guys okay
Trying to figure out how I messed this up
People wearing Google Glass around like I always tried to Google Glass and it was just it's not
Robust
Like he was kind of cool but it was more I feel like gimmicky I'll 57 people
Gas with bottled water
Model point it's right there why can't you find a computer
Don't want to attract new
Why can't I find it
Hydrocat says Charles GTB won't make it?
I don't know I just it's easier for me to run valgrind real quick
Like I can run it and kill it running kill it running killer wears dccu access to typing like quit it's an extra step
Little annoyed right now understand
Hi
What is wrong
You're the Oculus just got controllers again we got them at the house that I'm living in right now and
It was a good experience
I'm going to put that one back
What does CLR mean I don't know
How much are cool people knowing
Point of my username
Oh it's just my first name or first initial middle initial last name
Yeah I was like I don't know how much you're comfortable saying whatever its initial
Yeah
Yeah Charles and I don't know Anna is lore nobody knows
Maybe that's what it is
Nobody
Charles nobody lure
Why isn't this code working I don't know what it is
I can't even think of it in name
Ned
It is not mad
You only get one choice or 11 guess
People in chat when ask they can ask Adam. Adam
Question in his Adams question was Nathan it's not Nathan
No it's not Noah
Nick
Norbert
It is not Nick
Barry said no to Nathaniel I think
I assume Nathan Nathaniel be the same thing
Homer J Simpson is just in like 10 or something
Nolan no
Angie
Which 57 guess
Snake necklace Arsenio
It's not Nick
I don't give away your necklace guys
Norm's though it's not a normal
It's not Nigel
Nicholas it's not Norman
It is Nicholas
Why is my Json EQ failing
Lancer
Positioning system was based on huge magnet somehow
Oh that's cool like a stem system
Also there is a really cool way that you can also do positioning called stem I don't actually know what it means but what it does
Is it uses magnetic fields in a Polarises at this way than this way than this way than this way than this way in this way
By looking at the dude like having a thing in 3D space and looking at the change of the magnetic flux as you change the magnetic flux
In 3D space it can tell where it is really neat
But not anywhere near as needed this Lighthouse stuff
I love you let me figure out why this isn't working first and then I'll log off
Wait are you back to work and no I something's I accident I don't know what I did with the duddy
Modify I deleted the file to get help with all the points in it
And I tried using I realized I didn't have it
And then it didn't appear to get abs without nobody has the hmd points file
And means that my other way I'm parsing all this is broken and I got to figure out why that is Princess call or the
Json eqbgl2q is not returning zero when it should
Like this here totally
Wait I + 1
Call a John
John
Residents wouldn't have anywhere near that area
There is actually a device made by razor
The Sixth Sense Hydra
Yeah the Sixth Sense Hydra that actually used magnetometers and a law
Large ball that created changes in magnetic flux
The one that I bought on eBay with brick
0 returned zero
That's right
Got Carol what did you download
Michael says that it wasn't even razors thing six senses separate company that made it
I should say you should start
Type defining your function
Where where is there a problem with the type to improperly type to find function pointer
John says they downloaded initial hmb data. Text that yours Charles
They download it from you
We've been doing this for a while Matthew Jones yeah that would be me but that would be
The old data
Let me delete this cuz this is wrong
California Matthew Jones City find the
Pretty good to me
The stream is about collecting data
And I'm just saying that like data
From From The Towers
And then rendering that light data in
Whatever that was that you had going before I don't know what it was on this live
So before we were trying to collect the data from the headset
And parse it tell us where the location of all the the sensors were on the helmet
So now I've actually posted in the channel
The hmd points and the the new tracking data
I'm so I'm actually going to work on this problem at the same time as everyone else but
Just wanted to let you guys
Have a crack at A2 since
Chances are you guys are going to able to come up with a better solution than I am because I was known as the math built
Electron ashes question
Is the code something that is screwed up in the latest version does it not get backed up on each commit to
I don't actually know what happened but it works now so I'm not going to worry about it
?
Yeah that change that changed
Yeah that this is a much better organizational just met this
I don't think the Power Glove used anything worth talking about not even electron not even ultrasonic transducers
I think one of the problems was I haven't been committing enough
Which I'm really bad at anyway especially with get I'm really bad at it with gate with some Persian I would like to make a new versions all the time
Charles isn't nearly committed enough
Huh
Okay everything is now in Issue Number 3 and I have the the coat in there so
I think it's time to go guys
I'm sorry
Although by the way
Trying to make the Power Glove work with the Vive seems like a pretty honorable
Saying I might I might actually try for that cuz I do have a video where I totally hack the snot out of a
A Nintendo zapper
You're curious just look up seeing Laura Nintendo zapper I had a lot of fun with that one
Congress
Oh
Okay goodbye Noah
Goodbye everyone
Goodnight bleep Pavel
The way over there
Where you're at least going to do it again
Early at this point
David Aaron do this again
We might be doing it
I mean I don't know weekends whenever I'm free
Some weekends
Okay