Okay hey everybody Welcome to the fourth live stream of me hacking
Well not just me but all you guys hacking the the HTC Vive
PNC we were a little bit of that is true
We've been doing over the last couple times is we had been trying to well first of all get access to the watch
Fan controller be able to read the the times coming off of that then it worked after
A bunch of help from Ben and the rest of the guys over at valve I feel kind of a fairly reverse-engineering when you get there
Map of the company who made it and we've been trying to figure out the position of the lighthouses they
Based on this position of the of the headset
Stop about the factory config much much thanks to then
And HTC is apparently HTC did keep a copy of my key
Configuration so I was able to actually get that copy of the configuration
And put it back on the headset and it tracks just fine
Looks like it worked and on top of that I did actually get the new positions
Normals of my headset up on up on to get Hub thing so if you
He go to the GitHub
What is it the table live survive Issue Number 3
You can actually see that yes then came through with the email to HTC and
Nhtc did have the the my configuration still there so that's really good
Good news if you want to get the points that were operating with you can totally get that and
And see if I can get the normals somewhere here
I also took the normal for my headset which I found out is kind of important
I have a my program totally did not work
Work that well it was telling me like lighthouses will be under the floor and all this other stuff until I started taking into consideration
The normals and what I did with the normals was
Draw little thing here
If I have a
If I had a a camera position that I was going to try to go to and so say for whatever
Reason my algorithm thought the camera was down here even though the sensor has a normal pointing up that way
Because the cameras behind the normal of the sensor I can now no that's not it that's not
Not a good tracking point because there's no way for this Lighthouse be able to cast a ray
Onto the sensor for the sensor to see it if the sensors pointing the wrong way I'm so soon as I did that
I was able to resolve much better the where where I thought the lighthouses
Today some of the things I really wanted to dig into this time
Or I wanted to find out first of all from you guys if anyone in chat
Nose forget a copy of the the positions and normals from the
From the from the Watchmen so with that is
On these controllers right here I want to know
If anybody knows where to get a copy of the thing I think I saw it online somewhere but I just don't know where
But the thing that says where the location of all of these points are and their normals, now come
And really helpful I think because for my algorithm if I just have the Vive and I'm trying to figure out the positions
The fall of the lighthouses based on only the Vive it's kind of hard because there's about a maybe
Get two or three DM area easily two or three decimals about 2 or 3 DM
Really can't figure out where exactly the lighthouses within so
First bring up that program and I'll run
Make sure I can run it I didn't even have not tried yet on this this user account
Under Tools clean test to make
Correct
HMV points
You guys want to see this how you guys can play along with this tool I did post the files in the issue so
So I'm going to go download them
So correct H&B points the next one is hmd
Normals can I go download that
And that's downloaded what's the last one test 5 was I actually already on test 5
I don't know all I have is test for
She's at the last one I posted I guess we'll use test for
Fixed your cursor how did you get it it's a totally different setting that was not highlight
It changed it definitely does not highlight only the things that you've changed it was use local kersal
Use local cursor is false so you guys know that use local cursor equals
Apparently it's the thing another option I don't remember what flags I passed this
I'll see if I can
So this when I say x 11 TNC no x no X damage Quaker mode show cursor
So this is the plan that I use for my client
The fact what you missed was the fact that we spent the first 15 minutes the livestream trying to figure out how to show the
The cursor on the actual live streams that was a little bit embarrassing
Yeah back to work now though are you
You guys in chat able to monitor seeing what's happening
Brandon okay
From test 5:05 I mistyped that test
4K can't open to lighthouses test data
That really
Can't open
20 test four
Four. CSV what did I miss type
Charleston modified shootout the screen to the hackerspace bombers you absolutely should pass the stream out to anybody
What do you think of
See that looks like a reasonable answer so
What is programmed as right now I guess I should go over kind of an overview of how I decided to tackle the problem
And let you guys know that the the problem
Dissolution doesn't really work out as well as I thought it would explain why I think that's the case
And we'll talk a little bit about some of the things that we can do to try to make it a little bit better so
I have a see if I can get this
Have some way of holding this here
There anything rated you can find for me hey give me a board game box
Accomplishing counter
I don't have any good oscilloscope splitting around downstairs today
Do you know who we will be explaining this lighthouse
Thing on the game of life here okay anyway
So what I had set off was I had the the
The system setup where I had the head-mounted display with all of its wonderful photodiodes on it and I
I have two lighthouses
Now for those of you I know somebody said Lighthouse? Lighthouses are
The funny black boxes that come with the buy system that just fits emit infrared out into the sea
So what they actually do with Phil sweep laser this way on one axis and
I'll sweep it this way on the other access and it's creating a plane of a laser-like swooping down but between
Those two I can have an imaginary point that comes out from the lighthouse into a point on the
Into the appoint on the heads mouth display I have a magic wand that comes out of this and go through it
Point on the head-mounted display so what I wanted to do was I want to find the the lighthouses
In a coordinate frame that starts in the center of the the bad mouth display so
You can actually have a shot at seeing that
That's only awkward but
Rrr
Center is located and we're going to figure out where the lighthouse
Houses are relative to that I'm so my first approach was to take these cameras and then moved
Everywhere in 3D space just everywhere everywhere I can think of and then
Or eat them in all sorts of random directions until I found a direction that kind of work
This is really terrible
This is
Really
Really terrible because you have to search in Six Dimensions because there's six degrees of freedom
And that takes a while it worked but it took quite a while into that was terrible so then the next thing I
I did was I decided to start using some linear algebra so I can try the Cameron all these different locations and then
Use the magic of linear algebra to get the camera to point at the head-mounted display and then I will go
Go through each of the different photodiodes that were visible to the camera and figure out well how off would it be if the camera was right
Right here
So that worked a lot better but I can't seem to reliably get
Get the position of the of the lighthouses all that accurate
That reliably so let's let's first start bye weeks play
Playing what it was like how if I if I say lighthouses here and I want to point it at the head-mounted splay and
I haven't oriented so
From the lighthouses point of view it's going to be pointed off in the middle of nowhere land so
The first we have to get the lighthouse here to point at the head-mounted display
The way that we actually do that is through the magic of some aqua turn Ian's here and
What I mean is I right now if I'm a lighthouse start on a new page here
Find the lighthouse I'm pointed up by default like I'm just going to say this direction is Plus
The terrible drawing there and
What I'm going to try those I have a head not display down here
All these little dots on it and I want to be able to find out how would I have to rotate the lighthouse
Get it the point over there and what I can do is I can draw than imaginary Ray
That's going in the direction that this thing thinks it sees a light and I'm going to draw an imaginary race
From where this Lighthouse is to the point that it should be intersecting and then what I can do
If I can take the cross product of these two factors and that will give me an Access and in this case
Out of the page so it'll give me an axis to rotate about which is out of the page and
But I can do is I can take that's the cross product cross
Cross product and then I can find out how much it needs to
Rotate find out this angle here by using the.
Product
Now by using these two things I can help point the head-mounted display at the at the story
The Lighthouse at the head-mounted display so what I ended up getting is something where would have
Effectively show a bunch of dots for the head-mounted display and a bunch of God Square
It's thought they would be but they would be oriented all wrong and so I have to buy the way
The point I was pointing out is now dead on but now I have to go rotated a bunch more and rotated around
And try to get it to the where is pointed and that access is exactly where it would need to be pointed
Based on that location that is currently at in this this worked actually relatively
Well and was relatively fast and in fact I guess I should run it
And show you guys with some of this looks like so at the end of the program
Right here I have the output and so what this shows is the position that the
He'd had mouth display was actually in and the position in imagespace that we think we were pointing at
So nice from the point of view of the
Of the camera calc
I'm just paste it in here
And I'm going to grab this so I'm going to show you guys so this is from what
My thing thinks the best location is and so what for
That's some of the points on a head-mounted display and you can see they the point actually kind of line up to what the head-mounted
Play really is I'm so if you look here you can see based on this it is getting better
It is getting some of the points on one of the sides of the head Mount display so that's what those are
And then fix my access a little bit here
.004 okay then I cannot
Also show the other data range so let's add new column here x-values
Film y values hoops
My values boom okay and so now we can see that
Where the camera where the watch where the lighthouse
From their point of view again the lighthouse has no way of seeing anything but it does have a point of view from its point of view
The the red dots are where it thinks it sees the the dots on the vine
Pfizer and the blue dots are where they should be so we can see here the lighthouse in the visor
Kind of lined up but really not that well and there's this one point that's just off in the middle of nowhere land
And we can look at it from the other lighthouses point of view as well so right
Now I'm looking at the El Lighthouse which is the one that's closest to me the one up there I'm going to nail look at the
The our Lighthouse take a look at that one save
Ron
So now from the right Lifehouse is point of view
Oh I do I delete that area see that again
And we're going to fix our
Are axis so that we can actually see everything so now this
Blinds up extremely well have a fairly High degree of confidence that it figured out where the lighthouse was pretty well
Now the only problem is that because the
Angle is so narrow on because from the lighthouses point of view the
The the the thing though the head melt display so we have a lighthouse
Over here and it's looking out into my my living room floor
I've had male display over here with some sensors on it from this thing's point-of-view
That's a really long way away and those are very very tightly placed so
All of those those dots right there are very very tightly coupled so
If it's looking to Target on that one and it thinks it's it's whizzing by like that it's pretty good
But you know this thing could be moving in or out by 5 easily decimeters
I would have no idea so that's one place where this algorithm is definitely coming up short
But other than that it seems like it's getting at least a rough estimate so I don't know
Exactly how we're going to solve this yet but I would imagine some of it might have to do with using the
The Watchdog controllers here and here to somewhere else so they
That you can have a wider range in order to calibrate based on the only problem is we don't know where these
These controllers are so we would have to look at it from to Lighthouse Point of View and
By doing that maybe will be able to resolve a little bit better figure out exactly
See what's really going on there and I've been pretty much straight through anybody
Can't you just get the time between the sensors or
Hit by The Sweep since you know the sweep speed calculate angle
Nissan The Sweep time the sweep speed from this Lighthouse is point of view
What angle it sat for the head-mounted display right there
So, things that I really wanted to approach
I don't know if anybody keeps track of like my Twitter or anything but my recent post
Twitter has exactly to do with this project let me go close the cap on this
Okay
Cyclone asked if you're taking averages of the data
Oh yeah so spell balloon
Wanted to know if I was taking averages of of all of the data and the way I did it was I just ran for life
Like 10 seconds and took the entire thing as an average I'm just just the whole thing average it together
Weather and that's where we're going to be considered PowerPoint so it was able to resolve the angles pretty tightly
So the one thing I wanted to mention was this right here
Is is part of my voxatron or sorry box
Plastic right now
Download github iOS
Boxel Pathak okay so one of the problems that I ran into is I needed a way of visualizing
In 3D space How likely it was that anyone of the
That I might have the camera right and so I have a level of confidence if those. Do not line up with
Where I think the photodiodes Arthur's raise don't line up but I know the camera's not there but maybe it's better in some
Maybe it's better than others maybe there's local minimums and local maximums maybe the global minimum and global
Maximum Global minimum are the same as all the local which case we
We can do a lot of things to speed it up right now all I'm doing some searching through all the points until I finally
Looks really good I'll just go use that one and then just go a little bit around there and search more than
Until now I've never been able to really visualize that data so
So this right here is the the Wi-Fi visualizing Wi-Fi videos
This this area right here isn't about a 1.3 by 14 sorry .3 by .38 18
M space the amount that Wi-Fi signal is up and down and these notes
Static and there's a whole video about that just check up on the Wi-Fi VDOT was not seeing that this is some really cool
. point is since I made this video JavaScript now has a file API so I
I can load my own file into this to visualize so I'm going to be trying to Output
3D file so I can take a look at the probabilities of How likely it is
Is that the White House is in any one location so let's go do that right now so party
Camfind here I go through and have a whole bunch of print apps to get someone else to clean some of that off
Where do I buy don't I don't have to do that but I will do
I will make it so I have a first-run if I could just do it on cycle number and
Splits
Let me make sure that this actually works out to the right number of of everything
So what I'm doing right now is I'm just going to try to make sure that
That when I'm searching the space the the area in which I want to see how likely it is that the lighthouses in any give
Given location I'm printing out the number of points in that space I'm looking at
And I need to make sure that it is something with the power of two edges so voxel tastic
It can only display data if it's exactly power of two sizes so if I
I have 423 pixels wide there's no way I can display that data but if I have 64
4 pixels wide Good2Go 128 probably
Do non power of two so we're going to have to make sure that we search a power of
Two space-time switch this to I don't know 32 pixels wide and see how they
Alekos
Set X Y and Z on a see if that works out correctly
Okay so it thinks it had 139,000 something that is not a power of 2
See here if I get rid of the less than or equal to
131072 that is a power of two
See make sure that that's right that would be I think 64 by 6
54 by 32 131072
Do we have a power of two points that we can investigate so what I'm going to do is I'm going to open a file
Files to RF equals who actually better yet
If cycle = 0 ft
Equals F open Raw
Data lighthouse.
Yes voxel Pathak only take some straight raw files
Can actually do red green blue flyq have for things or it'll just do it heatmap if you only have one so right now we're
Visualizing one lighthouses position in 3D space so let's see what that looks like so
Cycle of 0f open all that jazz then once for every single.
We're going to go display it out what it is at that that space so I'm going to say
We don't need that sells thing anymore
For this particular location I have the Ft which is the quality
If cycle
I don't have is I don't know what the range on this really
Should day
Let's make it so that if the RMS error is greater than one that I say that can't possibly be
So if it's greater than one s k equals one otherwise it's going to be between Z
Your own one and so I can say fprintf F4 Scentsy and I can
Comprension
Okay so what I'm going to do here is I'm going to take the
The amount of error so runoff these is the part of the algorithm that oriented riorio
Lighthouse to try to figure out from this particular point of view what is the best orientation and then
He tells us how good matches that from that particular position
And I'll tell you okay so from this particular position
This particular position I just can't get into it looks terrible it looks terrible so
That's what we're going to be looking at from a given position does runoff D say good or bad
Don't want to just see what that heatmap looks like going to go here print
FF cell dump the data
Cycle equals 0 f close app
Try it and see if this thing works I have an error forgot to include
STD in stud h
Okay oh it's safe faulted that's a bummer cheap TV
Ron
35 then I work PT
85 printsf cell
Why is that not good
Nil-nil
Okay boom
Cool let's see if it made the file it did hexdump Dash Cyril
Lighthouse data less Caleb's take a look at this
It's like most areas are ff0 you know what we should probably convert that so that the areas that have
A whole bunch of air would be very low on the heat map so I'm going to say 1.0 - SK
All of that * 255
Got something okay
Okay see here
Try loading it and see what it says so the
Exercise is when we say it was 64 by 64 by 30
2 I think
No Dona flip and no it's not an rgba math so this is the very first time
I will have seen this date I have no idea what it looks like other than some random printouts I've done here in there I've been no way of visual
What's a pasta Clive survive
Tools plane test
Call Lighthouse data hello look at that that is interesting
I don't quite know where the exies are on this but that's interesting that it's star
A point which looks like about 00 actually it is 0-0
It says everything from anywhere near there is good
Ha
Maybe we need to tighten that up some let's make it so
So * 10 so now will be more difficult for to look
Good
Oh hello okay so what we're seeing here is
In 3D space representation for all of the possible places that that Lighthouse camera should be in
And that is not the shape I would have expected
Brendan just said it looks like a human brain I would not have expected I would have
Expected that the lighthouse would have had a harder time determining depth away from the Target and an easier time determining
Opposition to draw a. Right at 0-0
So I can tell where the origin would be
How would I do that
That would be
How can I be in here
If
What am I looking at if easy
And the x is greater than 0.4 - 0
0.014 01 and I guess
Heated d y is greater than - S01 and ey lesson
You're one then
We're going to print 255 so we can at least have an origin
Are you answering the lighthouse play OC you guys are actually helping out with the answers
Okay so this this thing here is a cloud of of I'd like I guess points of where the camera could be
Be relative to the the lighthouse I'm going to cut into that a little bit more to see
Okay so these are all approximate Aries let's let's make it even harder so make it 100
So it have to be a very very close match for even a few guys
Crazy weird
Try with a more constrictive
So now it should be much smaller
Harry around it
How awesome knowing I guess not visible at all from that
Try that again it's 2:20
Who is this is really cool it looks like as we start to really tighten down it is much
It's really getting clumped around a specific area very well I wonder if there's some sort of numerical method we could use
In order to say take this data and then fit it with like a gossie and curve or something to figure out where it is bad
Cuz right now I'm just sitting through every point trying to find the best one
Keep pushing a spider and Tighter in seeing what this looks like
Are you guys in chat having fun watching me like do this or
Like
Okay so I'm I'm this is not boring to people
But don't actually understand what's going on if you okay then tell you what guys I will in about two or three
3 minutes I will go do a review over how the HTC Vive does the fee
Think it does and then if you guys don't want to watch that you can go like to the bathroom or so
Something so this is looking really promising cuz
From my point of view that's a much I was expecting this to look very different so there's clearly some Jitter
But for the most part the expectation for where the camera is is is pretty good
Maybe this might actually be sufficient to to go do the problem with
Do this from an absolute Point of View 250
50 nevermind I had it
Little bit unrestricted so it still is not really that sure
Text as we tighten that up try 50
Okay
Looks pretty good for those of you who didn't notice I changed the levels on the side originally
Was a very restrictive point of view so let's try keeping on tightening this up and seeing what
We got
I don't understand
Out having your nursing onebeacon in the visitors right now how would that look with two
Are you at that point can you let that happen when I look at two beacons
That's a lighthouse o lookin that we're both beacons are that's a really good idea let's let's do
Do that so this is one weekend so unfortunately I have it loaded is
Is lrr so it's into different files and I'd have to merge those two together to
How would I do that
See what I can just write a program I can just do it once for the AR and do once for the AL someone to go Lucy
This up a little bit so it's not quite as restrictive
Okay so this is
Time just find a good a good level to visualize
That looks pretty good so there's the hmd in the middle
And there is one Lighthouse up there
And now let's
My copy that file CP
Raw Lighthouse data and that's for the our lighthouse
Stop. I'm going to do it again for the L Lighthouse so
Are Lighthouse over there a lighthouse over here I think
Also I just realized we move this window over here then when I look at the window I'll be looking at the
Okay hope you had to be a little bit less disconcerting to everybody
Fat donkey when I keep looking now that you in that you
Sol Lighthouse let's run this again for the L Lighthouse let's see
See what that data looks like
Oh I can't find me a lighthouse
Make it much less restrictive
Spencer and days
Oh that's interesting the other Lighthouse it has no idea where it is
That's not good I was expecting so okay will look at these two lighthouses
Was in the same dataset how to do that right now
Again I'd like to remind everybody out there if you guys have a
A know where to find the list of all the points on a on a Watchman control
Color and all the normals of where all the points are on the Watchmen controller so it points the normals in space of the Watchmen
Please post that to the issue on GitHub and in chat telling us that you have it cuz I don't know where to find it and I know I've seen
Before I don't really want to go look for it in the middle of a live stream
So right now we have our lighthouse in Ella Lighthouse data
And I'm going to go write a program real quick to just that data together
Again
Michael
If you think that's what you're working on is something that would be interested these people and if they want to like hop in, tan
Anything I think I'm going to be like I'm only going to work in B like spurts like this
I'm so if you want to think about something you'd want to talk about on a live stream
Think about it
I'm sure another hour or something be ready to go and David for you guys he's out of frame right now David Chapman
He is also here so he's the guy who is working on Matrix
That's Dave waving that's inverse phase right there and that's Mike over
On the side and
Neighborhood back
They'll be talking about various Vive related things later on in this broadcast
There we go
And again thanks to Unity for a buying provide for me
So right now I'm reading the the left Lighthouse stay to the right
Lighthouse Daytona be dumped it into a dual Lighthouse Ada so I can visualize it so this reads the right this reads
Lisa left for eichel zeroize + 131072
Plus I'm going to be dumping into
The output file 05
Data are dildi and
Maybe you should just be 255 255
0hone oh no that's not right hand
Our car is RDI and lre
Kohl's ldi and Alpha equals
Why would I do that
Are are straighter than
Lrso are otherwise LR2 alphapix the most important one
R r is greater than 1 R equals 10
Her
Yes
I can't do that actually be fine so
Rd LD and Alpha let's just try that
Oh what did I do wrong
What did I do wrong
Spanish Spanish
Try and catch up with it.
Moderator
Take a look at what the stain looks like so that's the probability for the the derby
Elite now we're going to use an RGB a map and we'll take a look at the combiners
Google lighthouse data
Okay
So that's a little interesting
Wonder why the one light house is completely terrible and very poorly grouped and the other lighthouse
So wonderful and very tightly grouped
Not right to cuz I think was from about this point of view and both lighthouses are pro
Probably at about the same height okay
That's really troubling though so the red one tightly
Group that means that we're pretty sure that that's where the camera is and each one of these cells let's see
How big each one of these blocks represents one of these blocks represents
I guess
5 / 64 decimeters are sorry 64
Divisions that's 7.8 CM so the grouping on this one
One would have to be about 1
Count the 123456 about 6
7.8 CM blocks
More densely populated area sensor
I think
About the same number sensors to oriented it to the lighthouse was directly between the two
Hamsa means it's 4.6 even on the tight Ones Still 4.6 DM
Oh wait no I'm using exactly the same
Directions it's exactly the same code checking each side
No there's nothing reflective on the floor
That's really odd I guess we could just take more data we're going to turn off the
The lights though because you guys check it out I'm using a drop lights to light it up
Open lights look really good on film but tungsten Laika I guess could potentially mess up the
Five star centers
I guess it's time that I go and I do my little steal again on how the The Vibes
Survived by his do that mean yet how old am I
Works I guess at least my perspective on it
Good can you guys hear me is this clear
Levels good levels look good I guess I'll just start talking
Okay
So I guess you can't really see it but it's fine
HTC Vive this thing right here is far as I'm concerned the complete
Future of everything VR and that's because of room scale so bunch of different people
You'll have like kind of gone into direction to try to make Ruthy lvr and people are doing
Cameras and other stuff
But there is a technology that I had never even thought of and I've done computer vision things before I just
Never saw it I never I don't know how to get those living under a rock and it's this idea of Lighthouse technology
I've been saying Lighthouse Lighthouse Lighthouse lighthouse in a lighthouse is one of these
Little boxes so like this thing
Nothing right up here
That is a lighthouse
Kind of see it flashing a little bit and
Showing the
I'm going to see a red light and then two scanners and the way it works
Is
The way it works is by taking a flashing flooding the scene with lighted
Like a like a camera flash and that tells all of the little dimples on these guy
Guys all of these little sensors
On this exactly like hey synchronize know what time it is right now and
Then what it does is it takes a laser and it sweeps the laser across and it hits
One by one and it sweeps across the entire scene and so the time between that flash
And when it actually sweeps and hits the different sensors that's how it knows exact
Zackly where in this Dimension it is relative to the lighthouse
Does it again for this dimension
Hitting all of the sensors all the way down and the cool thing is it doesn't from to lighthouses so it still
Uses imuse like many of the other systems like The Sixth Sense and the the controller is in the PA
PS2 PS3 and 4 and all that to tell like oh I'm moving really quick in this way so it doesn't have to
Wait on the data from the lighthouses to figure out where it is let me taste it does know where it is but from frame-to-frame
If I move it it doesn't need to wait on the lighthouses to tell if I moved a little bit you can tell that really mediately
At the lighthouses give you the ability to track basically and unlimited number of points
In a 3D space and track them very very precisely and absolutely
And that is something that is kind of like the Holy Grail of cracking and that's why I think the HTC Vive is like
Wheatley the future of how this works and so again it is you sweep past and so we're trying to do in
This project is a much larger scale project it's one that
It's going to have impact as far as the goal would be to make it so you can just straight-up right games in life
Survive for very very minimal framework so an HTC Vive
Something that says clearly
Requires a VR capable computer
Right there I think that's a little bit ridiculous and I'm going to see if I can get it to run
On this my Gen 2 Core i5
Really really horrible book that has integrated Intel graphics
Good overview if you guys have any questions feel free to ask her right now
So I've been working with Steve I've since
Early summer I am Mike and I was curious that I've seen this
Survive can both locate where is currently but it also has a bit of a predictive aspect break until we're
It should be is well is your library going to handle that or is it just going to leave that
Leave that be for now that we're working with Dave on Dave
Batman is also in the back over here and for working with Kim on
On some more of the details about the Calvin filter and it'll be using motions guitar
Understand
To tell both
Like
Based on my current motion
I expected this time even if I haven't received any sensor updates I expect to be here
Prediction time
Right tell your best estimate of State at the next time step given
Information from only the previous timestamp and there's another term which is your best estimate of current safe
Question is how much do you weight new information versus your prediction of
Oh yeah okay so I was just over there
Is it just the right place to be
We are figuring this out and so I was just I was just mentioning
Common filters are predictive filter so there are really there really to
2 * 1 is the best estimate of State at the current time stamp given
Only information from the previous timestamp so that best estimate is entirely a prediction
And that prediction would include your current position your velocity acceleration
And also all your acceleration in direction as well so then the other term
Would be your best estimate of position or or partial estimate of of of position
Given only information that you can see at the current point in time so really
The question is how much do you weight those two terms and depending on your measurement mod
Can have an uncertainty model for your measurements and depending on what those weights are you know just because
Just because the accuracy or the Precision of a sensor is ex doesn't mean we can't change them
Number to make it Whately prediction part more weight the or wait the measurements more
Really interesting that I actually learned
About these I don't even know how long ago when I was in the Navy I worked on the IMU
You are the Gyros for the ship itself and that was one of these systems that was working on and
Part of that was learning how a Coleman filter worked and how they calibrated so
It's always interesting to learn about that and then suddenly almost 10 years down the road have this come back up
Yeah nana nana
So while they're off to the side of briefly just a common filter is actually
Used it a lot of different places I was on a cruiser in the US Navy
And are gyros for the ship actually used a common filter to help us with dead reckoning and cuz
Possession
Something the chat mentions uavs and flight control as an exciting
Also used in other applications such as uavs flight control or
Any place where you could have data coming in or you could be reduced to a dead reckoning stay
Due to either loss of data or unreliable data coming in
Anybody else in chat really said much that we should be dressing right now that's okay
Anybody else from chat want to mention anything or grab me other questions until we
I guess some point look at the next thing on the agenda for tonight
Wow
Matthew Jones asked then why would it affect one of them only one of them I don't understand
Sorry they're talking about the noise patterns why it would affect only one of the lighthouses
I don't I don't know I think
Specific to women filters and like what we're talking about right now
So Nathan I saw you were asking if we could feed accelerometers or data
From the inertial directly from the accelerometer as you can but by applying the Cullman
Able to smooth it out and get a more accurate picture of what's actually happening then just taking an arsenal
Later right off and saying okay but we must be going exactly that far using the call me smooth
And control what you're seeing instead of just trying to shoot raw data at it and see what happens
So I think it's actually probably went back to this cuz he asked me about that
Where do you want to work let Charles move back to the visualization
Science for a while so I didn't want to stay
Destination and so bad at measuring
Where it is I don't know
Anybody has any ideas that would be super cool cuz I did not know the air
Airbound look like this okay
So I guess I should also mention the sweeps and the way that works is that what goes on is lighthouse
House number one of their sweeps flashes sweeps flashes sweeps then
Lighthouse flashes sweeps flashes sweeps
You've been scolded for being too loud
Oh I'm sorry I'll be more careful with that in the future I will I will I'm learning
I don't know a splitter Suites creeps and beliefs baseball
Sorry
Way less accurate like super less accurate that's not what reality is showing us right now
And right now this is solely looking at
Efreet one of these these red and green blobs it's only look how hey it's kind of Christmas-themed it's only looking at the
Is the depth right
That's a really good question let's find out if the death is right I'm going to go back to
Plane test to camfind at sea
But Ron give me a solution oh you know what we need to collect more data
Really good time on what I'm going to do is I'm going to set up this system exactly is is I would
Would set it up to do the calibration and I'll record some data and I'll post this data into the issue
And then we'll use that data collected from this time to check it and we're going to tape measure
You're in measure the actual position to the lighthouses so
How the lighthouse position it I don't know about race
On the floor that you can kind of see that
EXO
I had not this play is right here on the floor
Positioning it to that a bunch of sensors can be seen from the point of view of both lighthouse
I don't know you think I should make it to this pointing this way or some
Tween the two lighthouses know it is
I'm not measuring anything between the two lighthouses
We want to do we want to spoil the
Popcorn so
This the date is entirely to do with the headset data coming from just the headsets not the
Do lighthouses unless it's somebody else knows is there an is there a photo sensor inside the lighthouses is it there
The photo center inside the lighthouses by gosh now we have another absolute datapoint or reference so we can find out
Do actually communicate and synchronize with each other so they have to be visually
Insightful each other I think they I don't know how they do it exactly but if you do now I don't know so many
Online knows if there's a way for me to get the the data from like the lighthouse like like
Oh I see the flashes coming from this other Lighthouse that I would be cool
I know that they do
Synchronize in some manner but I'm not sure the message I don't know how either method or protocol or anything I don't know how
Illuminates IR LED
In sequence in sync with ir cameras
So which is totally not the way I would want to do it
This way just trying it have it sitting on the floor it is right now oriented with the camera
Pointing towards I think that sell camera real lighthouse
I'll have Mike Like Houses said to be and
Channels BMC
Yes yeah one of the things been suggested we did before was to use one Lighthouse and mode
O'Day I did that I was able to get the data but I think it's much more interesting to just
ShopRite off of two lighthouses data
Nothing that I called Data recorder and I'm going to go run that
Make sure where is the
I'm going to just turn off right now the the Watchman and so we won't have
Watching data for this data recorder
Pipe tee live stream
Test one with light with hmd in Center. CS
Somebody was saying why don't you try hooking up to them using a USB kit
Or updating their firmware just to see what you can pull out of him somebody suggesting up to the USB
C cable I could but I tell you what if you
You go buy an HTC Vive system and you hook it up and you get some awesome day to go share
That dated with me I'm very very tight on time
Okay let's see is it doing it and I press 0
Send all okay so that's another thing sometimes for the hmd just stopped sending data and I'm not sure why
Give me the IMU data but it will not give me the lighthouse data
Pick something else
Testing just think that's Mike 1
Switch to mic
Oh hey good good
Okay
So sometimes for some reason the head-mounted display just stops giving me liked it and I don't
No Lie
So we're still trying to figure that one out but if I plug it in
Highway
I run the program
And then I say oh
Then
Should
Still not giving
Try that again might have to restart the heading out to fly
Also
Try again
Plug it in
Kuwait
Way
Run it
Fresco
Poster
Send the magic to make it start sending me some data
Not
Light
Sauron
Why is it
Not working
Sometimes if I just poked at it for a while it starts working
Okay
You hear me now hey that actually looks pretty good I guess they don't need to yell
Okay you guys should probably calibrated to this and it's not working what's try just giving
Butthead mouth play a full power down
I haven't got a background static yeah there's bacon cooking
In the find there that's not
The atom is cooking
No you don't but you can hear it
Rebooting the lighthouses here
Snow Moon
Beacon bacon
Yeah I'm hoping
Some of you guys end up getting a vibe to start you know troubleshooting this with me to help figure out like okay why is it sometimes being a
Little bit wacky with the with the two dots
Looks like houses are green oh give me data oh
Jada
Live in the normal capacity inside of unity
Shanghai know their exclusive unfortunately
Actually been amazing for me Mike wanted to know if it would have been possible to collect data from the Vive the same time
As the steam interface I don't think that's possible
Sometimes it seems like five
John engineering the Vive to run on lesser Hardware
John wants to know if we are making a virtual wifey
Not making a virtual Wifey I'm pretty sure a virtual wife who will not run on this laptop
Mostly because if it was I think it would commit suicide to the laptop so bad
The other day they're trying to tell explict virtual waipuna capsules in Japan
It sits on your desk like Alexa but it's a VR girl
Plays off
I can't touch the back of my running oh got it I don't know why
Magically works now there's a favorite in the background
Okay
Close curtains
Let me text
I hope you don't have to go do that
Okay we're now collecting data off of these two
The two lighthouses I'm sorry about the Bilal thing in the other room that's currently
Making popcorn actuate
Quieter on your guy's end awesome collecting the data I'm going to run for another couple seconds and then we're going to stop
I was going to get a lot of data points do it averages out fairly nicely
I could probably best if you guys want
Watch the first video anybody who's new to this summary video between the two others
Can you post the link to my summary video so the 20-minute one
So I think that's probably enough stuff hey if you guys somebody wants to go do a
FAQ on the GitHub site if you want you can just do a pull request on my on my readme.md file
The second white house right now
Are they Independence right now the two lighthouses are completely independent the goal is
As soon as we get this thing off the ground that's when we'll use them in like coordination with each other in order to figure out
Better Where We Are
Tryna get this lined up better here
Don't worry
You guys will see the popcorn when it's done but you won't be able to taste it
Livestream with hmd SSA
3 MB files that's pretty good zip 9R live-streamed edited
Zip live stream fat deflated
Issues determine location of lighthouses
This is the hmd static
And middle of the room
Okay now let's go upload that
Okay people are already commenting
How cool is that yes guys please participate in the issues on github.com
Flash live survive or live survived
You pronounce the libraries
Coughing on the guys from 5 matriarch contact looks like too much of a hassle
Okay I just published the copy of the test data so any of you guys who want to play along you can
Just go download this from Issue Number issue number 3 on online survive
Okay so now I'm going to go into tools TV plain Test 2
Copy... Livestream tests All That Jazz.
Flash camfind Otzi
And we will open this file instead
Where is that that somewhere here
How to rank amfine 4L
About Lee Hackley boats instead to use with Google cardboard okay so this is actually calibrate
Going pretty well what these these settings here show me is that
Every single one of the photodiodes on this one from the from the lighthouses point of
You is actually calibrating to under a millimeter of accuracy and this is the first time I've actually taken any day to wear
That's the case I'll feel like a complete idiot if it's because that's stupid window there was reflecting the beans and I was getting
False data that would be so dumb
I can just ignore datapoints they're just outside of the mean
You know what that's effort I don't really
I don't really have time to put in that kind
Kind of
Can't really do that so
Well let's go take this data brawl lighthouse..
Combiner miss one is El lighthouse..
Let's run it again with our
Queso from the other one's point of view the
The one on that side that's actually a lot worse that says two of the sensors are to M&M's out
And that's not very good so I guess we'll just test that one anyway
So let's take a look at this date
Now by the way people keep posting articles in the
Issues please postcode code post patches there was an a little
Funny thing GCC did with experimental versions where you have to set an environment variable that says I promise to include
Food patches for all bug reports about ready to enforce that
Like I'll just post a link to something actually like posted a scussion from it
Who that's interesting
Haha that's actually
Worse
I would not have expected that to be worse
Why is that worse
Tell me nighttime now like looking over a very large range but
It shouldn't be this bad
I mean it's it's it's geometrically correct but that's still really depressing
Okay so one of the things people wanted was they wanted to know if this was actually correct
Or not so let's see for the our lighthouse
It says it's 2.93 973 so let's just say 3M and let's
Check from the L lighthouses point-of-view from the L lighthouses
Point-of-view it says three point six years so let's check and see if that matches reality
Adam can you get a tape measure
Popcorn
Metric tape measure
I do choose my units based on the project if I deal with speed of light I do more things than.
If I do more things in a different mentor
So go to the nose on the access property line
293 cm
Okay so 22.9 3M let's check to this one
That would be I think that's like how can you do it less
Okay that would be Lighthouse to which I think is our and this one says
3.6 me about 3.65
So oh hey
Okay actually gone wrong it's 3.65 so okay so that's pretty close to three point
65 3.69 and
190 a little almost 300 so 2.9
This one is off by only 5 cm this one up here
That is all correct
PSL that's us right sets off by 5 cm and then the other one is off by I forgot
Cowboys number again 2.99
Okay whatever it's it's only off I like to see em so I think we're figuring out the locations
Of lighthouses pretty well right now not locations just right now all I can
On measuring distances from the lighthouse to the headset right there so I'm going to go
That's surprisingly good maybe we really can
Can't get away with this without doing a lot more work although I don't understand why the clouds are so terrible
Like that's just awful why is this data so
How bad I mean yes it can approximate distance great but
Cook Creek OK let's try it I've been curious about this
I want a I want to try it again except from inside having the
Hmd oriented this way don't have it oriented in playing with the lighthouses so I think they would be affecting
X primarily mostly affecting why
Soty this position I want to switch it to Italy this way
At least two recommendations to just walk away houses to make sure it's not a lot of people spend the night
Why I don't want to swap lighthouses
Physical difference in the way your lighthouses are operating
Just at the date as bad as for the
External if you swap the lighthouses then you'll get the same data whereas if the data if the
The difference of the lighthouses themselves that's a lot of work
If we would have just moved the VR headset. Yeah we can just do that
That's pretty good idea we can just write one another one real quick
Pipe tee
2 xxs.
Yesterday okay
Oh why did I do that that was I need to get it oriented first and then
How about you do that let me oriented yeah you do that and then I won't come again
Tell me what you want
Oh no I was going to have it sitting
Doing it the other way so upside down
Yeah I'm not I don't think I want to do nothing
Nothing too well yeah I don't think it'll work well either but let's find out
This way
Put the stator on for a little bit so right now the reason I think this won't work as well as cuz the things our group so tightly
It's kind of a hard time resolving any kind of meaningful distance out of it
Thai Kitchen 1
I was just had a question for you Charles whether or not there was some tunable thrush
Threshold that could be adjusted that might affect the size of the client thing that it has to be within some
Aerotolerant or if there's some
Confidence that used to have anyting I think that, I think a lot
I do have a lot of stuff going on with the algorithm that finds the right orientation and there's a lot of heuristics that go on
On with that so it's entirely possible that algorithm could be improved significantly
Be more reliable that maybe there's just something about the state of it's making it not resolve well but
I don't know where I would search for that cuz I mean
Unitus returning a single point cloud
Adam are you done with the okay I'm switching the microphone back in
Into slightly louder mode okay
I mean I also update the
Can I put axies on it
She's on it
Just a penalty at like you tight went on just on the chair or something somewhere
Closer to where you actually using it well it has to be able to track their as well
Because to calibrate seafloor height there is a calibration
Also Toby asks what the points of the top of the gooey arm and is that skiing
Hopsin the gooey oh okay so the points the top of the gooey
I guess I can bring that back up what that's about is if I don't get data from
Both lighthouses for sorry know if I don't get data from both X and Y no great
Now it's not giving me data so I can't show you but
I can wake it up
Or not if he's not want to wake up
Does green but is it really waking up or is it just lying to me
Let me just try to run this right now
I'm going to run with this new data
Can you maybe make a note on the voxel plot of the size of each block so you can have asked
I'm not mad that the box of pathic no
Pull request so if you want to go out that you can go out that and I'll go say okay
Some happy
One camera green is the other camera
Voxels the inverse of the RMS error of the points from the cameras pointed
View at that position
Hello there has to be a full red yes absolutely
Is that impossible Pathak
To draw as red then it could be that a very small number of points are full red
Yeah but I
Mike no more involved
Future please o
What which which aspect would I commit which which thing if you can find
Find out whoever was the one of me to commit just tell me specifically what aspect you want the tools committed or what what do you
You want committed or do you want the combiner committed
Taxis on Vauxhall magic taxis on Vauxhall Magic
Catholic there is no axes unlockable tastic
Do you want me to add the feature okay what I'm actually going to do is I'm going to make it so
Help getting axes from Boxville tastic I'm just going to make it so it points
In the y direction direction by Direction
Please open the headset I'll make it print up in the y direction
Call Candy is that
Randy Wise less than 0.234
Okay it'll have a little bit pale pointing in the
I'll make it do an X and Y both
That'll have a little bit like a coordinate frame thing going on
Let's see how old is this one resolved
Unresolved to at worst
666 micrometer micrometer that's right that's millions of M
I believe so that's incredible actually
It is possible science
Yes it is it is actually resolving 22 right here this one looks like the worst one
Resolve in the best 147 micrometer so I think this date is going to look pretty good
Although know what you know what no no no because they're closer together
You'll naturally resolved to lower errors and that that's just so it's really not to act
It is an artifact okay I was really excited there about it you know resolving so
Tightly
In that direction
How fast is our Outlook to run it 90 times per second
So the algorithm for this only needs to get run once ever once it's run
Once we know the position of lighthouses and then it's much easier to do the inverse of this problem which can happen
Super duper fast make sure it's the right one L Lighthouse Good2Go
I was running again for the our lighthouse
Are Lighthouse done
Combines the data
That's nice still realtor
Totally week and that's odd that there's this one point down and I'll make it totally clear
Google
That's weird are good at the ballgame
Gothic there no boys
It's not liking that okay
I don't know the concert
Is everything under a certain RMS is bright red
No it's it's the color red
Is the is independent but the capacity is depending on how wet it is
So right yeah so so so so the full opacity is that set to a specific
Value of RMS or is that dependent on the smallest RMS you find Abby
I'm wondering whether whether box of pasta cuz you
Using an absolute or relative color scale
In a specific RMS in meters is
Are meters squared is set to a specific capacity okay so to answer that question I have that code
Going to places one is right here where I take the RMS error and I * 10
AB greater than one I just don't worry about it it's just I set it to 1 if it's less than one which means that it's it's better
Better that I make it less than one and then I saved the inverse of that out out to the file
So it looks like you're not and nowhere are you Computing the men or Max or the average or anything
So so I guess my my my thought is that let's say you have a situation where
A lot of points that have a low our mess but there's one point that has an even even even orders of magnitude
So all of them would show up in the cloud I would see that in here so what I would do is I can set this
Higher so I can set this to say like 200 or like
Jordan 39
One of these yes so I guess what I'm saying is not be that huge green cloud and might be that those are the o
That's a good point scale you just had a color scale it wasn't so Jen
So generous right that everything look like it was everything look like a good fit but there was only
One point that was an even better fit right that's a good point Okay so
Oh yeah sorry the yellow thing in the middle is the headset and I was going to try to make an access point which way was wiped
Boss but I mess that up somehow
Okay just you guys know the Axis ad is going to have to happen
I guess it can happen in combiner that's probably the best place to put it would be in combiner let me go
Make a makefile for combiners that that's at least reasonable
Make file
Writing a C programming to make file
Is the wrong with me smile
Coaling combiner combiner coaling combiner. Cdcr Co dollar at
Dollar carrot clean rm-rf combiner
Make combiner
Ron's okay
This looks like it's running okay so I'm going to go commit combiner now
What is an right
Don't recursively commit I don't remember the command for that
Cursive Lee I don't want to add recursively get ad now
Does anyone remember off Catherine
Read what the command is to commit a folder but not everything in the folder
Move the files out of a folder and then unit in the news
David suggesting copying the files out of the folder committing the folder and then
Moving moving not copying
Or something
I'm familiar with the CPP and sdp commands and
Very familiar with the overwrite okay okay fine I'll just copy the file move the file download go from there
Somebody's showing how to there's one way to know it commits LS.
I can't commit the folder inside the other folder until I commit the folder that has the fold how do I say that
You're going to move the files out and committed technology
Oh yeah
Good that's fine everything is fine now
Define okay
Special okay that's working
Totally works everything's fine no we're not coming
What the bacon is going to be a part of
Bacon pancakes
Making popcorn pancakes with I still think you should
Sungold bag popcorn I really do want to find a good way to make
Savory popcorn oil and then powdered
Tell me something else you can blaze it with I wasn't joking when I said you could put it in the car
Caramel it will work try it I think you're insane okay that's all
All up-to-date so now I got to track down in these clouds figure out what's going on
I'm not really sure myself though that data looks pretty good
In the ranges are pretty good I don't really know what's up with from the red point-of-use let's actually look at that right now
Who dudududududududu playing test
Let's see which one is this is this a good one of the bad one this is
Terrible terrible data let's take a look and see why
There you go
This dude actually looks pretty good
Oh I think that they wanted you to do is to take Levi and
Close to 1 and close to the other and compare the results I can do that
Okay sure I'll do that in a minute I will do
Vivelle and vybar okay well I'm really can
Dana doesn't look all that bad is Maya my calculating RMS is wrong
Calculator
Matheny has not been friends as of late it's pretty good
I mean it's a little off but not that bad
I just think it's off by so much
I guess it is right even though it's a very small amount
Radians in this graph I guess that makes sense that
Just doesn't look like it cuz it would be like on the surface of the the thing here to here
I guess that's for mm
Does it calculate the position at the street bottles and then
Pick the best one is out your body here is it calculates the best air
Area of voxels to look inside of from the best voxel it down the previous round and then it searches in there
Churches near 30th and Edgerton it does it does actually narrow down
Not binary but like a multi-dimensional iterative tightening surgery or something
Hierarchical I like that word Dave
That was our Lighthouse looks like an L lighthouse
Okay take the stator and take a look at
At it in the graph and see if it's spot-on
Okay the other day to look good but the
Just looks amazing yeah okay I understand
Now the other day. You could see the red dots behind you can't see the red dots behind on this one there just
It's so good
You supposed to store data is beautiful again so I really supposed to start
There needs to be more context as to why this is so beautiful
The setup for this date of the second data is with the sides of the lighthouse or sides
Bhmd pointed to the two lighthouses let me update that in here
Okay so right now I think it's time that we
Go and point the lighthouse straight on at one point hmd
Those two words straight point the hmd straighten it one light house so it'll be like crystal clear
Cleanest day can't be confused it'll still be confused I just know it
Posted real quick before I do that sweet posted this the lighthouse USB protocol
But the stuff
Doesn't give me
Give me celebration
Hmd Lighthouse centers
Actually Lighthouse centers mr. Redbeard if you know if
This is actually like the hmd although this is not aged in because that's where I'm getting the data from
But I'm wondering though is there any way of getting light data from the lighthouses themselves
And I don't see it would by the way this this some of this is men are all you're going to have to
Update some of the states of some of the things we found
What is this wireless buds Wireless me a trigger button touched the Watchmen
Yeah it's all watching stuff so now I don't see anywhere in this document it's
Saying where it goes
GitHub
Reference does not show anything
About Lighthouse Park receive
Living light data
Check this
Oh actually I should show you guys the photodiode that I intend to use
Use 444 my experiments with this it's cheap
Cheap okay so this guy was one that okay
That's interesting this guy does have a bit of things about the
The position calculation of the although he's doing it at a much smaller scale
And he's doing it based on the known positions and it's using math what I can do is to
For this to Dave though if they've stopped for looking at it
What you're going to do is go to the GitHub live survive page and looking Issue Number 3
Third post from the bottom and see if you can make any sense from it
No We spelled Unity correctly
Cuz I understand it so it was before
For the game engine right it was like the same year that their company was founded okay so yeah there is no
No relationship between Unity Technologies the people or helping make this happen right now
And unity the game engine
Different things we use them but they don't pay me so
Okay so if you do such right now
We're going to go not camfind we're going to
Data record
The rest will be Lighthouse lrh MD
Pointed at
Still put the lighthouse appointed
At that lighthouse
Facebook
So now it's it's pretty close to the other lighthouses actually on the floor you can't see it from
Right there lighthouses right there
Focus camera focus focus come on
You can do it one focus camera focus focus
Not fine whatever Justin want to focus
Yeah it's collecting data
What's what this run briefly
The lot of lights that are in view
We mentioned that they made me on FM was there anything else you'd like
Recommendations for learning C Lennox I know the teams
Kind of odd but if you start actually using Linux and you have the environment they're in Lenox it really makes it easy to
I want to do X and you can go get love whatever libraries you need and all of that just get moving see and when
Windows it's a lot harder to get all the pieces and bits to make you do something useful and fun
Now since you can use the Linux embedded in Windows you can actually get started without
Diving holy into the Waters of hell that you're not ready for no that's
Terrible I tried doing the Linux on Windows saying everything is broken you type in D message and it just says not implement
Recycling like live USB broken
So what all did you say was broken
What's USB if you want to access hard
Where it's really easy and say yeah
Hmd pointed at Lighthouse Nursery now get it can find at sea
I think we should be on the L1 so
This I didn't edit it yet
Somebody would like to know if you accounted for the slightly different origins The X and Y Suites
How you should not need to account for different origins of X and Y sweeps that I'm aware of
Because the center of the effective sweet like not where the
The actual emitter is but where the access that it's rotating around is should be sent
I heard inside of the like this one goes this way in the song goes this way it should actually have a point in the center of
Whoever were considering the lighthouse to be
Thankful
Yeah
Hahaha
Grinding it
Servel grinding things
422 says the problem is here
I guess that's that line Maybe
Oh.
Okay
Yeah I had to cap to small it did not find that very well at least it doesn't think it did
Although you know what that's an absolute space so it maybe this is actually really good
Let's see what the data looks like in here first
They'll grind is for finding memory leaks right for finding memory leaks in anywhere that
You're violating any kind of memory rule valgrind actually runs an x86 emulator and so whatever you do
Anything with memory fell Greenville watch you like a hawk like Santa Claus
Okay so from this thing's point-of-view that's what this date
Looks like I'm thinking it's pretty good that's definitely the sort of thing I'd like to see what's
I'll see what it looks like that particular camera in in voxel plastic here
Wi wizard says valve uses and I'll grind in house I would
Would hope that everybody uses valgrind in-house Bell grind valgrind I don't know how to pronounce
Ryan is cooler little grind sounds way more metal
Totally wrong try that again not in rgba Mountain
Oh that's not right either
Or maybe it is
GM says that their code was so big they couldn't even run
Dial Brian no part of it this looks
Super weird I don't even know what I'm looking at here
What is up with this
Smoke
Oh wait no the hmd is not in the center anymore it's pointed right at it
Santo Que
Why is it shouldn't be that bad that's such a large search area
And not to mention there's two locals so there's I was really hoping
Able to use like gradient descent or something and just find the right answer but
Wikipedia says pronounce
Rob if you pronounce that yourself louder
Turn off the screen will hear you in our hearts
I don't
Yeah I don't know what's up with this that's very strange
I don't know why though
That would be I mean it's kind of right like that's kind of where it is
Whatever
Just curious I'm just going to try the other light house right now
But I need to be able to drive home so no hard liquor
The other lighthouses like I kind of have an idea store the thing like they
Hahaha
The other lighthouses to wear that it's you know somewhere on that side of the
The room knows the other lighthouse
Those that you know about that far away that's really cool that the the shape that the probability
Kicker for the other Lighthouse makes is that nice and pretty but
Cool ya-ha
You may want to move your coffee table over a little because the edge of the sweet might be hitting that actually look down I put my head on
On the floor where the thing was and it was totally not all that is so
Weird
So yeah I clearly the other lighthouses not getting enough points to
Know where it is
Okay sorry what was the next thing that we were supposed to be doing
I've been derailed with something Adams.
Copy railing people let's see what the date of
Have you been reading the article the guy posted in there
Okay I'll see what else was actually on the original agenda so he's done that we've gotten the
Points and the normals for the Watchmen oh no
Anybody yet in chat found a list of the points and normals for the Watchmen
Specific
Specifically if anybody has access to the
To the points and normals for the Watchman controller that would be super cool I tried
Asking the Watchmen the nice way through the to hit interface and it totally did not tell me anything so
Visualize the lighthouse probability Dayton voxel
Plastic totally did that improve the Watchman disambiguate ER
We're going to have to work on that
And collect more data is people want it so I think the other thing some people wanted was for me to point the
Camera at yourself that's fine what's the point the
Badmouth display at the other Lighthouse and see what it says so we're going to go do that right now
Yeah there's not much left of probably you don't mind
Face is all mine
Glad I could share some Polish
Couch if they were working that would work
Haha
So we'll start tracking some Lighthouse David here
So right now it's mostly pointed at the Lighthouse are and we're collecting that data
For Christmas
Hey crazy right I've an idea you take so many screenshots of the bloxels
And you make a billionaire and give me $1000000 in will be set
Crazy bread is named after a fake art dealer from Animal Crossing
I do not have to fly any rough
Destinations where the lighthouses are this is just purely based off of position of a word is what
Could be okay
Do you have to supply
No already answered that one
We all look like we need some adderal is there anyway
What kind of
Circular LED purple kind of
Yeah in that thing is I have in in the tread I have the raw times but
You would have to Park City to get angles back out which you could just bring camfind and then
Get the angles from their loads in here actually
David I will pull up him find in this thing I will walk you through it on the screen
Okay so inside of Cam find the first thing we do is we load data and we say either our
Or l4r for the right camera or L4 the left camera sorry I say camera I mean lighthouse
Okay you know what load data
Lighthouse
Oasis and get Havasu number 2
Issue Number 3 Issue Number 3 is where I have a bunch of the example data at any rate so in the
I'm fine. See I go load the data and what this does is it first at Lowe's
All of the sorry it's down here first
Get where is it. Is first it opens up
Correct hmb points that CSV which is in an issue number 3 then it opens up
H&B normals. CSV which is an issue number 3 and then it opens up whichever
File you want to do like our and it reads out all of the lighthouse data from that file
And only uses the our Lighthouse and it figures out the the average angles
Of all of the photodiodes that it sees and it does that by disintegrating over the whole thing and
Converting them into radians from text Betsy
Taxi work pretty well the first one
Is correct hmd points at CSV the second was hmd normals and the third one is
The actual light data and the actual like data I posted is like the most recent thing in
In Issue Number 3 I'm going to be posting a little bit more soon
Parrots talking to number our look at that data
It's off by few millimetres but that still so much see what it says
If I copy this data into here
Automatic and
Turn off apparently you're offline again thinking you look like a strung-out Kotor I am strung-out code
I think it's the bags under the eyes cuz
I've been up all night every night doing the stupid Lighthouse stuff
Staring at the infrared lights pouring out of them
Me begging the lighthouses tell me your secrets mean while Ben is just there being like
I put those secrets in the lighthouses
Yeah I don't know if he's like actively in the channel right now but he did say something earlier then
The guy who coded oh my gosh look at how gorgeous that looks over yes
Yes yeah toad
Yep it's right there but I think it's wrong
Exploded maybe it's right it's
Probably right I think it's right
Cuz it is in the frame of reference from the whatever is the cameras point of view
Yeah
3 + 5 think we only need to be an issue 5 if you're talking about the controller calibrations
That is in those space that there because the uplink
Can't be pasted the John says he's not seen a person so obsessed of lighthouses
Oheine are all Sony Rawls the guy who did all of the initial Lighthouse Rita
Redox stuff which is amazingly well-documented it's almost all correct and I don't know how
How he was able to get all of its that is truly amazing I'm so happy for his work if it weren't for his groundling work I would not have
Even tried to do this project but I did actually try the exact same thing
To get the data from the controllers and they don't say anything unless I have to be plugged in
Buy USB directly to the controller do I have to do that they're all do you know if I have to be plugged in by USB to get that data
I also pull request
The Ashley's things in a pull request hold on let me
Let me get this data committed or added to the issue first
If you're into electronic audio you should check out the things that my buddy Paul made
Electronic
Baker 12555 timers and pots
Pretty impressive holding a boards generate sound they use a bunch of likes that before Gates and whatever
Advanced still supposed to use the Internet or something with the
I don't know if you ever finish that woman on a lot of time working on it I should show you what
Because we're trying to do it can you guys do that later like take a note
See here so you got you said I had
Pull request it says pull request
Better access
Comma I think
Not sure what's going on here
Who makes l255 for
Preach
Sure why not let's make this the thing this looks good
I guess sure fine whatever
Can I merge this without hosing that file
Know what
I'm going to just check out my stuff
I don't feel like dealing with a merge right now
So I will just accept what they have wholesale and hope for the best
Merge pull request confirm git pull
Can't find Ducey
What
Poppy can't find it oh yeah I could have done that all well
I don't know which day does
Set that just operated on let's just try it for Al's raw lighthouse
Tool playing Test 2
So interesting I have no idea what I'm looking at their like accies that come out from The Middle
But I don't know which one is positive and negative but still pretty cool
So which ones why and which ones X I wonder
I only see two going like the same direction their there's this
Other fainter wanted more I'll make it so it's easier to say
Now I can't see it all the video actually Niceville to see it
Yes now I can see it it's green
Okay that's neat
Where's the bluest left right
I think Z is foreign backward nosy would be like this way down although wow that's a weird
Shape
Know what's causing that that's very strange
Okay point is the thing I was really really hoping that this data would just
Charlie like converge totally not how it works
Huh
Okay well that's that's interesting
Has a has neural said anything in chat about how to actually get the data from
From the lighthouse ashore to plugging them in I don't think anybody in life to anybody's said how to do
That yet question more data is people want
I'm going to need a break right now anyway. Dave
Michael did either of you have anything you wanted to say
Like talk about anyting
Dave are you ready or do you want a little while longer
Just play a an advertisement for a minute and then oh you guys wanted to know
No Unity Technologies was
So Unity Technologies this thing that Adam me and I are
Teriyaki we've gotten together and we've done a number of different projects mostly commercial thank goodness
Everything down to making a how many was it like 8,000 crosses
5000 cross commemorative crosses for the Pope's visit to New York
Sure they can't hear you over there
Can you guys hear him if he's over there did you experience
Oh I can't do can you Adam
Str8 so we do a lot of custom engineering work we have a meal we have a bunch of
Just mechanical stuff that we do and we we do make arcade machines so
See what Brandon
See if I searched that I can find a good
Also like the newest game that we we made and word vide
Debuted at Napa was the world's fastest drummer and this one is
Italian conjunction with the fun company in a few other groups and it's just a game where you have to
Kdramas fast as possible left and right and you have to alternate and Vie for the best best score of the day month
Xcetera arcades or anything like that
World's fastest drummer we did unit if sorry we did neon FM
Which is a video game that's like
Stand-up arcade we have us and I'll we work with andamiro very large Korean distributor
Are Korean manufacturer and game company on the the Korean
Version of the arcade cab just some of the things that we do up at Unity Adam of anything else so we also do
Custom Signs so anything involving ws2812 or other Innovative lighting stuff
We totally mess with anything else you guys wanted to know or anyting Adam you can think of unity wise that we should mention
And by the way you guys can totally take it as a hint there is a reason why
They got me an HTC Vive
Okay I need
I need a brief break I'm just going to keep that scrolling
I will plan ad I think I have a button to phone
Right there and I'm curious
I guess I'll leave it Ron not hurting anything
Caramel popcorn
14 minutes that's why it's not
OK Google everything's fine
How long is your ad
Why would you have YouTube okay to be fair I'm really glad you YouTube Red people
Because I make like it's like 10 times or more I think it is purview off of YouTube Red views than I do
You off of Regular YouTube views with ads
I don't think we need any intern this summer we have had interns in the past and it worked out really well I would never turn down into
Adam we consider you as an intern just apply though reply email us in a fly
Do you guys have any did you want to mention like some stuff you were
Working on and maybe if this would be of interest to you or like if anybody else who's interested in the vibe stuff would be
Then I can just talk about what I was doing really briefly and how it's time release today
Vibe stuff
Sowell Charles are taking a quick break here I figured I could talk about my project with the Bible little bit see if everybody
I was interested in working with my university University Maryland Baltimore County
This spring so I've spent yesterday also went there
Been working on a research project related to the HTC Vive where were you
To perform human studies about reaction times
And how people react in different situations so what we're doing right now is
Simple pilot study to make sure that we can use it in this capacity and I programmed
Basic shooting range simulation in unity with two types of targets
One you're supposed to shoot one of the sister. Shoot and the goal of the study is to see
After explaining the tasks that allow him to take it once comparing a control group who just takes the test again
Yan vs a group who is trained on how to better take the test
How to avoid shooting the wrong targets to see under stress
Situation how they respond and see if we can measure differences in their abilities to perform
Through data gathered from the by while they're taking the mother taking it
Trials it's been to record information about the position data of the headset
Mission Ada of the controller as well as every time they shoot when the targets appear and disappear
As well as would be taking physiological data on each participant such as EG heart rate and breathing
And after that our goal is just to make sure that we
We get good data out of this project and see where we can go from there there's a lot of other studies were
We're interested in but we need to make sure that is possible in first
So
Even when you're sober you don't understand how much have you been drinking
Even when I'm sober implies quite a bit of drinking
Are you the are you do anything I want to talk that's okay
Yeah my study is still were waiting on approval
So we haven't really done any test subject data collection yet so I don't have too much to say about that
Portable study involves inducing stress through
Shocks so we have to wait until all the people who go and make
Not doing horrible things to other people approve us
PVCs
So what was that
There was a similar
Someone did a fan experiment involving tdcs tdcs okay
Know what that is
Brendan speak loudly
What would you like the perfect intern to do
I think that's a human at UPS
No that's not a question I can never answer because I never know what I'm going to do it changes very routine
Family Unity. A lot of stuff so the the definition of a interns job changed
Considerably from David hey I just don't understand how people can Define their jobs cuz I like
Never known is just figure out what the heck to do all right
Oh okay yes I actually I do remember reading about that study Michael
They did a thing where they were stimulating the brain trying to induce stress
Ours is similar but it's a bit different in that we're trying to weed
We already know that I method will induce stress but we're trying to study is Ken we train people
Through using the EEG data and the the game of the simulation can we
Train people to improve the response and their ability to operate properly in a
Stressful situation or to inhibit responses that they become a b**** waited to when they're stressed
All the people on GitHub
This is the internet you are who you say you are until you prove otherwise
Not sure what you mean by a god helmet
I think probably something that involves us mic button
CK one
Maybe it's a collector's item but other than that I can't see what
PS4
Okay so they were trying almost the opposite of
Trying to induce stress through the immersion that stimulating to reduce it okay
Yeah what we're doing is not quite
Extreme as anti pedophilia training
Somebody mentioned that what I was doing sound similar to the method they used to
To use to Frame data files to not look at children
Here's a kid here's an electric shock
Proletarian dictatorship
Robotic overlords they are coming but first we will be the overlords
Robots that have taken our jobs
Jobs
Whatever you want Davis radio
Any more questions about anything that I've done 90 it's not a whole lot yet but Dave actually has some stuff that he likes
Speak about as well
So for this project we are trying to minimize the total number of
Dependencies on anything external so that's for a few reasons one because the reason this
Project started to begin with is because I ran out of data on my cell phone plan trying to get all the dependencies
For the osr vosper Libre Vive Library tours
Run which was annoying but more importantly in the long run this is really kind of targeted
More towards the esp32 so we really need to use is lightweight and has minimal
Like Library stuff is we can in order to keep everything moving slowly or moving smoothly on his
As many processors and targets as we can so one of the things David's been doing is in order to the cabin filter we
Have to invert matrices and notary in for matrices there's a bunch of operations you have to do to do that and
A lot of people use lapok and that's not
Open that was kind of quite work for us because of some of that the size and additional things surrounding it so Dave is going to be
Speak a little bit about what his his effort has been and in case you guys could use some of what he use he's produced now
You guys can just go check that out of the live revive Repository
Charles has
Talk is incredibly easy to install and Lennox the the packaging before the appearance of acne
Has been around for 70 years
Fortran
Problem was that I try to install talk back
I'm a Macbook and there were all these dependencies
Which I was I was surprised by you know I didn't you just say yum install or after install
And I'll have my powers and installed over and
Make mountains calling and I actually have to write your own
Which did havilah Potter package but it depended on a lot of other
And I couldn't actually get it to work so I won't up
Rewriting one of the numerical code do I use Lu decomposition
Which was an inventor named Alan Turing
So you know this is America codes
In history did Alan Turing is an algorithm which was developed
Incredible mathematician astronomer inventor name that I call friends of gout
All right so this is a very classical thing to do
For me it was kind of fun to be able to take a step back and try to implement a
Classical algorithm now one of the things code
But we're dealing with 36 by 36 matrices and unless we find a better way
Of of working with it and 36 by 36 major season.
The code that I wrote invert those at about twenty thousand Hertz or so on
Mac that there's a few
Can people hear what I'm saying
I was looking at the okay okay
Better basically I was the one I was
Working on rewriting a linear algebra package because I couldn't install
Call apak which has been around for 67 years or least I couldn't install
Saw that on a Mac because of dependencies and there isn't really a whole lot of support for which really really surprise me
I'm so one of the things that I wanted this code to be is is really really really fast
And one of the things I was little bit concerned about has to do with
All the way that see handles pointers compared to Fortran so C
C is is doesn't have the same kind of bow
Tyler doesn't know as much if you have a b and c and if you're reading from pointer a
And writing to pointer be and you're in a weaving these operations the compiler doesn't know
Know that you're writing to be isn't going to affect the reading for May so that can slow the compile
Tyler down if it has to wait for that right to finish inferred that reads
Finish it they could introduce additional stalls to way out of being conservative doesn't know if you're riding this memory
How do I know that doesn't affect that other memory right so CC Fortran knows that these are arrays he doesn't know that
So I'll one thing that I did with this library was that I made everything in macros
Rather than using functions I'm so by putting everything in macros the compiler
I don't have to pass a pointer the compiler can actually see where I put the local variable I'm so
At least think that it should be able to optimize more aggressively then if
I had written a function that had to pass data through a pointer now lud compass
Position is where you do row reduction effect
You think you can help...
Composition to convert your Matrix
Into what's called a lower triangular and an upper triangular forms if he's
Scroll down might be able to see some examples of a lower triangular on upper triangular Matrix
That I just said that those blocks of matrices there you see that
The one in the left is your original matric say that you try to invert the Y
One in the middle is a lower triangular Matrix and the one on the right is an upper
Triangular Matrix so for those of you that have taken linear algebra the first thing you had
Why do was row reduction so I Matrix is a system of equations and
And how do you solve for two equations into a non 12 you could use a substitution method if you can solve for 1
Variable you can substitute that another but matrices usually what people use are
You would multiply your equation you would do would multiply constant by one of your equations and
Add that to the other one so that some of your charms cancel out so by putting it into this
Upper triangular form that you have on the very right most Matrix if you had an upper triangular Matrix and
And you wanted to solve for a vector product the very last row
I had only one term so you can actually solve for the last if if you want an upper
Triangular Matrix X XYZ well you know you can solve for Z directly
You know that what is it you 22 x e is equal to 2 BC
Besa Besa see you could just you know that that has only one term you can solve for that one
Once you have that one term you can plug that into the middle equation cuz you have
Have two terms and two unknowns but you already have one you've already solved for this and I can solve for y
And then what you have why you can plug that Y and Z into the first equation and then the only unknown you have
Abba sex so you can you can you can solve for
You can solve a system of equations if it's an upper triangular form so by having a lower triangular and an upper
Triangular you can you can solve a system of equations using the upper triangular using what's called
Back substitution and then take that result and plug it into the lower triangular using Ford
Actually have to plug into the lower in the cold
The code I can see why accept the plug it into the lower triangular Matrix first and then take that result and plug it into the upper trying
Regular Matrix but the other thing so
By doing the decomposition I was a question
Inversions over what time period by what metric well I took the Matrix of the problem size
Guys that were interested in because he had to make it by relevant and I ran it in a loop
And I ran it in a loop of 10000 times and it ran in about
I have a second so so that that would mean that the Matrix inverse
InStep which is usually the most expensive operation in the common filter that that stuff and I
Isolation is plenty fast enough or at least it should be more than more
Enough for what we need to be able to use it for I haven't tried running this on very
Very large matrices I mean I tried running it on a 50 x 50 and yeah it looks at you know if you if you invert The Matrix
And multiply the inverse X original Matrix you get the identity so they know that's that's a good sign
Another thing about row reduction if you go into the code
The inversion function so well
If you look at the inversion function it defines a few matrices there and then it calls
It has a few steps to create an identity Matrix
I am going to calls Lu and LU is the Lu decomposition so that's the most important one
I'm in that led composition are you actually it's not until you decomposition of Domaine
Matrix a it's an Lu decomposition of the Matrix a with some of the Rose interchanged and the reason why
I want to Interchange Rose is that if you just do row reduction you know the way they taught you in school you my taxes
Currently have two divided by a very small number if one of those
Entries is close to zero and you try to / it then it could be numerically unstable
So if you swap the order of the Rose you can make sure that you're always dividing by a large number so that you don't
So that you don't have any numerical problems like that and then what you see is it it does forward substitution into the elm
Matrix and then it goes back substitution of the umatrix and that's
The that is the Matrix inverse so it's it's it's really really
Not that hard when you look at it from that high-level but if you look at the L U decomposition code that's a bunch of
That's that's above and that's a bunch of four loops and it looks very similar I've looked at the Fortran code
I I can't write in Fortran but it looks pretty similar to the way people do it and it looks kind of like a
Especially since the macro I don't know that you can put comments in macros I would have loved to put High usually put comments in my code
Function that you really should consider writing them and function yeah but I want
Wanted the compiler to have all of the hints that it could possibly have
In terms of the way the memory is laid out so that it can make it really fast
So
No I just I didn't have a copy of the function in front of me
Give me just a second
Not one I do intend at least on x86 to the dino compiling with
Beaufort and AVX and even on this old processor right here
So it's going to automatically do a lot of the Cindy and you say no it won't compilers are terrible at
That's wrong because I just totally of like written a bunch of test program to do some pretty like like screwed up things
And the compiler can still figure it out and still like totally paralyzed the heck out of it so
I am thoroughly impressed with everything past GCC for it just figures out this automatic factorization
Totally Cindy's it exactly right better than I can do it this time and I'm like I love assembly
Did you guys hear what I said clearly
Oh no okay
Do you guys hear me clear enough or do I need to go back Charles was basically saying that g
Gc4u compiled with the dash 04 flag should figure out automatic vectorization
And he said he's tested on some programs and he thought the compiler wouldn't be able to vectorize and it was able to do
Do so so I haven't seen it
Only but Charles is is giving us his word that it
Rise of the code and I tried to write the code in a way that the compiler would have as much information
Is it possibly could to optimize aggressively but I don't know that it's really
Play necessary by I think the performance is fast enough so
Hopefully we can compile it I even out if the computer doesn't have gtc4 and it would run
It would it would run plenty fast and if it does have GCC for that it should run even even even more
Even you know more even faster right so so
Yeah sometimes you have to oh yeah we were looking at
The goal is to eventually actually get it to run on this little guy right here
He does not have Cindy instructions esp32 does have a floating-point unit
Gold is get it running on there eventually and you'll see why
This case that a regular computer is someday hopefully
So so so the Lu function there's really two parts to it there's that there's this
Giant for-loop I guess it's about here that's it that's that's going
Going for every row and then this part this first part over here has to figure out
Rearranging the the the rose because we don't want to divide
I'd buy a small number so we find the largest number to / and that's that's called a pivot table
I'm in and that's something that you have to do with LED composition to make sure that it's numeric
Stable and then this
I don't think I'll even be 5 minutes and then this part here is actually
Doing the division and the thing is that
You have to take a row and a figure out how much to multiply in add it to that
A Robalo it cancels out to the first term cancels out 20 that's that's that's
That's for the row reduction and that's how you calculate the upper triangular Matrix but then the law
Lower triangular Matrix right it has to be you have to have lower * upper
A but you know what you're actually doing when you do that operation that you're taking a
When you're multiplying a buy something so you're actually you're you're saying something kind
Is a is equal to is equal to you so you have to you have
If you kind of set up those two equations on
Piece of paper you can figure out okay well there's something slightly different times.you is equal to a minced
Set of something * 8 is equal to you so it turns out that all you have
Have to do is hear I set the L4 the
Iji term equal to scale which is you suggest
5 / use of II
Just have to be careful about it and the other thing I have to be careful when you swap the order
Hours of the of the rows and columns and a that you swap the order of the same Rose in LA
And in you not just one or the other on those were a couple snacks that I got into but
So yeah if if if if I had a
Package that was working for me on the computer I wanted to use straight out of the box that could have saved me
Sometime but I think this was a nice little exercise and again it was a step backward but
We're preparing to make the big step forward so yeah that's that's
That's all I got any other questions for for Dave right now or
Any more questions for Dave right now keep in mind that this is the sort of thing that you'll be at
Able to use on other projects and whatnot because all of this is going to be licensed under the MIT X11
Yeah it's it's 200 lines of code and it's probably the easiest
Is to install one header file Matrix library that you could probably find to copy on any
Everybody if NFL are bugs in please fix something that's intimate but
Yeah we have not instituted yet
Strict I promise to include patches with all bug report policy yet but I hope we do
Don't have to go there for you if you don't know if you it back in the day to use the experimental versions of the compiler GCC
You would actually have to pound to find a thing where you said I promise to include patches
With all bug reports to fix the bugs that you're reporting okay
Back to business so has anybody in chat yet figured out how
How to actually get the anybody in chat yet figured out how to get
The data for the normals and positions of the photodiodes on the Watchmen
And I see that narrow has reported that it's there
But I just don't know how to get it cuz I did try running it against it and it just did not give it to me
I'm looking right now I guess we use the lighthouse console
We can't do that just the fiber has to run entirely without that
I think arresting them I never heard of the mamora corrected
Files what is that
What is this identified hmd open the Chase on filing it started its data
I don't know what the the Murrah correction data what is the ma
Correction data oh my gosh what is that that is a
A really dense picture calibration
Fashionphile whoa I totally do not know what is going on there
We are going to have to add that to the to-do list to learn about won the war
World is does that mean okay I have never heard of it
I've seen the thing in my config but what is up with the Mariah Carey
Direction stuff that looks Wicked
Do it for Pixel brightness calibration cool
That's really going to be something that would be a problem for me then cuz I want
Wanted to do I was hoping to do all of the correction for the lens stuff in
In a Vertex Shader and do everything in one pass instead of rendering to a texture and then rendering the text route to the sky
Scream that's really hoping to avoid that cuz I am working on the bottom
Intel integrated graphics
That the image coronavirus passed through almost I think that's what they're saying so so mi casa
Sing that basically the Murrah correction this thing here is a filter that the Vive like all the data being pass
The vibe is passing through before it gets displayed I don't know if that's actually the case but that's
Yeah yeah
I would definitely make sense if that's what's going on I don't know that that's what's going on but that I would totally buy it
Has a correction for the
An OLED display I didn't actually Rises name LED display I thought it was an LCD display but it makes sense
Susan AMOLED cuz it's no there faster and all
I don't actually know where the png's are store cuz I do know when I wiped out the configuration on my
Candy did not wipe out the the things
Jordan HMV maybe I'll figure out a way to extract it sooner or later certainly I didn't
Not accidentally blow it away though thank goodness
Rob everybody don't just linked articles Dallas like a brief summary
I'll look at it okay Mike's going to look at that
Okay so anybody have any
Any idea how to extract and see what are these controllers there is a Json file for this other person
Controller that looks pretty cool
Basically they want to come over here and explain
So thank you rob for the link I was just reading about it and it says that they
Basically Motocross Action is a system that came up with to level out the income
Consistencies in the scream they're using inside of the Vive cuz each pixel would have varying Brighton
Ness even just buy a little bit but when it's that close to your face and with the
The lenses on it it becomes a pretty drastic difference once you actually level that out and get a consistent imagefirst
One with that variance in it the it helps with
Both Clarity of you and with trying to even out what you're looking at so
So that you're not drawn to one area over another or distorting the image of the colors
So that's basically all the Merida
But it was not discussed how Miraak reaction was achieved but looking at this it looks like it's
Moore Hardware oriented the files stored on the hmd so
Show me software you implemented in software
Applying to the fragment Shader stuff it looks like
Restored in the hmd and would be used by the CPU door by the GPU in the fragment Shader step before. Puts
The picture to that the thingy it's basically just the last thing that
Needs to be done to the image so that it can even it out before it gets displayed
The rest of the stuff in that article is pre-release or
Early stuff
Yeah okay so nothing so does anybody else have any idea
He has about how I'm going to go get the data from the controllers or anything I just need to plug them in and try to hold off that way cuz we can't use
The steam tools to pull the data from the various subsystems
Amy accidentally
Do I will go run that on the other ones and we'll take a look and see what it it says
So if I go back over to here
Close this out
Yeah yeah we can't we can't use steam Cool Tools because we have to be able to run
On Independence of the steam tools
So right here is a load config and I pull it from stay like that
Headset, if I wanted to say pulled from the watch and 0
I can pass it in a different stud device ID and then go from there but that doesn't work so if I say
They make and I power on the Watchmen this time
And the other one to let me try
Running this it just doesn't work
Could not get a survive config
Off of device 20 device 30
Could knock it off 30 and I have 40 installed nope just cannot get the data
Tried a couple of other combinations and there's just no way of
Getting it off
That is ridiculous you should just buy a Vive
So
Taylor looks like a look at Moody just open the one
Basically the biggest thing I've got with the life right now is the fact that nobody's willing to I already Set It Off
Nobody's willing to put forth the resources on a AAA game because it's a $700 peripheral basic
Yeah the marketshare just isn't there yet for the resources of the AAA game
And a lot of people are waiting for 5 to point out
It's there myself and get replaced every year where this where's the new vibe
Why have I forgotten didn't hear
Whoops
Some of us live in the house together Adam and Brendan live here
And Mike and Dave do not currently live here
Florian we do not currently have access to a good 3D printer we have friends who have access
Okay 3D printers but
Mike says he has a sort of decent 3D printer
Get config that's to find here I think yes
Silence I say he'd get feature report timeout and I passing the ice
My face and then definitely definitely comes from like CTX tab so that would be
See where those setup
Case I guess that would actually be in our face
0 C what would that be
Message from one that can't be right
Sirius watch and want to watch them to or 2 and 31 in the world why is it getting it from the iff lighthouse interface
Death Lighthouse that's just weird
So it is actually to sew to his word should be reading it from
So if I try reading it directly from the Watchmen nothing happens
Nothing
So let's see here
Open that device that context
Yeah just can't get the config
I guess I could add something to be able to pull it from the
Why wouldn't it be able to pull that
That way though maybe it's hiding on the
Anybody has any ideas here I'd be really really grateful
I'm just
Shooting in the dark
I'm just going to try to pull from all the things
It's a 40 cuz I already know that one works
Oh
Rob suggested treating the pixels is signed and subtract 128
Pixels are mostly gray because it's a median
Man why do we have to pull up the more stuff I can't have you guys distractions with that
I got to figure out how to get the Watchmen data once it so the other reason when I get to watch bendita is cuz I think if we play
PlayTube these into places in the room will be able to try to narrow down where the lighthouses are
By trying to solve simultaneous system of equations to determine like is that and that really a valid play
Place for those two lighthouses where would they probably be if the the two were to match up to the controllers
Yep looks like another devices
From 12 to 100 show anyting
Pinterest
At what the actual distance between your lighthouses was
I mean if it's been three years to the headset diagonally
Which is the 18th to check hey
Interesting too much data on packet from config device 0250
Sex therapist exactly 16 ft
I mean they're working fine so
A killer clown
Actually guys if you want we can try this microphone for a bit how do you
How do you like this one
FIFA some Works any better taxi in the webcam
Too much data
On packet from config for device 00c what is it saying
Shabbos
Is that valid
That might be valid
So 135 what happens if I just make this
Figure
Can we actually read that
Let's see what the data coming back from the devices
That's
Something
Definitely something
But that does not look like configuration day and it looks much more like settings data
Ha
Not sure what's going on there
Don't think there's anywhere else I can load config data from I'm not sure what's up with oh hey
Bacon caramel popcorn
Internet
Do you want this wonderful baking caramel popcorn
It's amazing you can't have it
You just totally blew somebody's mind.
Maple syrup instead of corn syrup in the in the making of the caramel
Did you guys hear Adam when he said that
I know I smoked maple but I wasn't sure
About the maple syrup
Maple smoked bacon
Difference
Nothing
Does Sarah smell
Every Power
That apparently used maple syrup instead of corn syrup on this batch
Make the caramel
A variation of disrespect separated into and that has a very interesting kid I like that a lot
I'm going to try to do caramel apple
Raffle business
Skills
We have some people coming out of the woodwork because
Making popcorn with medicine
Subway something that makes sense to everyone was brought up
I'm thinking I'm not getting any kind of configuration from device zero
I guess for the time being we can just use the configuration data that was provided binaril
I wish they were all stuck around I'm sure he'd be extremely helpful right now
So the other thing I wanted to touch on was we do need a better disambiguation
Wait when do you think you'll have the other live streams up on your Channel.
I want this one's going to become live by tomorrow morning
I'm not exactly sure I know device year was the one that I send the magic codes to
But it's sending me this thing here which to me looks a lot like those magic codes that I had been sending to it
Godlike turn on codes
So
I'm not really sure what's up with that
The magic is that in here no that's in USB
Magic
Yeah
702 Wanda today ad so it's 78 now it's 87-78
Access interesting does anybody know if 8729 or valid gzip headers
Actually I'm streets I just read it all in one Fell Swoop
Doesn't look like she's a data
Apparently they're saying the archives
Previous dreams was not
Darken my previous dreams are definitely Bello
Oh wait hey internal trivia or Infinity trivia
If you can please try to get some of the packet dumps of somebody pulling the configuration data from the
From The Watchmen controller
Is this part for your part 4
This is
Kind of part 4
There is no part 3
Okay
Part one was like actually to live streams
This is part of part 2
Kampar to is where we try to find the location of the lighthouses
I can see
The two videos a week ago and 5 days ago
Yeah I'm thinking it's probably not Jesus as well
But it doesn't actually look as much like the
The default data are the
What herb is the setting date of I thought it would
No it's part 2 episode 2
Yeah that does not seem to be I'm really curious now
I wonder if it's possible to get more data at once from the head reports
Tunis
Marco pasta crumstown spider in Firefox
Itsfunneh sometimes boxel tactical run better in Chrome sometimes better than Firefox I've never figured out why
Jimmy is asking if there's a knot
No there is no non browser version of axel toxic
Voxel tastic is based off of the render engine from no Euclid
Which is not a browser thing it said it's only on regular computer
Tom
If you guys haven't seen no Euclid it's totally worth looking up I think cuz I think it's pretty cool but I made it so I'm
Really biased on that
I think a lot of things are really cool even I don't make them but you know what I do make them I wouldn't do it if I didn't think it was cool
So I guess I could have a larger control message
Yeah I know I'm going to cut it off in about 4 hours and stare over
Jaquez
We didn't actually start recording until about maybe 10 minutes in
Make the buffer bigger and see what happens if I just read it
The control message sent back 128 B
That's interesting
54 cuz I thought that was the biggest you're allowed to make them
I'll print out the character day. Let me just try making sure there's nothing good at the end of this
Oh that's weird
I-Ready togetherness
Yeah
So apparently you're not allowed to make it bigger than 128 otherwise it just gets host
Freak out
I know none of this looks like character data
Yeah it says the same thing the first time and the second so
Yeah I don't think this is configuration data
If anybody wouldn't mind getting some pcap dumps of reading the stator from a actual
Vive on a Windows box that would be pretty cool try and understand what what message I would have to send
You just take the pcap and then send me a copy to be cap
That way we can see how they actually pull the data off
You know I have a 5 setup for their break
What
You can just ask
Weaning I have a virus
UMBC
Have a seal do that later
Switch Amazon
Call
Most with little endian
Bananas looks like actual data so
I mean fffffffffff that looks like a like this might have like Max in it or something
Mac Mac addresses or something better
Infinite rival said they posted
Play
Oh and finish 3000 is
Well somebody said my Rollin them at all
Hell yeah oh cool hey thanks Tyrell
You're up to start piping up and chat so we know that you're all you're working on things
I think he has but
No
StudyLink couldn't wait a minute Herp Derp infinite trivial is nairo
Yes we just went through that okay I did not catch that until right now
Oh wait you LinkedIn chat did you also posted in the the issue cuz I can see the issues I can't see chat on my mile
A laptop
Sort through
Help
I'm pretty quick with Wireshark I'd love to be able to do that right now if you have the pcaps I can do that right now on air
Norah infinite trivial where Where is the
He disappointed don't Lincoln chat I can't read it if it's in Chatta can only read it if it's in the
The issue in in GitHub
Sorry I didn't mean to get angry
Nitro can you off
I'm sorry I didn't mean to get angry everything you're doing is so helpful thank you so much
Yay thank you
Which one which number do you think would be the most likely to contain
This one may be turning the wireless controllers on
First to do you think that's where it would be
What which recipe or I'm specifically after the messages that would pull the configuration data from the
From The Watchmen controllers so probably am guess
But if it lives on the the controllers and how would that be possible
Poet lived the actual controller from selves controllers
Delhi Metro they do take a little bit once
Turn on Netflix
And use USB.
Addressee
What contains 1.11
1.1.1
1.11
Oh really
No nothing
Not 1.1.1 either
Process not using a mouse
We spent 15 minutes fixing the mouth
At the beginning of the Stream
I don't believe an actual mice
I mean I use them sometimes but only you know whenever I believe touchpads are a completely cromulent
Mechanism for a kid getting human input into computer
Get out
Not really I thought I was going to tell your first flight
Absolutely love having a surface
Iwawa
Okay here's a bunch of USB controller
Does a Surface Pro
Fac3
What alphabets say configuration
See here
Interesting art
Oh that's interesting it so it looks like what's going on is it sending something that tells it
Dear watchdog or watch Watchmen please send me your configuration and then it keeps pulling it
I think that's what's going on listen to a different device altogether
Ice picture 1900s
But I don't see anything being returned
I mean
Wow hello data
78 9C
Now that looks like some magic
That looks exactly like the kind of magic I'm after at least 79
She is a valid Jesus thing
It's not Jesus what is the
Online gzip calculator I guess I would say
190 + 111 / 2
Deflate
Haha
I guess I was a little loud sorry about that
Surprises
But something happened in order to get that what did they do to request it
Two starts there
So what did they say 1.1 1.0 was
Brandon
190 and 1 11:00 or the 12
Not wrong
When you say the wireless controller so like the package is going to the controller here
Is that like the actual same device that I would be talking to when I'm beat like getting the light data to and from the device
Oh yeah I know I know I'm going to do that in a minute but I just wanted to make sure I'm actually looking at the right thing and that I can actually talk to this I don't have to
Do something wacky to get a tub
Start talking to some other way
I guess
That's awesome thank you Night Raw
I do not know enough about usb particles to not be totally confused by this
Hey so online sees I ca-78 9C in this USB
Control packet
And what happens if you speaking for packets is it's a really simple command you sending control packet and it sends you dated back
But I specifically I've been looking for something it has 789c in the s b
Because I know that valve compresses whiskey zip
The
They take the config data compress it down and then put that on the
On the controller or on the device and that's the compressed configuration data
So because I see this 78 9C
I know that somewhere around here they're sending us some magic
Dust that makes it go and give me the data
Heck did you figure out that 78 9C
Was there compressed data
Oh okay so the way I do that so frenchton saw what I just did here was I took data I just said test
And I compressor using the deflate algorithm
And so this thing just returns it in in base64
If it base64 eyes it and dump it through hexdump it starts with 78 9C which is the magic that says
Deflate compressed file and
Something about the weights decompressed and that's what the 9C is but I don't really know what that magic is
That is to Latitude you I've never seen before and I like it
Tom
So
I think I've learned Warren list three hours they have this entire semester
That's depressing
Okay so the conversation with one 11-0 starts here
Control in
3 minute warning
No no it's not really three minutes to soft for hours but we did start 15 minutes in
Let's make it our mission to try to get this the state off this device here in the last few minutes though
Thought so
Conversation with one 1100 adhere
Animal Control message in
Whatever it's just getting some data I don't really care what it does
Control out
Herb setup
Okay so it's saying request length 64
Tri-Valley 3ff
I don't know what that is
Maybe there's another way of getting the
The data from the device that I'm unaware of
Ff8 300 V6 that looks like trash to me
It's not trash that's us sending the Watchmen
Is that some sort of magic code that gets sent to the Watchmen
Yeah I don't know what it is I don't care but I guess that means I should probably be sending it
But it then it looks like if I start issuing
This message here
The request for in
And I just keep requesting it eventually The Watchmen response
Much much
Actually responds with
The actual compression
Stop
Scroll down too far
Well that's weird it sends this data first
Oh weird
Okay wait so
What is the actual control message look like
In
It's right here get feature report
I miss you in a lie to USB control transfer
With the transfer into means I'm requesting data from the devices is how I get the config from the the main
The main thing
And it's using 0 x 300
Or
Data
Waterdata 0
Test request one
W index of 0
I guess that's the interface number
See you sad that it's past here so it's interface interface
Device interface
But they 20 has to be cat
What's the weather for this one
Okay what about this one
Okay so I can supply
Hand starts at all
If I read 11 whole bunch so they're AAA
So that should be responding
Maybe I have to issue this several times to get a response
Okay watch 1000 that's right tags 0
H20
Let's try running it again and see what I say
Know what am I doing wrong why is that not
AOC
Maybe I have to issue the other command first before it'll start talking in any reasonable sense
So I am I'm sending a request one
W value 310
Andw index 0000
But I am getting data back why am I getting data back
No I got to turn that down from 128
This 64x back why is what I'm getting from the watchdog
Oh
Getting negative power Norfolk Power them on
Hey Nara
You think that it saw
I guess you think that they are stored in the
They're sort of the Watchman right now than the other thing
Charles is doing
Noticed what
Top of the Chattanooga
You were asked if you for guy or seek me answered that
What does Charles know about usb album
Charles is doing Charles on his code and he won't respond to anything we don't Shout at the back of his head
Yes correct
Easily 5 minutes
What I was going to say is who watches the Watchmen
Install USB mod on my computer and see what the messages going out at
So I'm sending you control transfer
Ameriquest type is a one request one
W value 310
Devices responding with
Nothing
Nothing at all
So what makes it so different when they ask for it
You actually know what you're doing
So here
The steam stuff is connecting and it's issuing this command
Maybe we need to send the Watchman a command in order to get the Watchman to start responding
Okay
Float config
How make another parameter that has an extra magic flag
I don't think I already learned
Yeah I don't either
Where the controllers officially called Watchmen
I don't know
Sister reference that's the reference I've seen everywhere
Just a lot of people refer to them as Watchmen
I didn't like houses are called lighthouses but
Let's just in the official documentation what they call him
So now and here
Send extra magic so if it's a Watchman we might need to send these extra messages that are being sent by Steam
Say start here
The first one starts with
Request one
301w index 0
Watch for the surname of any lighthouse receiver including the hmd and the controller
Then why in the world do they specifically called the other is Watchmen
It's probably a lot more going on than hmd controllers the elections play delinquent
Capelets run this
Brett from first 64 that looks interesting let's look at the data
Anita
Coffer something
Terrible allergies
Sorry okay
How to get rid of the stupid for Scentsy thing
So the first ones tagged Euro 1030 to
That looks like some interesting data
And that's definitely different data than I do know that's right that's good that's really good that's that's perfect
Guess what it's still coming back from the valve 01 03 02
So that means I have successfully finally was able to talk to one of the Watchmen and say something
I think we make sure that I'm talking to the right device
Yep I'm talking to device number 2
So I can talk to the Watchman a little bit
Okay let's see what the next thing that has to get done is
So after that
Send
Albertsons a
Message out
Quest 93 FF
Riverside puts it into some sort of like read mode
I'll just try skipping messed up cuz that makes me nervous
The next one is a control in
That makes me less nervous
By the way the reason why are the way I blew away the configuration that's that was my son to control out when I should have sent a control in so just
Deleted the whole configuration file
Second-guessing
Yeah I'm going to avoid those messages
His best yeah yeah
What's just try this once without sending the control message I'll see if it
Takis Takis
Can't you just go to reset
No
You can't
Discovered this the hard way
So it returns
FF
Oh
Bombs
So is their thing when they run it return something meaningful
When I run it returns just a bunch of zeros
Yes it returns a bunch of zeros for me
I might need to send a control message that makes me so stupid nervous
Is anybody else has got more familiar with
More familiar with the way the hidden requests work that they'll be able to look at this packet and tell me
What it really is doing so I don't have to worry about damaging my Watchmen
Also I want to see real quick if they send something else to say
Replay mode
May don't
Baby here
That makes me so nervous I don't want to do it
The magic what are some that look like
Doesn't quite look like that either
Okay
Play white guys I'm going to go turn this off now
And what Imma do is going to get Adam to backup the configuration on these Watchmen so we don't accidentally blow it away
And then what I'm going to do is just use exactly the same messages that values in order to know send
Nothing to watch Venom pull it back off
And I guess you'll just have to see the summary video that'll be coming out sometime later this week wait
In the next few days
Stalin
You'll be quite noticeable if you know what to look for
Allen
I can see in these these Wireshark dumps you're sending a control message out
And then when you send this other control message n
The valve thing totally or sorry about the valve thing the watch man totally gives us gives you data back
When I run it however
The Watchmen does not give me data back instead of f whatever it sends FF you said you get f
I got FF
Male actually
If you think you might be able just get me though the configs for these I don't have to go over and back
Back him up
If you want to just get the shot right now
I'm just so nervous to
Accidentally blow it away
Oh
Alan what I'm trying to do is get the configuration off the Watchmen by treat the Watchmen
Like the
If I treat the Watchman like a bhmd it just doesn't send anything at all from the
From the configuration data
It just nothing
On what it's looking like is that
And the actual thing that you're doing
You're you're sending the
So you're doing the same sort of thing so like I in order to get the config like I will send a 305
Start a chat
But
No I know I can use Lighthouse console to get the configs but I don't I have to go over to Adam's room
Do all that stuff to back everything up before I can start pulling the config here in this code I have to be able to make this code pulled
The config the self
So
Okay
Yeah okay fine fine Allen I'll go do that
Actually Adam
If I plug the Vive in out here
Can you ask you to command at the the lighthouse Consul I'll email to you
Emails a bit of a pain with the way I have it all set up
Can one of you guys email him the link is in issue number five
Go to issue number 5 on live survive and pull out the
Adam can you open up just get hub.com seeing lures
Flashlight survive
Okay I guess we'll go do all this right now
No I've learned that's why we're going to be backing up the configuration
Methuen plug everything in
Be boring
Say what I think
Look up issue number five
And somebody posted a link to the narrow Lighthouse redox thing
And from there you can
I get all that Oso internet you might think this is entertaining I don't have access to computer
Fast enough but Adam in the room back over there does so we
We actually
Cuz I can
Are you doing
You can see right there in the very center there is cable coming out of the
Attic that goes down to Adams computer so that we can actually
Get the data get the
USB and everything
From his room out here
So I'm going to go
Was this is the USB extension a player can pull off at config so we don't accidentally blow it all off
So
That right there is now going to Adam's room and I'm going to try to get Adam to back up the config file so
We don't have to
Totally
Blow that away again and go through another couple hours misery
USB extension
Long-ass active USB extender
HDMI
Wow
Let's audit doesn't list the lighthouses
In there
Palm it's a different LHC number it's
Well I guess it doesn't say on the box does it
Yeah those serial numbers are different than the serial numbers in the
Can you
So I'm going to open up the configuration file
For my headset
And find out hopefully in there to list what the lhr numbers are
Home
Bummer
I guess I didn't post the actual file unless get Adam to open the file and look at it
Hey Adam email
The Watchdog the other person
Watson or coward on open it
A Charles
I'm going to hit plat ad
It playing at
Play an ad also
Danger
Something
Yeah
Okay. Power ours plugged in video is not plugged in give it a shot
You know almost anywhere
What
I need help
Okay
So I can't figure out how to back this up right now let's see
He's saying that
Sorry to hear all your all if you're here they'll be really helpful
.
Does anyone know how to get the lhr number for the controllers
Cuz it's just not showing up in the lighthouse console
Oh
Looks like cereal
Hey Adam
Did not show it when he run Lighthouse serial
What are you running Lighthouse console serial
It only shows it for the
For the hmd not for the
These guys just like these guys actually being hooked up
And like green so
Not sure what's going on there
The USB descriptors
Not mean I just I want to use the lighthouse saying from valve to backup the configuration
And it's already on these guys
So that nothing
Goes
Like Bonkers when I go send it some commands
I think I need to send it
Get the configuration stuff I don't want to Nuke it
Lighthouse console space cereal and it only shows the
Hmd number or sorry the lhr numbers for the hmd
And not for the
The Watch
Dog watch band
Which is really confusing cuz it does show up in Steam
Not sure what's up with that
What is lsusb going to tell me she's going to tell me the the the descriptor number is not anything I can backup
The configuration
On the The Watchmen with
Oh that's a reasonable point I guess I can plug these straightened Adams computer
Um yeah does that mean I do need to plug it in to give it to talk
Disembodied human arm
I'll never see that until he goes to edit the video
Asriel's common
Indeed
The person that said
Yes I know
Invested
Wow
Funniest
Looks like compact falsified rescued
You want to say goodbye to everyone
Oh I meant like Dave cuz I'm about to head out
All right well have fun with the backing up of the update I'm going to
Well you already had funny
I think I'm going to head out
But a lot of fun
Thank you for coming to hopefully we'll get to the point where we can start using your stuff soon
Brenton Adam just emailed a copy of the configs can you connect the
Are you opening Earth put them in the issue number five
A store pastebin to issue number five
Or like not Jesus but like
I don't even remember my password
And apparently it's a token now
Something
Goodbye Dave
Look at him leaving
So sad
Brendan still here though
Okay
We got the config backed up so all is well now
Anyway now I can go Sunday things data
And I don't have to worry about really terrible things happening
At least I don't think I do
Let's get it crackin
So it looks like they send this message
Which is W value
3ff
See what we normally do
Update feature report
Only resends not that
So
At least 09 code yes be requesting 93 FF
So you should be able to use update feature report this function here
To go send that value
By Dave
Control
Your quest 9W lenk64
What am I missing
Cuz we should take a look at the data though that's coming back I don't understand how that works
Sure whatever I will
How does that work it says it's going to from host to their from host to their
Nitro are you still
Waited anyone get to somewhere on the post Lucia come yet
I'm back in
When you get back in chat and see what's happened earlier
I mean
VK Tuesday's been saying things
We were finding the position of the the o.c. I'll show you that part but you missed a little bit
Earlier was were using this point-cloud to approximate the positions of where it thinks
Be at the camera Mighty this is pretty terrible the way that this one was configured
But we do have other other ones that when we ran it produce some pretty good results
I can show you some of them I think that I still have some of those files around
Under combiner
Whoopsies that's wrong
Say what
Looking for external
Yeah that's fine
Okay so here
This was also I guess I'm a bad dataset but someone they get pretty good this is the point cloud
Oldies of the the
The thing being in any one location
So this is
In case you wanted to
See that
Specifically to Alan that's kind of the recap there
Change that so it's a little bit more restrictive
I'm so here you can see that like chances are it's probably somewhere here and probably somewhere here the one thing I thought
Thought that was really unusual was that the
I was able to approximate the distance really well and like we measured with a tape measure and it was accurate within like 23cm
But the actual like up down position of the the
What do you call them this was not quite as good
Lighthouse was not quite as good
Two places at once we use to lighthouses that wants if that's what you're asking we're trying to find location of both
Lighthouses
Yan are all if you're still in here I really don't want to know do I need to send the stator or do I need to
Just send the really short thing
I don't necessarily know
Oh whatever I'll just send the shorts thing and we'll see what happens
Oh you know what I need to plug the
Bring back in
Everything was static
No emotion at all there is somebody else who wanted it with motion
Our who was somebody in the issue wanted me to collect some data with an emotion so I did take that
And I do understand now that there's no way with just the headset alone for you to determine the exact location of lighthouses
Takes additional data because there's just really no way to
Resolve the
The shell down to an area that's much smaller than maybe a decimeter and a half
Cuz you already at the point where it's like
So precisely like it's right there but like moving the camera little bit would produce like micrometers if
Prince on the effect of position of the
Centers all man
Helena
Huot's you get a chance he's probably just re-watched the first part of this live stream because just the very first B it
It kind of goes into
All of that status
Okay
Let us try this again
Did you record the cursor apart
I know I think we did record that was Paul we were recording
Oh yeah okay Allen you might not want to watch the very first few minutes
And then he came out with a solution
Switch to buy 5 minutes
What is the end goal of this they want to know why
Nope I won't know why sorry
Not sure exactly what he was
Talk about but
Quesadilla
Probably
XVideos
Bomber
So what do I actually have to send this to tell to get me the configuration
I was trying to find lighthouses right now I'm just trying to figure out how to
Get the Watchmen
To tell me there are
They'll need their config files
Nothing though
I'm really confused by this one thing though if anybody
Particularly use 2 USB I've never seen anything where
FF
Okay I'll buy that
Cosme
So no I don't understand how that works it's like sending a message that's empty
But then it's getting data back on a control out message
Never seen that
I don't understand how that works
Yes in fact I am wire sharking this USB connection
That is how I'm looking at what I mom
Doing right here
In the code
Part of
Salt so
Goats bar shark
Is using USB pcap or USB monitor one of them
But Wireshark totally understands exactly what you're talkin about
God send the control out
See what I can compare the official valve thing to mine
ISO game request is 21
Requested 9
Caillou 3ff
00 64
Okay I guess I'll send one of 64 length
Turn 64's let's see what that looks like
21:9 3ff
00 64 but then it sends the data fragment immediately versus in his stuff
It sounds that later
Why would his message have that later
Oh whatever I'll just copy it
Are you guys in chat
Everyone's talking about
Dementia
David school project has actually been importing virtual.boy 25
I've got to work. One
Okay I'm sending seriously the same thing right now why is this not working
Obviously YouTube
Halt to
That
That's weird
Oh wait no now it's fine
No
No it is it's getting fault - 9
That's
Really confusing
It's all so confusing cuz it's soon as I sent that message the Washman just turns off
The code for naptime
Clearly that's not what it wants to talk about
Do you want to send it blank
Wow in the world
Stop turning off
I don't get it
I think I'm sending the same message
Or something
Stop insulting The Vibes mother
Wait did I ever insult
Alan other than that one day that I didn't know it was Allen
I don't know what you're saying over USB would be probably is holding its mother
I don't want to talk to you no more
Send it anything it's like I don't know since being -9 and then turns off Luckett just turned
Stop
I'm not
Why is the thing just turning off
Avesta
Turn off
I'm not even
It still turns off
Get feature report
Are you just
Not allowed to read the configuration when it's wirelessly connected
It doesn't make any sense
So he was saying something about what is the actual process
Remind me at 4:20
I don't know actually
They come prepared right
Do they I don't know if they come prepared
Thumbs down macalino to hook up to the Box
Hmd whatever
The only time I've ever had to plug my phone into USB word update the firmware
How to make slime
Pace that matches perfectly
But then there is this magical control out message which makes the controller your friend
I do not know how this works I have never
Ever
Seen an out USB control message
That will accept data
Back
Now you sound like
Controller keeps turning off even if I don't send it that message that causes it to freak out
Play it stays on
Trust me a different message
I've been poking it that
It does actually returned an error code
U r b status broken pipe
Hospice compare these two
20193 FF
Then if I send a control message you just dump the whole thing
And returns Anni Piper
Okay
What time is it here it is 203
I think I'm going to give up to the fridge tonight until I can figure out how to read the configuration data off of the
The Watchmen
Unless somebody online is willing to go give that a shot
Then the next couple steps are going to be able to slay the Watchman down on the floor
With the ihnb in the middle and try to resolve a little bit better the locations of the lighthouses from that
I was hoping that that would not be the case
Does anybody else have any major points or anything they'd like to talk about before
Closing up shop
Yeah I think it's time to call it quits tonight
They're still alive
Checked it and it halfway bug is still in the V6
Extreme I don't think I'ma do it next weekend
But I'm I'm hoping that you guys can start doing more
Work with the
And vika Tuesday you're talking about making sure they are all
Emails you
Neural if you have it I really
Hey I really want to understand so
What is going on can you just stick around for a minute just did the Delp me out here cuz
I have never seen
Aur bhi control message
That accepts data back from the device used to be out
You are bee control message that accepts data from the device
And that's what I'm think I'm seeing here where I think you're sending it
20193 FF
But you're not sending any data
And
All the tapping is for getting data back from the device
Does seriously like does anybody have any idea what's going on with that because I have no idea
I have never seen anything like that
Nothing
Mural
Anyone
I have never seen a message like this
I have no idea why
I'll just have to play with it more offline I guess
Well thank you everybody for coming out today I'm going to close this down and then upload and it'll probably
I'll be ready mid day tomorrow
Tips for watching
Allstream Allen if you're interested I think the
The pictures that we made with a 3D thing we're kind of meet earlier on
Other than that not really much else
I'm going to go plug this back up in a couple minutes and make sure we didn't just totally blow
Away the Watchman or something but it is still green so can't be that bad
And
Oh hey no dear all we got like all the wireless packet stuff Dakota that's all fine
I just want to get a copy of the config off is all I'm after
Yeah what is going on how in the world do you have a control message that
Just don't know
Okay sorry for this being another anti-climactic closing to another
Great deal of effort
Sing
This is hacking this is what you
Should expect right now
Disappointment in the tears of those who are attempting to
Do anything before progress
Got it okay so you just don't want to mess with anything in the Wi-Fi thing I a k
Well thank you everyone for coming out
I do have to let it run for like another 10 seconds to clear out the buffer
Yeah
By everyone
My colon
Pregnant baby