So have randos drop-in just going to say I'm not recording guys
You guys can do her it's like we're just starting right now I want to
He's the one that's actually coming up in the video
Okay looks like it's coming up for me
Hey everyone hold on here still trying to figure out when people start rolling in
Will be doing like the official start
Yeah probably maybe
No no
How to make a note about that
Crew launch
Oh that's right we have notes oh no we didn't do any of the things on the nose
Oh no I didn't bring my microphone
We did some of them though
Okay got it
Howdy from New Zealand
Hello Bruce
Hi everyone
Cuz it was a bad like Batman
You could have named it through swings
Maybe 20 man
You don't I do them in the evening it's so convenient for so few people
2 p.m. in Tasmania
How convenient is that
Pennsylvania
I think most of the complaints you're getting are from Europe though
Yeah sorry European I'm going to try to start doing it earlier it just doesn't work
Hey everybody how are the levels like is this good if I yell into the mic real loud is that like painful
When John speaks John speak
John speak
At full volume it's like
It's a bit much but it's what about you are you
Let me see testing123
Yes it painful. Okay I guess I just have to learn how not to yell
Don't y'all what are you can you guys hear John when he starts talking
Okay okay I guess I should probably turn it down just a hair
Yeah it is 5 I'm going to try to make this a little bit shorter
I really want to make sure
Yeah I got it I got to actually commit to code more to also we don't have a Adam here today so we do
Don't have like the awesome computer thing going on so I hope that this doesn't like overload my
My poor little laptop here
Don't know I just closed it
Nope not yet I actually just purchased all of the parts for desktop
Slow shipping to take my time
Everyone who
I love bottom desktops I'm going to re-enter the world of of desktop users
My laptop but
The song
I'll just painfully slow to edit 1080p video
Do the windows but you should probably just come over here too
Scump
Doesn't know I know I know
We'll start doing things at
Okay
That's actually more like 10 minutes from now
No although I do have a new esp8266 Gadget that I will be presenting later on
This coming week
Sex with an IMU and a bunch of other stuff all kind of crammed into it the biggest feature of it is that it has
Has a lithium ion battery charger like at the same time as having the circuit for USB so you can just like
Like plug it into micro USB while its operating and it charges its battery and then you unplug it and it keeps
Working so have you got cursor is do you guys see my cursor today there is a cursor
I hope you see it
Can you see my cursor miles
Yep it's there
Okay good good
Oh hey wow that's weird
Twiddling around others
Yeah
I guess we'll will let this thing go for a second he rents shrink this window
Okay and keep that up
Let's chat
People
Yeah I would do after use a really low-res preview on my laptop otherwise just gets out of hand
What's a wemos I've never heard of that I've seen it on Twitter but I never
Directly looked into what it was
Good luck today
Hot sign is actually something that
We put together
Or aiyappa
That was Adam Charles
Did the wiring right and then
Give me that in the shop super off
Yeah we for Unity if you guys know anybody who wants a sign like that it is Wi-Fi controllable
So I can take my cell phone here and connect up to it
Strong mode
Take my cell phone and if I connect into it it automatically connect to my cell phone
As you can
You can't really see clearly yet it does have an esp8266 into in it which is I guess
What else would you expect
If I visit
192.1 58.4 .1
Right there it loads the
For the house
Floods that the little webpage for at the control so I can go under
LEDs
And you can see that it's showing via the effect that's going on right now
And Kane fused I don't really know how to pronounce his name but he
He put a lot of work into this to make me a really nice interface
So LED pattern to say it was 14 was the good one reason
And
So just by using the phone I can go click the button and it it changes the patterns
Thalia product if you guys want to get custom signs made we totally do it
Hell yeah I know what I'm doing doesn't really have anything to do with that
Packer
Is that how you pronounce your name Packer Acer paker pack
Packard Bell
Throwback
Let's see how many people do we have in this 42
That seems like a nice number start with 4343
Person but we were waiting for you
Packer got it
Okay I guess I said 15 minutes 10 minutes
It's only 7 minutes away
Sure let's just keep on chilling or things going well humidity you have no idea where
You're going with this
All all say something whatever I'm getting to the point
Communicate
Facebook texts
Speak now. So yeah
Break it down
Yeah what's up
Why I said where is the common core for scientist
Redundant I will get into what I'm doing tonight at 10:15
10:15
Guys on topic
Is just saying where's the the new math for
It's okay
I don't need a phone off
I have
Have enough
K I'm blind LOL
What
I don't know somebody named
Redundant HD Thursday I'm blind
Hi blind I'm Thomas
See if I can get all this out
Every moment we can
So strange to see you here and then here
Doing different things I can do two things at once if those things are slightly offset by a few seconds
310 the morning in the UK
And this other person says they are Christmas drunk in Ireland High Christmas
Call Justin
Plugging in the Vive right now this day will be
Today that I have the least preparation before the livestream to do the livestream so it's going to be pretty much by the Sea Tow
All of our pants
Apparently Christmas frog is different from regular bra
Okay
Memory NEOS it's about 5 seconds I say
Yes of Hitler
Lochmoor whiskey involved in Christmas frog
Also keep
On topic
And we do have the YouTube Community guidelines so
3 minutes to go
2 minutes to go
Start a few minutes ago
Time
Tim Henson
30 seconds
What is the global today
No it's not just the been coding decoder
It's a it's a couple things this is going to be kind of recapping what works being done right now
And
You guys can wait one more minute to hear what it's about well minute half here but it stopped
Pisces
I don't know who you are
One minute
Venice in the chat he thanks you for the caramel for
Oh hi Ben I'm sorry
But for those of you who
Oh gosh I don't have a picture
I'm going to have to go off stream for just a second
Then I don't believe Adam hasn't Twitter does he
No Adam does not have a Twitter
Just make sure you guys couldn't see anything could you
For that bit it was just like a black screen I'm guessing
Okay good good
Oh yeah
He responded Charles
It's black when I switch back to my my personal account
Sound on my laptop I do everything else from this account I think I'm actually doing this logging into a hardware terminal
Rpt terminal by definition of virtual terminal but
Weight GT terminal virtual terminal
It's like ATM machine okay
Okay
I think it's time to get started
Okay everyone thanks for coming out to the 5th live stream now it's actually the third in the second row
Group or we try to find the locations of the lighthouses I think there may be some other ways to come about this but right now
Now I'm kind of heading down the whole find the lighthouses but before we even get there if there's just been a ton of problem
We've been running into just like one after another after another mostly due to the fact that I'm terrible of coding
Which makes me wonder what I'm good at but on any rate so we're going to have to today figure out
A little bit more about what's going on with the Watchmen a little bit more about how to do some of the disambiguation
Of the light timing signals and I don't know maybe I'll be able to get a chance to show you guys a little bit more about what
What we talked about in the
If you know it that's a much better place to start let's actually start going through the issues right now
So some of the the issues by the way I encourage everybody to join along checkout a copy of
I've survived if you have I've fired up on your bike and if you have problems with that
Patchett
Do a push request and I'll handle it
That is if it works make sure your code Works before you do the pull request
So some of the things the one the issue from the last time determining the location of lighthouses is now up to
297 comments from just about everybody and this was from the
From the livestream event that we did two weeks ago at my parent's cabin
So punch people visualize where the points were realized we got the normals wrong
Amazing things happened where Ben was able to get HTC to send me my config file so I could
Unbrick the the Vive
And we started to really dig in a bunch of different techniques were kind of brought up
Perspective npl like the PNP problems
And I don't remember the name posit I think it was positive
Was that name of the technique I'm just various techniques 54 talked about to do what it seems like we're
Trying to do
But one of the really big things is that the problem with the Vive is different from that
And Alan Yates the guy
I guess we should call him the Godfather of Lighthouse technology now
Actually buy the wave and if you can reply and chat and tell me if if if Yates is actually doctor Yeats
Somebody said dr. Yates and one of the things I'm really curious if I should be calling him dr. you
At any rate
They pointed out that
He pointed out that all of this mess that has to be done with like pasta and the PNP Pro
Problem missing I can find the opencv
Epmp paper
I think this is it
No that's not it
I can't find it point is there's all these really complicated techniques to figure out where cameras are
Based on like three representations of the environment
And it's really complicated because of such a mess that there is with all the stuff
Torsion and everything else that exists with cameras people try telling me that that's the future of VR and that's just
Completely bogus because
It's just totally impossible to calibrate to anywhere close to the scale that Lighthouse thickness
Knology can be calibrated to a lot but for the most part I think that we're kind of shy
Flying away from some of these already existing Solutions in really trying to forge forward with our own
For better for worse if you out there I'm talking to you anybody who knows how to coat it all one steak
The crack at this problem for this part of the problem I do have all of the other the files of
Available under common data for project
So if you want to go give something a shot and try to like pitch in and see if you can figure some of the stuff out
I do have a CSV that recorded from the the real systems
That's all right there
At any rate so determined location lighthouses
A ton of fun stuff
Having hard time here
A bunch of fun stuff happened
PK tubes if I can find his post
Oh
Something else we forgot about a half a day finally posted Allen yates's talk
I can't find it here where we relegates actually went into
By the way it's been responding chat been said you should totally call him.
And then someone else has responded that his Lincoln does not mention doctor so okay
You should call him dr. V K Tuesday no it's okay you stalked I renamed
Altus dr. yang
So dr. Yates totally explained in his
And I wish I could little bit older for getting closing in on it
I totally went into a lot of details about the hardware and software problems that surrounded
The creation of the Vive and why it was not trivial which I would not expect it to me look stupid easy
But he points out that
I'm obviously not the smartest one in the room when he started busting out the whole point about the fluid dynamics linear
Something fluid dynamics something Motors
I'm like okay got it this is way outside or something I'm going to be doing in my basement
Any rate if you guys do want to go see a really awesome talk about how the lighthouses work
Totally check out the hack of the article
You know what I think I might just post this in the
In the
The read me here
Extra resources pack-a-day article
Article and video with doctor
On how they made the Vive a thing
Okay
Moving on
One thing we had a note on his but I do need to do more get pushing and I'm going to really
Make an effort for that this time and I will also paste this into the chat
Hey Charles just try the opencv algorithms I found out today was very noisy with some light filtering I was able to get
I was fairly precisely Octavio if you want and you're up for it
Please please pinch in here start trying to pitch in
Specifically finding the lighthouses we can get away with something other than the MIT license
For what Mayan gold needs to be though I would really like it if we could just keep everything seed and
Everything minimal requirements I know what the opencv stuff you kind of have to pull in opencv
And that's that's kind of a big deal
So going back to all of this
So Alan needs kind of hopped in and he pointed out that the the volumetric plots that we were plotting out
Last time didn't really make a lot of sense to him as to why
Why the data would look the way it did and I totally get that but I think that to me
It made a lot of sense because any of
Well we'll go into Howell my Approach is working soon but he pointed out there was a little bit strange
That's one of the things are going to try today is to try to view that data in a different way
Or or analyzed in a different way that might be a little bit friendlier to finding the centroid be
The most likely location of the lighthouse
Okay
I think anything else
Just that right now my plan forward is by
I'm going to we got to go figure out what's going on with the exact pulses and why some of the stuff isn't lining up the way I thought
I think some of it has to do with the disambiguating being rough
My disintegrator is not very good so if you think you can figure out a disambiguation the signals the pulse
Houses of light and what they mean better than I can which you probably can
I go in there give that a shot
I have an example of some of the code that I did use
It's a little different now but it's almost the same if you look in the GitHub repo
And I collected a bunch of data and we uncovered a bug
One so far which I'm sure there's more with the Bendy coding
So that was that was kind of fun
Pepsi I'm just kind of rambling right now this is there any direction anybody in chat has your questions
Different couple like basic questions they've been trying to summarize like just
What's going on here about like trying to reverse engineer with the Bibleman case
Okay I don't think I want to spend five minutes explaining how the vibe works
In this this this life has to have done that about every other time
I'm sorry I'm going to avoid that this time
So I do appreciate that you guys are kind of chatting back and forth in chat so we can keep things rolling
Figure it out for themselves
It's probably best to do the first video
I like the summer video Summer video yes I am going to try to get a thumri video edited but I
I unfortunately do have another closet commercial esp8266 project I need to go make a video for and
I need to get out the door like ASAP because parts are literally just waiting to go out the
Need to make the video I am sure it later on the broadcast I'll explain that to which at the time
I was not thinking about the buy but now that they might be able to work together
I'm trying to think of anything else that really happened that was that cool I mean just the really The Big Three
Freebasic
Three basic bugs the first fog being check
Been coding to the bank holding is still something's not right with it in my code I'm not interpreting
Something correctly I don't know what it is but we're probably going to have to go scope that out some
That that can be done kind of in parallel with this other stuff
One of the other things has to do with improving
The disc
And big you a tour and that's the thing that can kind of tell me based on these flashes of light
Where is this photo diode based on this lighthouses sweeps
That's going to have to invite where it is I don't mean where it is I mean where it is and 2ds face
So like if I were to shoot a real from the lighthouse where would that go through what point would that go through
That's that's what they needed for and finally
Really doing one or two things one finding Lighthouse positions
Or finding another way altogether
Or something because what we need for face 3 so we're still in phase two of this project which is annoying
I thought we would move in but it's harder than I thought just like everything else I've ever tried it
It's just always more difficult than I could hope
Phase two is where we
Find the lighthouses
Phase three is where we can track a point and a
Hose
And phase four is where we used and
And if you guys have been paying attention to the GitHub things I am really tempted to just Jo
Jump straight there
So I have actually done a fair bit of computer vision stuff before this is a picture from a project from a
While ago where I was just tracking using cameras really really inexpensive planners
Oh got it
Can you say something so I can get your name to moderate
Can't do anything either
Say something in chat and I'll mod you
To him
Set user as moderator
So it's not that I haven't ever done any kind of tracking systems before and I
I have dealt with them
I've dealt with commercial ones and I've kind of rolled my own never had to do anything really precise though
Except for my thesis had to be really precise but that was a different problem altogether so it was much easier to
Much easier to accomplish like
Mm level tracking but it was totally different solution very easy to do
But I know like I'm toying with just creating a pose
Like a
What are those things called where you have like
Seasoning stainless Center
Nothing that has the x y and z
Oh
Display the actors I don't know
But it's like being the physical
Whatever it is
One request from the chat
New I have the chat window on the sides they can see it cuz it doesn't get archived with the screen
Oh okay
Oh I know I do know they want to make it to it that anybody who's watching it later can watch the
I will said it's always on top okay and I will scale this so that that work
Okay
Frame that's the right word I'm just toying with
Using a coordinate frame in 3D space
Plopping it on the floor in the middle having one meter between each one of the stupid accies and then having the light
Lighthouses figure out where those are and then we can just straight-up resolve position
Define their universe
I'm 20 with it
But
Not necessarily
Going to happen
After all it is kind of skipping phases
Phases two and three all together kind of use for to go back to and I have no
No idea how hard it's going to be to use the esp8266 as a detector in this sort of situation
So I really kind of want to go through in order but maybe maybe not
Anything else that came up in chat that I should be addressing right now
Okay so going forward some of my plans on this one
So from last time
Fossil Pathak
If I was using voxel tastic to go visualize some
Some 3D models of how would it look like the the lighthouse data
Who let the knotwork rgba pretty
Yeah there we go
Plastic tube you what the
Have you what the the shells look like what the
The shells are the likelihood of a lighthouse seen any one of these
Locations
And as you can see that it's it was a little bit rough
So
Didn't really work that well
I did try though and we're still going to keep going right now this is being viewed
And kind of Cartesian space
And I want to try to move it into Polar space and I think it's going to like really kind of bound itself into a centroidal
A lot better that way
One of the other things to note is that Alan Yates was a little bit
Concerned over the fact these look like shells rather than kind of blobs
So I don't really know what to make of that right now but we're totally going to look into that
So we can totally just visualize the different possibilities of
Lighthouse not that
Totally pie visualizing different possibilities
Like this is I guess the our Lighthouse where it's like Yeah The Lighthouse is totally in there
Locations jeopardized by the rotated wattles
Steve Hamilton normals before doing that
Doing what the visualization
Remember you were having an issue with the headset normal seeing tilted in
I don't remember that I know that I know that there was a problem somebody had with it but then
I don't believe there's any problem now did we check that before we did the beta
Hope it in ya The Laurels weren't actually facing outward
Play should be there all
Focus play straight down
What's what's the normal time the headset itself at War
Oh
I don't think so
Let me check the one guy did do the open scad thing
So those normals are all Hokie
Those are all Hokie
I don't know what's going on there
I don't know this person visualized the normals and open scad and it looks just fine
Mary Hackman everyone
Anyway
Yeah that one down the bottom
Yeah it does look correct so
Put in timeout how good
Anyway moving on Soviet visualization is kind of a point Cloud saying these are all of the possible places
Could be
How likely it is it is it any of them
I can make it so it visualization sold more so you can see that for at least some amounts of data
It converges really nicely like
You know the head like houses got to be in there so some of the things I wanted to do
Was I wanted to use the normals of which way it's pointed toe
I will not touch the significant now so each one of these sensors
Tear on the headset it has a normal associated with it I was my first look at them like
World they do that
I always I I never go into a situation assuming that I'm
The dumbest person in in the room but I will always be quick to realize that
As best as I can
But Eric was looking at like why would they put normals in with this data that seems completely used
I'm already using
So because there's a normal associated with this it tells you which way is pointed
So all the sudden there's a lighthouse up there behind the camera
And if I hold it like this then
Yeah that that sensor can totally see that Lighthouse but if I hold it like that and it's pointed at that Lighthouse over there
See it so really quick we can just immediately cut out that is a possibility of where those this lighthouses
Because this photo sensor here is getting data from it so you can do real quick
How to cut out
For one of the other things that I doctor Yeats has pointed out through a lot of this is that
The normal itself and the the the angle
And the distance from the lighthouse
Will control the length of the pulse now I'm hoping we collect some data on that this time
To try to get an idea as to how much the distance affects the Paul and how much the orientation affect the pulse
But I'm thinking we can use that
To help narrow down the picture so though the date of might look like this right now
Or I mean I gots a little bit worse if you look at the other one must look at
Our lighthouse
You look at this man it just does not know where that other lighthouses
I'm thinking that by using the normal data and having it like the rotation control that way you can do a
Much better job it kind of narrowing this down I don't know that that's true but I think that's true
The the other thing I wanted to try was to put the Watchmen controllers farther out
I still have this sitting in the center of the room 15 the coordinates frame and having to watch them controllers
Having Watchman controllers on the floor on either side and using them to
Kind of determine like okay it's not possible for this Lighthouse to be here and then this one to be here
Because if this was the case then the geometry for the the
The angles for where the the Watchmen are wouldn't lineup
And to be able to rule out that early come up with the score of How likely or unlikely
That we have the position and composed of a
A specific Lighthouse correct
Spell make it really easy to just kind of start ruling things out and hopefully narrow down where the lighthouses are
See how that goes and I did mention in the the issue that I am toying with just giving
Straight to phase 4
Not doing yet
Think that's it for the summary
I can't really think of anything else really happened over the last week that's
It's that big
The other than dr. Yates posting some cryptic things to Twitter
I'll see if I can find one of them
Calendar dr. I can't remember that time doctor
I posted a really neat picture here of
What happens to the region of convergence for the 2D Lighthouse problem as you rotate the initial speed
Depose
Through a full-term
I'm guessing that means that when you're just making a rough guess in the dark is to what
Where the lighthouse my
What is what happens over time as you move that potential pose I don't know for sure
I don't know there's a lot of nomenclature that because I'm so new to this I have no idea how to even barely speak
The same language is
Is
Fannin dr. Yates because so many times like they here's what you do
And I have to go spend the next like four hours figuring out how to actually do the thing they just completely gave
Give me the answer for
Orientation LightScribe
I believe
Who's Ruby orientation and position
Location I can believe that
I'm not imagine for this for this image yes that's just
From Unity
Okay
But then why would it be the initial seed pose unless he's referring to like Hammer here object here
Lighthouses guesses hear lighthouses get to your Lighthouse to get to your lighthouses yesterday
They don't
I have to figure out where they are
I think what he's saying is
If you have Lighthouse tile and you take that
And then you slowly rotated throw-in combine the data
Change the gas like that
But rotating around what like rotating around the point man gets around itself
Location Point rotational irritating it
But would it be the the the lighthouse rotating or would-be the lighthouse rotating in 3D space around the corner
Well this is just a stimulated
Problem I think
Well you could ask yeah
Dr. Yates
Too late you already know your secret
Oh by the way if you are curious the reason I was thinking doctor Yeats was
I first saw that was
Yeah right here I was somebody who is not named
I mentioned
I see doctor Yeats has already responded to more intelligent posting to threaten us like dr.yeh
Dr. Gates entity color is the number of the aeration totopos Verge 21
Um position urad wrote a orientation
Wait one micrometer micro rod
That would appear to be the case
Is that using fake ideal date or is that using real like did you actually capture some data cuz
There is no way I'm getting any of my data to converge to Within
Purple is where one micrometer singular
Singular
Yeah
Oh no
Photomath
I heard jacobia before so you're actually somehow I don't know what the problem would look like
Matrix problem that can just convert
I would be me to send me I just looping through a raise and just hoping for the best
Yeah I did see a doctor Gates's hackaday presentation video in fact
With all of the hacker. Hack a day
But just sounds funny when I say all of the hack of anyway all of the hackaday
Presentations from the hackaday superconference like even hoses there for one of them that I should have just
Gone like that would have been so worth it
Just to mean any one of those talks now
I would have been there I would have known
The month sound I when was the Super conference obey weeks before I knew about it
Cuz it is a little bit sad that I did not even find out that this Lighthouse system existed it all in
Until like
The week before Thanksgiving
400 * 1
23 is a lot different than 400 times and p array
Oh are you making fun of the fact that
That my
Okay you guys are starting to I know you guys know what you're talkin about to each other
But I think there's some information
Not
Oh no
MPI mean unless you're making a joke at me about my Approach being
On polynomial but it is by definition
Polynomial right like oh van to the 6th which is how terrible my algorithm is it still polynomial
That was my own python bug
400 000
100 * 1231 copies of 123 but I don't understand what that has to do with
Okay
Got it I'm as you can tell I'm not a python guy
You want me to go right this out will that
Well that's a laptop dying
Closing that closing that okay
What did you do to it
It's just so slow it's just that flow
Come on come on okay
Is a lot different than
I must see what this looks like
Injecting says he's solving future Lee health problems while you're solving salt float
Where did he say that
Absolutely earlier it's going to be 10 Jackson is solving future lighthouse
Problems while I'm solving solve Lighthouse problem yeah I totally believe you
But it's someday someday I'm going to be solving Lighthouse problems that will
Will never be your Lighthouse problems
In fact they will be Lighthouse problems I will create entirely of my own accord
Like the third
Why why do they exist says that
Operation not a scalar multiplication
Oh that's cool so it's like almost like
Finken convolution
Would make 400 400 123
Tannerite x 400 but I regret that I don't understand what that has to do with anything we've been talking about
Unless that has directly to do with the picture you posted to
Anyting
Okay
Laptop is
Cuz this is like I think it was
The first
I5 of the type but it's a 2450m which is
Like I guess a little bit faster than a quarter to Duo but it's absolutely
Cuz the laptop itself is like
Tony
Nope.
Okay
I also feel a little embarrassed I can't even figure out how to like
Make
No I don't have them hot
What
ShopRite of Ono
Oh wow okay just turned away out
Okay
Looking like a lot of background fresh yeah I know it's coming through
Normal microphone a little annoying
Let's hope that I can
What's the okay is the sound back to normal now can you guys hear clearly
The answer is don't put the laptop over while the webcam is plugged in because
Laptop also has terrible
So
It's really loud. High game
Well no cuz that's going to sound all crunchy
Okay hold on
Can you guys good now
Good now it's odd that doesn't
I hope I won't need to reboot
Stream to get that to work
What about if I just leave the volume down is this is this microphone good for everyone or
Balada background humming system humming okay got it so we really have to figure that one out
Timolol do I will just pause and restart
Laptops on board Mike I am but now I'm trying to push away from it okay can you guys hear me clearly
Really now does that work
Oh you got it okay if that's the answer whenever that happens I felt so good Lord
Oh my gosh so many messages
Okay
Song
Backcountry
All in an effort to just click on copy and paste this one thing
Oh you're saying that's a lot different then that no
Steve values Racine position or something that was for the
Dr Yeates Twitter video Twitter picture
No I don't think so region of Yeti solver convert
Initial seed pose through full-time
Yeah sorry this definitely works better with simple screen recorder OBS definitely when I
Never I have Adam's laptop and Olivia anyway I don't actually have a released
I would plan for today other than I was going to collect some data
I think he's had enough of the doctor Yeats is no academic credentials Beyond ice cream
Summit research
I'm clearly not a real witch doctor
Dr Yeats what is your title if valve or your position
Never really asked
We don't have pedals are positions that tell
Very
Abnormal culture as far as companies go there if you're hired
You're basically on the same one
That's a little crazy
It is very unusual
That is crazy
Basically there are no bosses or
I guess the only person who would have
A little more weight pull would probably be given
Okay but yes there's no official losses
I'm still pretty sure
Keith
Just released Kawasaki cardiologist neurologist like phrenology like brain phrenology
Okay let's see
Lucky Lighthouse virologist
Is that
But actually what that mean
Neurologist video cut out for me
I know why
Okay just came back hold on let me Jack in myself moving now
Okay and hopefully it will connect in
Streaming on Wifi bad
Yes okay now we're actually streaming on regular so good to go
I think we have
Stalled enough here
Coco somebody
And let's make sure that
Some of this data will actually work
Actually I need to make a new issue
Daytona recorder
I know it make clean all cuz I know I've done a lot of stuff that could break that
Guitar tuning
Right now
Work the first time tracking tracking but collecting date
Data from the
This thing
Timer
But I didn't move
Sudo get install coffee
Yes
I could go for some right now it is 11
Oh I'm sorry Mindy
I got a song but like
I thought for 5 hours after work
That's weird
What's weird
There's like one pose I can get it in where we just say it's freaking out sometimes
Oh I am too close. Yeah I think I am
I actually to close is that
Use the venerable Ben
What is your title
We have dr yates and the problem is that prevents
Terrible prevents me from getting too close to Lighthouse
Cuz the regular actual data pulses that sweet
Are so long when you get that close to the lighthouse because as the date of sweeping over
I just take so long to go poop that I'm entering the pulses is those
They were actually coming from a lighthouse itself
So that's why if I get this
Papa. Bear
So we have the lighthouse up there
And then I'm going to go sweet this down to me
Sony here
Lighthouse up there be here lighthouses there
Okay
So you'll see that these numbers right here
The column right here so if it's far away that they're relatively small
Scrap for
Can you turn around and face this one and make sure the other one can't see it
Towing
Gay an alpha around the other way
Why is that not a quarter
Is what we're doing right now
How in the world am I ever going to do this in like 5 hours a week. Where you want me to
Oh that's a good point indeed have to do this from scratch
Something's freaking it out right now I don't know what that is
Ben is the best guy and after Gates of heartbreak I
What doesn't make any sense the hell I've received it
Figure it out I'm sorry right now Chief virologist Gates
Right but why is it freaking out and of course then says he's a terrible math guy
So I know math people but they've never been able to can like convey to me
In a way that I can have some time but it's very rare that they can convey Matthew things in a way that I can understand
So very often I just end up doing terrible things to get by I'm curious if that's similar
Bodenheimer asks how important are the flashes are we using them
Location in this instance
In order for us to figure out where to plot the points on the screen which not doing too hot with right
Right now
Don't know why in order to do that on the screen here for the
Not working but
I'll make it work but most the time
What I do is I time the difference between the flash of light and what time they get swept so as I move
This way in this way
You can see it moving up and down a fair bit also it is I have never
Never seen it this glitchy me see if I'm just doing something terrible
Jittery hard to say buy a book computational forum
Optic
Am I doing
My wife
How to take care of I'm not doing something dumb lately divorce Eightfold attend at you later
No I need her first of all that is what the other guy I can remember his name right now while he's working
And it looks promising to me but I have a difficult time really understanding is Kobe
One comment in the entire thing one
Jay pichete I know his real name
File
Disintegrator Dusty Julian picked picked
I can't pronounce his real name cuz I don't know it
Yeah
Haven't give up at 4 a.m. Optik problem solution to our current problem
Okay yes possible
Phrenologist phonology
What was the word again
Virologist virologist
But I guess something's going on and no I'm not stepping on my own memory something's just busted
Boston
Wicked
Come on
Factory Card outlet even still freaking out
That was pretty freaking out
I'm sure
What is going on here
Mustafa's more busted than I realized
Right now we're not actually using
Julian new
Disambiguation her I'd love to use but if I can find the comment
Here, just maxed allowed gift for a match
Okay I guess I can understand what that means
Simply complicated
Be here so why is this doing that
Beta
Go on the things I've been doing a pair of it is printing out date at the distant the UA doorstep to try to understand least what in the world is going
Sort of what's going on
Hold this up until it disappears
Close it out see why in the world that disappear
Okay to talk about right now
I see here it's really simplified as though
We should probably switch mode a
Something something cooler Edge Phillips
Yeah you're right they are JK Oxys I really should Define it that way I like that you guys
Did they saying K instead of X and Y that way it really helped like prevent them of the confusion
Do you like where you're going with the polar coordinate system
What
Show the Cartesian that I've been doing I don't know if they like that
Still
So I don't know
Cartesian in the act like I'm not dealing
Because in order for me to know where I am the 3D space I have to be able to give a matrix to the videogame to say yo but the
Camera here
As soon as I get the video game looked at Matrix
After a lot of other math but I'm going to find out real soon that Cindy really painful but I'm just going to power through it and hope for the best
I can get there I'm pretty sure I can just like
Witches did hopes everything will be fine like
Terrible but fine
But now I do need to know where the camera is in 3D space in order to do that and I need to know where my little ESP
I will not be done just in time for 1 KB challenge even if I was
And I already mentioned before I don't think I'm going to be competing in the one KB challenge cuz somebody already wrote in operating system
It is it
Had the text editor a compiler it's got a file system it's got everything in one sale by
Yeah that was so crazy
Any racist to hear
Okay there we go so why is it
Freaking out sometimes
What is causing it to wig
Just make some changes my algorithm maybe I need to revert that
Oh no I have not done get reverting in so long
I'm doing it live terrible
Suburban
No no wait
I know you would never use Stevia nowadays
How do I view history
History history are you history
History
Call Haley that button right there says that puller should make triangulation easier
But
They want nothing to do with that mask
Going to use them initially to determine the location for Lighthouse and then once and not even that I'm going to
Actually use the color
Poke color coordinate polar coordinates to determine the optimal pose with respect
To the
Stimulated
Triangle thing going on make sure we get the position correct of the the cameras
Everything else in Cartesian
You might have missed it this is free number 5 practice
Git checkout the branch how do you do it
Just check out
I did not copy and paste that I intended to
Says just stick to Cartesian
Finding the centroid of that funny shape becomes much easier if that particular thing is in
Polar coordinate
Where the lighthouses are
Long-wear watermelon way from meeting care about polar coordinates
I think that I think so
I mean I don't think we have to care about polar but I just think that polar will produce a better centroid like the gaussian
Revolution will not be this funky shell which is not God and it would become a gaussian distribution
Which you can relatively easily find the
The centroid of
Okay how do you do this now is that right that work
Little freaking out
No it is not till freaking out so clearly something broken the last couple
RAB and we're going to probably have to figure that out
Totally
Much better right now
See how close I get this
I thought it
So what were actually looking at is the the position from the lighthouses point of view
Of all of the dots on the front of the face of the bhmd
The one on the left is the lighthouse that's on the side
And then the one on the right just one right here is the lighthouse that's up to the upper left-hand
Corner of the unity sign
Okay there I see it better now it was just
You were talking about it but I was watching The Stream So.
I wish that I had the lighthouse in view
Okay so
Cancel that
Figure out where this all went wrong
Some something went wrong somewhere
Oh you know what this is going to be hard because his pretty much supersedes mine
Understand Version Control
Cephas works
Somebody says you should make a Discord
What's the Discord
Discord is a new voice and chat
Program basically it's like having this
But live all the time and it's long so your messages
I received for people that don't know what I guess basically
But it has built-in voice chat too so you can do voice chat rooms as well as like multiple different chat rooms
Are you can assign people different roles like moderators Frosted Flake engineer's or whatever
But it's not in the YouTube chat so
It would give people a place for if they find something there to post it and believe it
Similar to the issues except it's more fluid okay
Discord is the value
If you want to set it up for next time I'm up for it right now though I would like to know the same
So let's see if this fix that
Right now I'm just bug fixing stops if you don't like bug fixing
Not going to be your your day
What is going on why can't it
Oh that's right this was after I started getting the data from the
Okay time power on the Watchmen
I unfortunately changed things a little bit so it requires the Watchman to be online
So can pull the config from them
These guys are now
Got fire them up
I'll look into making a Discord server for you and I'll send you the info
Okay
Noel
Logo
I'll go
Okay
So I have a random question
Neurologist Yates and
Then we have to have a better name for you
In your estimation how long is this going to take us to get to where we want to be are we talkin like
30 live streams or like
What can we just call him Uncle Ben
Uncle Ben
Turn off
Yeah
I just turned back on the Watchmen turn off on their own to some reason
Yeah well I mean I get to make sense if I stopped using it really good
You can look up how long it took you
Oh that's not good that's going to be getting data from these
Free
It depends how much gets done live versus between sessions
I am shooting for a
Maybe about 33% lives 66% behind-the-scenes like
I spent like 4 hours last night just
Banging my head against the wall trying to figure out why why the timing on my bank order stuff was all wrong
Embarrassing
I'm really dumb reasons
Oh how do you like the term been coating to in
That was the
What
Did you say you know I know the bank holding that's going on with the
The Watchmen
Would you say that the lighthouse intersection is Ben coming
No it would be
He does not name everything after himself
Don't know then Cody remember
When you do something and you give it to the world or the internet or somebody
It becomes theirs and they get to determine how is pronounce so like gift or gift
Even though the Creator maintain their called GIFs
Because the internet now owns gifts we've named them gifts
And they will be gapped
And we pronounce the name of animals giraffes
I don't really want to get to like all of my plan to the Lattimer just really lost a little embarrassing but I really really really want to get to eat
82-66 tracking in the scope of a system with the entire system being honest
Of its own
So we don't actually have to
I'd like rely on any of the libraries and we don't have to rely on anything open-source libraries
We got now face Italy found out a lot more incomplete than I ever realized
And more data
Then I have patient for
Esp8266 is 160 +
Esp32 is 240 MHz esp32 is dual-core we'll just see what happens
Go back to the newest
Acer says the SPs expensive compared to the 8266
Esp32
The $3 piece
Cheap as dirt
How much is a Navy 266xp 8285 for a dollar
I think
86 Oz are $2 with the 86 on the board everything else for two bucks so
Box yeah
Agassi would require an extra chip and all but you know you're talkin a buck
Getting something shipped from America to Denmark will cost me a month's rent
No I will ship it to you for $2 and
What is it $2 note $3.15 from us like anywhere in the world
Do you mean you wanted on a dead Ford yeah good luck with that
Still freaking out sometime
That's how I do it if I want to go to eBay and I I buy them
I buy them from
From from the sky here
Guy says taobao is amazing
If you can read Chinese
Specifically I'm not actually allowed to say where I get the distributor for most of the
Scott rotch if he's that I'm aware of so
I do have
I'm actually the guy who fell from everybody and I unfortunately I'm not really able to say who might have to get
Need the chip to go to 32 everybody else so
I just checked out master that means on the new one right
Sure Thang
Twerking
Sure what's going on here
Better watch out somebody's 12-yard microchip Mafia
There's nothing
Illegal about what I'm doing that I'm aware
I think
No, I don't want to copy that I want to
I'm not going to look at that bird
I think I can just India just go buy it off eBay
Try to find a way
By the way that's not just a selling point of the esp8266 that is
The magic of the esp8266 is that it is somehow they will FCC license the module
Without having a
Without already having to have the
Power supply and everything built into the module which I don't understand how they did
Cuz I thought the rules were pretty clear on that
Probably did it and so I'm good with that I'm more than happy to
Use the wonderfulness that some person got ft certified
If you plan on stop
Stop using the 66 S430 to dance around in time I might reduce my
But they really a different purposes so on this particular project with light survive
Ddst instead of E85 which are the esp8266 with the black built-in
Would be really good for just having one esp-4 Center cuz it can sample at 80 MHz
Ethiopian
Have tons of frosting is 150 MHz / LED
And then you can back up the change because they're only a buck up heat
Like
You can just use them everywhere but the sp32 is four different projects for much bigger project 1
Okay I need to go talk to like a camera
Or I need to be able to like I don't know
Do serious lifting like things like
Big project but the esp8266 still spectacular for any kind of small price
Yeah you know what I am going to I'm starting to acknowledge that there's just no way to get serious work
I just made a really loud okay
That that yeah any kind of theories work really has got to get done offline at least for a while I think we really lucked out on the fur
First few live live streams
Where
Where I was somehow able to work and focus at the same time but
Yeah that was clearly a short-lived phenomenon
You've never been much of a speak and code type person either have you know I've never been a freaking code person
I'm trying to get but
And right now all I'm trying to do is just figure out what in the world is going on so the chief pathologist says the penny
Dean and Elena first to get anywhere
Right now trying to figure out if
This disintegrator
Trying to figure out where things went wrong
Ftfe
Pacer says that they have to pay $24 fee for import duties for anything more than $11
Pacer that's just fine because he has keys are cheap as dirt
So
Might try the new disambiguation her and the old one and the
Maybe was somewhere else in the tree that change that I'm unaware of
What is a gift bisect I do not know what it is thank you want to do that right now
That's better, I've never done an operation with get before I don't want to do the operation live on air
I guess not really are
But
I guess some people where they have Wi-Fi connections their houses
Stop thinking
Are there any types of movements we need big tires rotation of headset and translation
Translation
Somebody's husband
I need a question time or something
Yeah I do need to focus a little bit more on
Separating out when I'm actually focusing on working
Talking to people
But I'm pretty adhd's.
So hard to deal
I'm probably not any better than you on that either so
This is probably a terrible combination
I should probably go out farther than I am right now but I'm just kind of like
There's so much going on
What's up
I know that
Isaac automated binary Servpro blog
Marquis commit as good or bad and it lets you move on to the next contestant
Palm
Yes that does sound like something really good
Painter if you would like for you to pacifically do you buy it off me on eBay
And you Market
I will if you're willing to not tell anybody what the actual cost is
I will mark it as the actual cost on your eBay thing and you will not have to pay the
The that particular import fee
But please Market as you because you know you have that problem
I don't think that's it it looks like the problem might be somewhere else
Where else could it be though
The new one
Heck I don't even know if it's is wrong or right I mean it looks pretty good
It looks better
Yeah but I'm not
Check out master
Oh yeah wow it is host
So what in the world is going on there
What
Just completely hose
Icy Point jumping all over the place
Whoa
So that was when I did the
Check
Something between the two of those really bad yeah
Okay maybe we do need to actually do some
Who is the what
Who is the person who suggested using it bisects you have any very good references for
For me to try to use get bisect cuz they both sound like the correct thing to do
Animal 1111
Can you
Animal honey if you can just
Pasting a reference cuz I'm willing to try right now
I don't actually know what files changed here and also I'm used to operating in a much higher resolution but
GitHub in
K Mix-Ups Warframe slips
Yes I have definitely noticed that
I'm not really worried about clearing out the JK Mix-Ups right now
I will be later but usually when I'm doing the tests the thing sitting in the middle
Where things broke because I do clearly have code that works much
Better butt
Don't know what's up with this
Yeah that's
I've heard that a lot robbed
Definitely heard that a lot
What do you say
List of the best coders are somewhere on the Spectrum
I can believe that I might be I don't know
That was not even the same what I was growing up but I have very little doubt and if I was throwing up nowadays they would have said that that was the problem
Dumb
Things
Do you need those over there or can you send them to me to keep trying them on
No I just
In the world
What changed in that pipeline between those two
I'm going to do something stupid because I cannot bring the livestream myself live streaming
Oh yeah that was like an intermediate one
You're saying good bad is this literally what you type gets good goodbye text good
And then I get commit and then get bisect bad head
Charles the telling you
But you have to get good
Does best advice I've ever received one of my boxes in my past
Courier jobs
Sun live streaming us live streaming
I don't know why it just
Sounded like a good idea at the time
Okay I'm not
I'm going to call this one good
Let's do that I'm going to learn something new today get 5 sect
Start
Get
Bisect good
Hey
Git bisect
Bad
Head
What did I do wrong
I'm about ready to just not do that and just revert some code but
Do I have to check out Alpine
Checked out bad
What is it
Add I've never
It already is so Good by S start
Attached attached
Here on the Sha
I don't know but I thought that was
Past Maya knowledge of get now
Howdy for is an old thing
What
Firewood SVN guy man I'm so out of my element
Here
Do git bisect reset before you start again
Because you checked out an unlabeled commit
Nope
Wow I'm just terrible at the Opera tonight
Okay start yet
Hey okay
Get B
Bad
I don't have any I don't do I have a family
Commit
Oh great things are broken now
This is why I was afraid of trying to get things now it's Mastercool and origin right
Liked it like completely
Reset it or does it ever get
Oh hahaha it's all falling apart
That is what you have checked out your check out failed
No it's pretty happy to me
Today
Someone said he's Master instead of head
Getmycheck reset menus Master instead of head
Data
Hey get
Hi
Of the head
Get
Check out
Had
Okay
Then
Get bisect
Okay what do I do next let's do Twix plays
Yeah
I will ever do is never open this one again
I will edit it to like the first 10 minutes are always day
Give it to explain
Easier to understand get them to use get
Hubris in a terrible way
So what they're saying is they get it
Whenever I see these things like we are not bisecting I just imagine them being said and Linus Torvalds voice
I just
It's so weird
Do is copy the last commit from GitHub instead of using head
Wow whatever this commit was broke everything
How do I mark this one is I did a thing
If I want to move on I know this is bad I just want to
Say okay what do I do next
See what is it today
Get bicycle skip
Skip
Do I want to say bad or skip skip
Skip from two different people okay
Okay well that once also bad
Todd building again
Duke Lane
Yay the internet Charles how to use get thank-you internet
I'm going to open up a new ticket cuz this has happened a few times before
Do not know why
Sometimes data just stopped flowing from the hmd
Don't know why
Sometimes
The HMV randomly decide
Even when finding the light on Magic
Apparently you using git bisect to on a large codebase is a nightmare
Beloved principal butt
It gets ugly know I'm sending it the power on command I'm sending it that magic thing
But the mattress have to unplug and
Replug
Wait a minute
Waking up.
Define don't know why
Stainsby magic like if I plug it in my run it I doesn't give me any data until I send the magic spell to go turn on
Magic is
Oh what is the magic
Power on command is located here
It's this one
I hope you can read that
I know it's terrible
But this this thing here totally does it saying I copy and pasted it from like a
Wireshark session with the
Somebody I think Meryl was the guy who published that
Yeah then wants to know what the power on command is
No I know I just showed it to him
Then if you want to know it's just Vive underscore magic underscore power underscore on
Okay I'm going to go
Rock Solid
It is just
Like foam
Track track track track track track
Price it now say git bisect
Good
You done got cut
0 revision
So if this kid is good say get my some good I'm going with this is terrible
Yeah if it's bad to terrible
So if I move this around it like randomly like you'll see it go like straight on the diagonals and stuff
I like that it's totally hosed
IPic
The points to finally jump out along the way
Did you make
Yes
I did not make clean that time but I mean not
Great I don't even know how to go back to it
Okay so what do I do how do I tell the difference
So I do get myself Ana
Goodbye
What do I do what do I do I see numbers and hatches and junk that I don't understand
All I see is git bisect bad
Get show
Okay
Oh okay that might be a problem
No
Chilling Yulia the definition
Yeah
So that makes sense why that would be outside of that codes that's all stuff I've already manually made sure was fine
That stuff here is down in the The Watchmen disambiguated stuff
Dino is good so it looks like it's just this thing right here
How do I stop it
Bisect
Cancel
Stop
Rita
Okay
Git checkout head
After after
Yeah
Master head in origin I have no idea what the difference between
At one point I probably could have told you but now I don't remember
I think it's like Master is actually wear the new one is in Heathers was pointing to An Origin is the actual repository where it lives
But I would have a hard time with
Masters the name of the brand so hopefully it should be bad right now
Head is always the Sham checked out
An Origin is GitHub in this case
Masters Branch name head is
Get whatever they think it bisects head it was like I have no idea what you're talking about because
I was still on the Old Branch
I could have been active in like master
Somebody wants to know if they can get the source code for Unity sign
Yes I get home
Yes for the unity sign it is GitHub.com
PN lore updp 6832 2012 i2f
Right here
I think they said in chat
Wait what did we do to USB valve. See
Wait what do you mean
Oh no no no no
No I don't know what any of those b mean in there I just know that you guys puked it out at the headset sometime
If I puke it out of the headset to that might make it do what I want
I puked it out the headset and it made it do what I want most of the time
Oh never mind now I feel like an idiot
Okay so this is broken let's go fix it
I think it's right
Year
That was commenting that out
The same
Why is it read only
What is going on here
Nope still freaking it out
There is mounting the chocolate here
On the dining room kitchen
Yeah you said dining room
Chocolate we're still trying to get rid of all of her Halloween candy
Take anything you want
Nope
You want I should have gone I should have written down the stuff from get by text so I would have been able to go back to it
But I'm guessing it seems like they get bicycle done
The chief religious says he should just write another descendant you later for you know
Ray what's another one
There's enough other problems right now it's not just the disambiguation or something is just what it was
Working the other day too
Although now
You know what I'm going to use the Charles mechanism for finding this which is totally like the subversion awful
Let's just go do that
Survive
Remember what I said about
Poet holtby Catalyst for me to in math
Milkshake
Begley milkshakes right now
Unless there's like stuff in the freezer that I don't know about Brandon
I got to a good of it I'm trying to take a more complex situation just to be able to shed this expense into the more complex
You write an app that makes more sense to me
Basic things like
Usurping the compost thing for my slowly got more complicated
I guess not worry said like there's that whole costume Shake in there
There's a whole frosting shaky ideas to things that are closer to the The Watch
Like if I move it up and down
If I'm closer to it than the Delta angle Delta's appeared much larger cuz that's all we really know is he
Engel Beltre
We don't know position relative to Lighthouse really no angles
I am not speaking a language I am speaking in terms okay
Do you want to talk about this right now
How confident are you that this is
Something to go down
I wanted to finish the complex situation first
Chocolate milkshake
Well
I mean the closest milkshake would be like
7-Eleven sell
Yeah I don't think anything else is open tonight
Crackdonalds probably even
Wawa cookout
Cookout
They don't have cookout in the North
For reference the
Charlottesville or Harrisonburg
Voice
Is he your making a lot of sense.
Mindy is person you're hearing disembodied voices stand over this way
Well if you want to work that true I'm confident that we will still have time to do it cuz we're only up to
Oh gosh what is that workout to what's wrong
Your master is making sense and that you we should continue down whatever path you are speaking
Okay
Okay how about that lets you that that's a good way to start so doctor doctor phrenologist
That phonology hi Mindy
I'm into one of the bases that that I think maybe in correct me if I'm wrong Mindy that you're coming from is the idea that that you
You may not need to know Lighthouse locations
Okay also sugar equals math
Chocolate specifically
Is she going to become a farala just too and we just I don't understand
Degree to be the smartest person in the room so
If we have just discovered now
There's different types of intelligence Charles Sledgehammer to code problem
Until they do what I tell him
Bncollege don't see eye-to-eye at all
Ulysses trying to kill me right now so
You guys have any coffee grounds
Probably not
Apparently
Talk.
Apparently wait you know it's been as a pilot
What what do you call Pilots their special name for them
Chocolate orange
What's it called
Captain Jack's that I like that Captain Jackson
How to make Cracker Jacks
So now we have Captain Jackson and Doctor definitely performing better so
Make sure that I did what I think I did
Has the dr yates will feel better if you call him captain
Call bencaz
Oh I tried pulling a trick in here
Open Xposed
Stop
I really have to I'm going to have to do something in my life to spend more time working on this tub during the week so we can
Keep this a weekend and it not be terrible cuz I feel so bad that we're spending an hour right now
Like
Digging through the Charles mad
When we could be talking about Captain
Captain Jack's
Empanology
I'm finally done with classes for now so now I have time to go through this code and we'll go do it
Do it this week make it happen make it good
So
The whole lot
Captain
Captain Jackson and sinologist
Is having some rain like them together
Oh Captain My Jackson but no but like it's like you know like so-and-so and his sidekick if I don't know which
Yeah
I can still pretend
Maybe it's like what incident command
Paris
Parasuicidal boy and that guy but maybe we can move from the light
Trying to classify a dynamic duo that hold that we don't really like we we interact with
Sparingly
Yeah okay okay we're moving we're moving we're moving
You know there's computers to do the more complex situation
And maybe if we get there you can help me do that but
Can I do this
Are you ready to talk it over with
First ask
Don't know what happened to my codebase
I'll keep working on this so
Who here wants to hear Mindy's
Ideas of how to do this without finding the location of the lighthouses
Go
I mean you're going to get it whether you want it or not. Okay
Here at least that around this way and Willamette
Camera down at you
Now it's time for Lindy's math corner
Significantly simpler than Dave's math time
Make video bigger
I think if we're going to you might want to make the video that I actually shows what
He's doing
Barramundi
Loosen a video of her over top of where the CO2 showing
Basically people want to be able to see her white board more clearly
I mean this is super complex and soul
Okay well hold on let me let me switch it so
Plus I haven't talked about how to tell any of you this so this might be wrong
I will hopefully figure out how to get this all merge together while she's explaining it to
We now have that you are the voice of reason I can hazmats and The Mindy Project
No
I was looking at doing where I want to go to closer
Well hello there we go
Charlton to work
Mark here for this
I don't know
Phrenologist says oh God we're old
Mork & Mindy thing
Walmart antennas go ahead and explain don't worry we'll tell you if you don't understand okay and you guys will handle that
Well I can go try to bug the code right at timer 125
Wentworth with the first time then we'll go back and try to explain it better the second time can you see me can we see the board
Only the board do we want to see you
That looks like I got the light fixed
Okay yeah
OK Google
Nope that's fine
Okay it's all my hypothesis is that you don't need to know where the lighthouses are at
You only need to know like some of the First Data we got was like I think someone stated it was only relative
Positions positions and I was like
Thinking about it and I was like yeah
That's nice of elegant
Actually because that's all you outside with Dinah you really want me and anyway
And so I really hope you're talking so bear with me on this one I might lose my voice
So I'm assuming
That we are using six sensors on the headset
And I realize this headset has points in the xy&z direction
And that's really useful
Minnesota rethinking about a problem you never taken a Physics course you always want to be like all my nose what are absolutely
Don't change that I can rely on
I realize that the headset the distance between all of these sensors
Where you are then
Speaking of distances and translations of the z-axis
We just performed an example of one of those things are a few
Nevermind
Really don't like talking
Okay now everything is in to you including you
I made some marks on it and
Homes are the distances between these sensors so I mark
Three sensors
On Eastside 1A 2A and 3A and I pick
This one specifically because these ones with have a nice elegant like
Right in the middle very obvious very in front and then I picked these two because
Today seems to be in line with these two down here and so I can kind of just
Whatever I do the math it gives me quite a few zeros to work with and zero as a really nice
Gypsum
Then I worked out some actual numbers
For determining the distances between
These and kind of like a generic faky unit because I don't really care how many centimeters or millimeters of these actually
We are the computer probably doesn't know that either so
For each thing is
Yeah but it doesn't matter what you wanted is for the sake of what I'm doing right now
So I assume that these two are basically two units away from each other
Actually sorry I use these two but he took the stickers off and became ambiguous
Using those two sensors
Resume these rtn sway from each other in the
X-axis and they are 0 units from each other in the y-axis and in the Z
Access these two are about halfway in between the slang
Asymmetry and the sensor over here so I kind of assumed this was one unit these are one
Away from each other
And so basically a half unit to the midpoint hacking it to the midpoint and here I assume these were
These words in the same
Why location as these to appear
These two are also one unit away from each other a half unit
From the midpoint hacking
And then there's some z-axis stuff if you're still looking at it head-on
Then in the z-axis there's some difference between there's no difference between the a the one
2A
To b-1b
And there is a difference between the 12
Or the 1A
3A Andy 2A 3A
And bison the same for the other side as well and so then you have some z-axis information as well
Eventually I made some assumptions about how far those were from each other and that's what all of these numbers are down here
That's what all of these numbers are down here
So
So these are the initial positions essentially from each other as I said
This is change in x
The set of ones
They do right here is the change in x
For the son of Wands
This is the change in X for the set of twos
And this is the change in X for the set of threes
Down here
This change in X being like the distance and eventually or don't want to think a distance is time
Sounds kind of weird but
That goes back to what our nuns are constants are it sounds like these
Motors
Emit light
Will do so in a constant frequency so no matter what
I know the frequency is I haven't really been listening half the time
. if you thinking text one full Revolution
Is a little bit too specific
Okay 800,000
I don't even know that
Okay
So
Whatever something sweeps it will always sleep in the same amount of time
Oh so you can use that to your advantage
Explain an hour later since I mean
So then I was like you don't we can even figure out the distance Not Just Between the set of Wands tattoo
The distance between like
1 a.m. tree
Or
181 entryway and then train PA
And all of those are going to the same thing as every other side cuz pretty symmetry
Everything's fine
Delia
Then I wasn't really sure what I was going to need it when it wasn't going to need so I went ahead and did some math and run to find the distance of a segment
In real space
To figure out like hey if I want to find the actual distance in real space between like 1 and 3 a.m.
This little pretty equation up here
Define the distance of a segment so far I don't know if I need it or not I haven't actually gone through and done more complex situation of some of the
Movements but maybe that'll be used later on
But just in case it is there
Do I need to explain the nones more about how I know we're different
Sensors are in a relation to each other that they are absolutely not going to be changing changing that's the most important point is that
This will always be true
If you hold
T1 and T2 constancy 182 always be constant
Respect to the headset constant
With respect to the other sensor so like the space between these two sensors will never change
I'm okay with that nobody else
I said is it essentially proof that relative coordinates are good enough
Yes
That's the only thing
I don't know if that's the only thing I'm really thought explain
I think I understand what you're saying is
Like like as long as we're sure because we are sure we're sure that the Physicians on headset do not change
Relative to each other
If it's sitting still
They're visiting so you things are going to change except for like jittering Aaron all that whatever
You can take that information and be like what does that mean something
And I think what it could possibly be true is that if you see a change in one very specific
That will mean one very specific type of movement
For example if we want translation and if you want to see translation in the ax x axis than Siri
This way
Okay
You can kind of think of the sweep as something that creates the court Cartesian
Coordinate system for you and so assume is sweeping this way
I like this point in space you can mark this basically as like
Tu at 1
As it passes by the next 12-unit to T3
30 equals
1 T equals 2 tbsp excetera 41
And the same thing for 22 as it goes up and down you can still Marquez
Whoever passes by this place is always be 21 22 23 24 25
System for you by doing these
Which I have no idea what kind of
What
Things other than what your wear like that if they've moved in the middle something bad things happen
I don't really know
Oh got ya belly band
Freaks out
That's appropriate for I'm hypothesizing so
Cool
Kind of bad but yeah
You don't pump lighthouses if you do a minute
I've always just stop and read in the whole room calibration
It's like a like a teetering thing they can actually beat hi-yah
But if you knocked about a position you're pretty
What's crew
Doctor virologist says
I have never tried to formulate it without using the base station coordinate system the observation changes with motion
Fly you to solve for the coordinate system so he thinks that this is possible
Okay keep going
Wendy
Okay so what you can do with keeping his mind is that
If you if you want translation along X so
Anthony still and it moves this way
Or this way
Then the time at which then it receives like
But if you move it this way then it's going to it's going to hit a little bit sooner is going to be 12
Did not hit 34
And so to think of this when a protective the headset because Lighthouse isn't actually do anything
The headsets like oh hey I got it
Repercussion comes in handy here so think of it in measures of 44
But are looping through each other so you have like
1234m is this way at all of a sudden
Your measures become kind of like 1234 no hits if you think of it from this perspective iffy
It's a bunch of looping like music measures
By the way Captain Jackson says it's recording you
The most important
If you is a precise time from when this week happens
You have to make constant adjustments internal Ada
Will I keep everything perfectly in line
Absolutely
Yes I think so it's like a stabilizer
I think his comments
A directed Jab
Sorry sorry
And Doctor Gates also says well you end up knowing where the bases are either in
Implicitly
It's some kind of stay for explicitly as blucian that use them directly
Okay
I think that's
Why you really need to okay
Translation want to access x-axis and then translation on the y-axis work the same exact way except like
Instead of the measures going from side to side like you would see it and music measure all the and down
Can awaken some music games
And then if you have movement I want to see access something I noticed whenever we're at the cabin is
Your distances between your known sensors increase and decrease over here
The distance between the two sensors these two sensors new sensors if you back it up
The old seemed to increase in so in terms of time whenever you think of it that way
It will kind of be
Large room
Changes
In
It's so here it will be like
Bam Bam Bam hero be like bam
Damn that's like hyperbole obviously won't slow down that much but
It's an example of what will happen there and if you get it a lot closer than it's going to be like
Bam Bam Bam
And so that's if those hits
Oil change in the X & Y axis
I'm going to stay in a particular way that will have translation along the exercises EXs
There's a few questions so Mandy what you're saying makes sense to me but would
Are you be able to know the absolute coordinate
If you don't know where the lighthouses are
Anyting so I guess I would have to do with more if you were inside of the room
Would it be able to know like where you are in the room or like really if you start here
There is more by the way
Because you know I'm
Can somebody else with a reasonable laptop
Can you lock checked yet
Are you can't pay Mike
You come over here with the laptop cuz you can actually do you chat on it my laptop's like totally
Not
Okay
Hold on
The general idea
Who sings in Grimes to punch a population challenge.
Previously like astronomy might think about
Crayon
Are all the lighthouses are in the lowest anyway
With the movement in X and Y and rotation
Increase the time in history that was going to be where I go next
Oh my gosh
I'm going to keep explaining
You can either end of it you can predictively kind of expected to become a later time so don't need to worry about
Emotions
Charles are you getting this I want one who having a hard time
I'm I know I know that that is kind of cuz I'm probably the one who maybe the one who writes it
Yeah
What I do understand
Is the idea of being able to measure everything with relative motions from where we are which I could probably like back until like
Absolute positions from initial starting position
But
What I don't understand is as you would get closer or farther from a lighthouse
That relationship
Like if you move forward and then left and right versus a few move back and then left and right
Situation surrounding try to get to you after I tried doing the basement
Complex thing
Pecan
El hogar we know that
With invisible space rotation can happen translation can happen and really those are the only
Two things I think we came up with so what I'm trying to do I guess right now is explained
What eats like a profile position
Single position profile
Movements along translation along X Y and Z and rotation along x y and z
And then after we kind of understand those basic six things and maybe we can get to a more complex situation where you are
More like rotating and moving at the same time kind of why I'd be like hey let's have a computer help us try to do to calculations
Because computers are great like that and I'm pretty sure to be probably already built stuff that can do that for us
What is horses conceptualizing as I think these
Base examples are probably what we need to import first
Soda translation along x y and z
Something also point out as far as our nose go is that whenever we are thinking
About this movement and he sleeps while we need to know the information
There is no way for us to blatantly be given the information we have to conclude all the information based off of
Information that were given
And is Cartesian system.
The to sweep sideways and up and down give us
And again I kind of showed that we can get in D by
If all points
Between X and Y
Increase or decrease
If it just acts so that's whenever we get into rotation why does not change but
Increases in all the sudden that kind of signaling signaling rotation
ISO rotation along the x-axis will be like
Kind of answer then you're having like your y-axis is getting smaller
And then larger is fluctuating in the y-axis but not the sea
X-axis and y-axis that we're not giving that information
Stop by the sweeps rotation along the y-axis it will look like this and
And that will be fluctuations in only the X and not the Y
I don't know if you guys cut taxes
If you rotate along this y-axis
Then your space between
Did axe is going to be slowly decreasing as a retainer and why
Full rotation of the z-axis which will be this thing coming here
It will be like this
And so this will be a change in X & Y
In a very very different way than what you're seeing in all EX and why's increase and decrease that's not what's Happening Here
It is a translation along X and Y and
Minnesota defense isn't really changing in between them
However these are cheap ones
Change if you want to change the key to our changing
Actually
What is the score for a single lighthouse
Inverse way to describe it from my point of view that you would be able to ride basically
Function so different changes in particular aspect of
Depose
In
In the lighthouse view like from lighthouses point-of-view even though it doesn't think
Would have particular changes on the
XYZ in 3D space
I guess for me I only see that is really having an impact
With one Lighthouse butt
It still is within the divisors point-of-view or the headsets point-of-view
So like if you say like translate X it's going to you're talking about translating
Ax
And like y&z
But
I guess from my point of view like from
I don't know unless there's got to be a way of Translating that back to
That's interesting so you'd be able to if you would even do it over an area you could then
Make it so you can make transformation
From like the the hmds local point-of-view so like this in this
Become like where those go in 3D space cuz if the end of the day we do need to know
Like with respect to the room where the headset is so we can render it from that point of view
But
I don't know why I got to think about that more cuz that would
More than a specific solution
I don't know why I still have to turn to this more for me at least I don't know
I don't know what sponge sponge man is saying
Not calculus linear algebra going to make do calculator
Calculus
.
But
I don't think that you want to be integrating differences over time you'll never be able to handle the error Accu
Malaysia
So he saying is as you move like up and around and all of that
You're going to like drift overtime and you're not going to be in the absolute space of the the area
But now the thing that I wonder if a hybrid approach would work
Where
You kind of getting some sort of ground crew
Complexity
But we're really trying to do like 10 different things that anytime the same time TCL 987
We are we basically all have ADHD the terrible project
Umpd HGTV doing
I don't actually have been says you are correct as far as there's a function that tells you
Changes in Lighthouse measurements will imply changes impose
But it's a function of the current pose
At most abstract lighthouse
Oh yeah except your question so been do you do strictly mean in relative post position or in some sense
Absolutely
My biggest question are all of these differences based on the potential initial initial position or all
All of them based on the position it just came from
Okay so all of these are building up off of each other so like
Position with zero data is all of this base stuff
And then you figure out position to buy this change but then all of a sudden
New
Information
I like your pose
Yeah I'm blending 0 12 + 12 + 3
Your third position
Is going to be this but it's going to know that it's this based on this position
Not disposition
Right so he's teeth concerned that any error that you get from each one of those steps will accumulate
I mean I definitely felt like I even saw the community when I saw Adam playing cuz I noticed that he's fully like drift
Playing
Have arrows and you like rotate throughout the tower
You're not moving from the tower not moving around the tower and then you just like
Basically sniping these balloons and like these nights or something I noticed about him playing the game he's fully migrated
Yeah that was from the lab
I guess the big thing though is that
With the lighthouses the magic is that they do know
With absolute terms
Where you are too I don't know what the actual number is I guess it's probably like
Down to about a centimeter probably or better
Sorry I said the lighthouses no I mean the computer knows where you are in some kind
I don't even know this and knowing exactly the space in between
Sensor 1 Sensor 2
But I'm saying
What do you mean
So
Eat soy
How is this related to how are these two ideas really okay when you have this based on this based on this base
Based on this based on their on their way
Not air will accumulate over time
But what I'm saying is that you can
The it is possible at least that's what valve is
I think doing
To determine clearly with some effort after a couple samples
I'm like if you just pick up
The Watchmen controller turn it on
It will know where you are
Eventually or where it is eventually
So there is clearly some way to get started though that's an interesting this really has an interesting point because
Pending on the way this works I don't know what maybe
I can tell us would be
Better than the naive approach that I was doing or not
Different far as getting just checking up to when I understand
The first thing I hear that's different that's very large is that you're actually using units of like centimeters or meters or something
Don't leave it that what you have to do in order to add that what I'm talking about
Two units away from each other it just you know that they're supposed to be
A certain amount of Click of time which Associates to like
How much is that like
Half a foot 6 inches or something
And so if it's 6 inches away and it's a certain position in space
Maybe between the two lighthouses then you
You know that it should hits like
5 Ms apart I have no idea what the actual timing supposed to be
You are correct you can calculate the absolute Z
Basically from the lighthouse
From sensors 2A and 2B
And it will not accumulate are overtime
Because
The depth to the lighthouse with those two
Pointed out that makes sense to me because
So that'll give you some level of ground truth because if I have an angle that's exactly that
Because if I do it like this I'm like okay now I know that the
Just part of my hand is this far from it but then like say it's actually to skew then we'll now it's like
. so it's ambiguous could be anywhere along
Was it better like no he does not
He is not a valve
Because you know that that was actually the biggest reason I thought that we didn't need
The actual distance in Lexington or whatever to the lighthouse because you had that issue if what if you initialize it
Our listeners would be like our lighthouses pointing up can you see me so is playing up there
But this isn't even straight on
So you don't have what's the triangle whenever it's two equal sides and one up
Please
So you needn't have an isosceles triangular if you got that actual distance in like
There's only one particular case maybe two facing the other direction to the lighthouse to particular exact
K12
Essentially wear your exactly head on to the lighthouse
You'll be able to figure out the death
But you have to be like
I think you can use more information about
So like if you know
That that like this latest sorry this photo died here the so did I just hear this phone did I hear this
And you know that that particular thing then if you watch all of them at least so what I'm trying to do
Do with my lighthouse thing I think that's what I'm doing I think that's why I'm able to tell depth well but not perspective
But it still works
From this point of view over here
Like from from right here
That has a different configuration
Like what that looks like
Then it does straight on it's not just put like $3 be further or closer it's that it's a completely different configurations
See you can kind of
Tell the difference
Yeah I know sorry that the other thing was that I Mindy's correct the scale is defined by the constellation geometry
The base emissions are
Angular fractions of time
And by the way that was before ologist and you can definitely get this time
Yeah I like maybe I could keep Matthew and get this until I still don't understand why you need like an absolute distance
I think the absolute so when Adam was playing in the game I would be surprised if it was drifting I think he was just kind of War.
Around or walking around or something
Cuz I think about like a like a space pirate trainer
We're like
In addition when you walk towards the wall it will draw the wall in front of you
Like the physical wall will be drawn in the VR display when you get close to the virtual wall
But so it still has to know in absolute terms with respect to say the wall
Where Were You Are
Otherwise how does it know how far close to Milwaukie or
To the wall you are because you drew the wall with your sensors and it marks
And if you go back to this thingy you have this static Cartesian system and so you basically mark
Hey I know my room is
Like
Here here here here here here here here here here here here here here here here
And so you have a picture in this
System
About where your room is
And then everything exist without room and if all of a sudden
Your sensors noticed that you're trying to like approach
This point over here it knows that you're not supposed to be at
Tu
Chowan equals 22 equals 4
Right I guess though like how does it know
Start in the middle
I'm sorry that I'm not
In the middle
And then you're like making motions overtime
Like like over that way
Draw the wall or walking around
I can try pretty good
But it's some point I have to know
On that like okay I'm getting cuz like I already drew it within the same frame but I do have to know that I am getting close to the
Right so then is just like oh we recognize that your team 7
She want equals 72 equals
That is
And so we know that that's getting here so we're going to go ahead and run to the wall whenever you're at like this
Slightly
Inside the wall point
But that still relies on like if this starts drifting over time like that then 10 minutes in the middle
And like these are start accumulating as I walk around
I still need to know and like I would imagine they're going to accumulate on like at least several inches below
Those were saying sometimes I do there is definitely drifting sometimes they're saying it's actually not fresh and so we need to stick
The real system doesn't have craft store
I'm saying the way that the real system is implemented
If there is small errors from whatever frame to frame it does not incur long-term
Dr. fauci says
God dammit where's my clipboard
Oh no is he going to do another passive Twitter diagrammer
What is the clipboard mean what behavior is coming back that was the one where we got our first hint
For like you know like they do this thing with the lights and they will tell you how to
How to do what you're after
That's why I
And the system will show you why you're wrong
Okay
I don't know
Present my base hypotheses with the simplest situations
And then you can chew on that
Visit interesting places
This does make
So one of the things dr. Yates wanted me to do was to look at the
To look at it with the ways we did in the cabin with the one
Lighthouse pointed at the camera right
Not helpful for me for thinking of this
Different I don't know if anything I'm going to take offline to
Thoroughly
Thanks bro
But like I feel like there's a lot of value in thinking about it this way cuz it does give you Deltas between the things very accurately
I don't know
I guess I just don't know if it's
Getting absolute position I feel like it's
Better
I know for me it's just it's so easy to be able to draw a line out from the the lighthouse if I know it lighthouses but I don't know what
I don't know
Is Chat thing anything else
Should I go I don't know people are saying we need a great job
Mothers
Some general questions possible Run the official room setup without two controllers come in late trying to understand
What's going on pattern
Sorry that this that we will be making the stream available later
Right now I am trying to go against title of the stream and I'm trying to say that we don't need to know where the lighthouses are
Intitle Loosely exactly like okra and a bunch of stuff is busted we need to fix it
Let's collect some data and fix them
Reminder fix megabox
Metro
Okay
Does anybody in chat currently have any data that they would like collected if that would make it really easy
You guys actually have something you want done or you want day 24 or something like that
I can totally do that is anybody in chat right now who's actively working on with these problems on their own and
Wish that they had access to some more data
Top Golf
What's going on
Can't even
Or anybody nobody in chat no data
Nothing so far
How to test put a headset at one end of a measuring stick it in the other
Absolute chords to know where things are relative to each other
Measuring stick
Organic sounds like
Try to correlate that data to an absolute measurement so yeah they're trying to figure out if the data is in like a kind
Standard unit that we would
Be able to
Figure out like using a measuring stick
Looks like
Tom
So what would you like Paul what what kind of data would you want me to take cuz I can easily take
Like really looks like we got the headset to coming back to
I can take the headset data and it will give you the the relative angles from a specific lighthouses point of view
A different positions is that that would you like Paul
TCL 98 7987 says can you get the absolute coordinates
I walked by recording a walk around the room in the official room setup
I don't know
Collect this stand in the middle of room
Richard 360-degrees on-the-spot
Question about that rotation wines you cuz if we put the headset on and then we rotate that will require it being like
Butternut Circle or do you just want to like sit here and then along like this particular
Sensor rotate along or just like take the entire like
Here
Okay when I say absolute
Removing the
Stopping real quick whiteboard
Whatever this is
Horribly bad
I'm going to move your math
The chat is saying more rather than absolute coordinates it looking like coordinates in the real world
Okay okay so here's what I was trying to
This off
Coordinates without attached
Alexa.
Pretty Jank for you I am the king of Jank
Yeah
After I still didn't see the backside of the units
Okay so what I'm trying to say when I say absolute terms I mean
I will just decide for this particular room
Like right now
What I'm going to do is I'm going to set up
I think you have a particular space in this room that you reference as 00 and the Cartesian coordinate system
This is a coordinate frame
This is
One Charles by one Charles by one Charles by 1 Charles
And you can see I can pick it up when I can move around
Imaginary light right here
You're moving your entire cortesian
Okay I am right now but but but but
Now I'm not now
Now I'm so right now
I can I can say pretend that I have a wall that starts right over there goes there there there there
Uni Nashua
I have a pretend wall to
Okay you drew it with your
Once Okay so we've already set up the wall
Yes okay
Okay
So now
I want to render it for the person
Yes and
Play Shawty Imagining the spaces unity3d
Yes
So in order to I have to have a camera in the in the Sea Bright
Let me know everything
Well
Can't see anything unless there's a camera
But is there a camera or are there multiple cameras
There are two cameras on One camera assembly
There two cameras one for each eye
Okay so that's
And then the idea would be that in order to display the wall
From my perspective you're saying that you could
And you kind of start with like saying that okay to head is when we start we're starting a 2000
And we have incremental updates as we move along but move us around in this coordinate frame start with the
Is it right here
And we can golfer the transforms for that
I just worry that overtime
Like
That wall that I'm drawing in front of me which will track perfectly to begin with Hillcrest start to drift over that way so
Or some way
And so I guess that's where I'm coming from
The value that I think that
What flight variable piece of technology pieces Mass where it where are you worried about that dripped out
Oh what you mean the cause of it
Yes
Okay
So whenever those things to say
Right now your photodiode is right here actually that way and sometimes
That way it's really over there a little bit little bit or not
Perfect
They've stabilized to ridiculous amounts of sounds like
1 something arcseconds like
I don't remember what it is
Itty bitty idiot Nvidia now
But you get that update 60 times a second
And
So for every single time say it's like okay well it was
A little bit that way that way
I just had a question about what is the are crashing look like for fun
What do you mean
Sounds like it has some crazy are correction algorithms happy on top of the other things that are already happening so I don't what it is
That's why they're so important
Yeah but why aren't
They're talking about a diagram that got those little earlier up here let me look this
I'm sorry
Have a horrible in Spanish why you asked
Where does the air come from or something like that
That's why that's so important because they're constantly
Tracking for that dress even constantly maybe like once every
50 seconds or once every like
360 Cycles or something
I think that they're doing corrections but I don't think that they're going to be able to get the air down
Do like the over several minutes the integrated like every single time
Keep track of the original position
How they do that
Just remember one thing
Pretend that the method down there
Okay well what have you started
So it was that right here
And then we figure out where the cameras are and then we move around so then the headset to find the coordinate frame but what
I'm thinking right now is weed stupid heads at right there
And then
As we move it
El between each other relatives to the okay if we had a single lighthouse
What I was imagining was
If we had if we had started with the right here but then now it's over here
So now we have a Delta before change between this to this and this and this today
So from there to here now we can define a relative
Rotation
Catch
All of that stuff
Yes yes
Okay
So now
We can then get this an absolute Court
If I did find this right here is 000
And now it's here
Now it's actually 001
Is that what absolute is for you that's absolute for me
That is also relative right now
My entire world
Revolves around this coordinate frame that I made several years ago
So
Like to me this is absolutely 001
But not necessarily
001 m
In this particular case where I am holding it this is 001m
This is
And you care about it being one m
And you know that it's 1 M because
Because if I'm going to present it from this point to be right here
It would look different than this point to be right here how do you know that it's a m decks
One thing I would need to know the right place in the unity 3D environment
Do we want to
You want to move on I don't know I think we're kind of did the
Contemporary dance
Is that okay okay
John Q U
That picture at me or something
Show diagram
I mean I don't know I just know that it's kind of
Don't know I've never managed this before I'm not a professional
Resend I can click on it
Oh my God people are saying so much stuff
Probably you're getting overwhelmed you need to like
Taken what we can take on
Yeah we might want to end the live stream soon
Let me mention wanting to actually get data though
If you can
Can just mention back in the chat again what day do you like and then we can try to
At least do something we said we would do this live stream
Like tasks essentially right
Oh yeah
Oh yeah that's a good point if you guys want something to Dad at ask for it and I'll go do it in fact we don't have to wait for the livestream for me to do
Anytime
Okay so I have open here wow
I have open here images
Well hold on let me go
Resize the camera again
I need to process this
By the way I think I have an answer for the meter question but I was waiting
Which was
Oh you mean later
I mean either way I can do it now or later
Okay so I have brought up this diagram who made the diagram
Let me find it
Take a picture first
They roll
Oh okay
Negril are Nightcrawler I don't know how to pronounce your name is the one who's responsible for documenting
The great volume of information that we know in the community about the
About the vibe
So that diagram that's up on the screen they're Night Raw I don't know what I'm looking at
It looks like a chart of the headset the two points on it that you're viewing from
Do you think you understand you should probably go sit in my chair and pipe up
Lonely sort of shore
Maybe neither all can start using some more words okay hold on
The original context it was posted if I understand that correctly than they want to solve the inscribed angle theorem in 3D space
The lighthouse
Like this but in 3D so this is a 2d
Example of what he is discussing
Okay
Nairobi Jake
BK Tuesday
The inscribed angle says that if I know the angle between two points in their distance I can find the circle
With the two points in the Observer sit on
That was my state point
Forget about the PNC
Forget about CNG
The trailer Hidden they exist they're just not visible
He has Paul Martin says I would like you to put the HDMI location and Reapers that
Repositioning the status of the way for instance one
1 / yard
Paul do I need to just start it at our magical coordinate frame and then move it up one meter like I was suggesting and pointing at a
Pacific camera
Do we have a new person
We have a tape measure
I wish we had a meter stick though but we're in America
Staples baby in order
Not now we will try to take us off and Packer says I'd like to hear the answer
You mean termini's M question I believe so
If anybody else in chat has any good explanation as to why
The absolute Physicians matter that would be really good because I don't know how to explain my understanding of
My opinion is that I've been through
Moderating chat I haven't been following walkthrough disgusting
A little tired and
I feel like
There are better head to the task than mine but I'm sorry
Paul says that Mindy the reason we want to M because he wants position I we want to position in real space
I also tried to talk to OK Google
Oh wait
What was Mindy's answer to the m question
Okay she is reading up on the Whiteboard
Okay tell you what are you guys okay with us just trying to
Do another live stream sooner than later and just ending the soon
I don't know I don't know what what is what is everybody's feelings I can just keep doing this indefinitely
Cuz next weekend
And then I have something planned for the weekend after and then
I know
That's why I'm irritated
But I know it's going to be at least three days after magfest before I'm coherent again
The entire weekend awake and heavily drunk
Figure out how to explain that last bit there are because I was just like
Distracted and tired
That looks like most people are fine with us and they can do another one
If you can
Mini quickly write off
Your explanation says people can see it then we'll just call it a
After that
So am I whiteboarding in front of the internet now
Yes you can wait for it off to the side or in front of the internet if you want I guess no not at all
Let me think for a second cuz I'm of the food sometimes just me staring off into space
Have a picture
Laptop and just plug in SD card
SD cards
Okay do you have do you have the thing or not
Everything
The the thing that you do not have a reader
Okay
Play Paul's test start at 1 position
Sorry for you
Making terrible jokes well Paul remember I was not the first person to do this
And on top of that my role was definitely I guess as far as anybody from
Give him the biggest props because the Spanx if it wasn't for his work
Early on then nobody would have gotten anywhere I would just looked at it been like well nobody knows anything not going to do it
Cuz I'm willing to work I just you know I'm not willing to be the first
I'm polite just updated your thing anybody else have anything
Anything else that we need to focus on now
Think that's why I don't think there's that much
What is the total length of the LifeStream
Cuz I don't even have a Time
So we can totally consider should we could probably cut it now and then we'll see
Where we can get after it doesn't make sense we will do another brief video
I mean I guess what we really need
This point is like a chat room or something I will say this chord chord
Scored for us pretty much the same thing
No voice chat
Images in all it's pretty much the same
I know you just how can you give an estimate of the next Vice gris-gris dream before cut
What do you mean by an estimate of the next live stream
The next one be like oh that's really rough with the problem is next the next week is
Bakery preparation for magfest and then magfest is the weekend after this coming one and is Monday night
Shmoocon which I think she's involved with so it's there's just no way
I don't have the data plan for in my work, Oregon
Okay there's enough people here who are excited for the prospect of training at mag.
Sounds like we're going to stream two weeks from tonight
Get a space in the living room cut out for us to use the Vive
Okay we can we we will try to stream live from magfest two weeks from tonight
I may be drunk
Just a heads up and if anybody else like you guys can make it out to magfest that would be
Super cool to meet up with some of you guys
Probably find out if they're at Mike that I'm pretty sure they're going to go find us I hope you
Greenland room like
Comeuppance
Man I man please enjoy magfest but dreams are Pleasant
Magfest will have a blast
End up going on tour somewhere else to do it may not stick just to the Vive at that point
We may end up switching to streaming from a phone and just walking
Around
No hate Mindy this is coming at you might find useful the
Alphabet just posted this year
Alphabet
Play Packer I could not see the face I had no idea I thought
Sorry I'm I thought there was going to be like
Google
The circle is that I've
The four dots are the sensors that are tracked these sensors have known distances from each other yes
That's the beginning of my talk yes this is simply straight on you yep sensors are farther apart
I didn't draw pictures pictures this is exactly what's happening
And this Vive is the same distance but since the Thompsons are closer they do know the vibe is looking up
Yasso rotation
Pictures again
Pictures
Rob bumpers also makes me good suggestion to post the Discord won't stop indicate help
Okay so you guys are up for Discord and on the issues and all
And it does sound like it makes sense of parallel paths I would be totally up for something it says not determined look
Locations of lighthouses
Provided I mean I care a great deal about I think I care about absolute positions
We will have to stay
Okay yes
How long will it take we could probably just leave this created it right now
Okay can you also do you mind I think you can just do a push pull request on GitHub and then it'll just
I can just accept that
Supposed to Lincoln here first then do a pull request
Okay
3 hours now
It is 3 right
Well yes we definitely been screaming for more than two
And now we're going to be taking this offline momentarily but I will have the
Nothing at it and you guys can can hop into the Discord
There's already a bunch of people internal Discord
Okay
Sweat.
7 people other than myself were already in here
But basically the goal of the Discord is on the side of different channels for different topics
Keep discussion
Centered around a specific Topic in each area
Oh my gosh it is Christmas Eve
Yes it is
Goodnight Paul
Actually yeah I really need to get out of here soon K supposed to go somewhere at like 9 in the morning and this could suck
Meeting girlfriend's family tomorrow
Supposed to meet my aunt in the morning
Oh my God people are already home I got a lot of people here
What's your what's your name in the chat I know your name but I don't know anything beyond that
I'm Ellis
Movies Horizons that is
Oh crap
Sorry I can't hear you if you're in the voice chat on here I just haven't set up voice chat on here so it was on The Voice
You're really helpful when we were doing the Bendy coating thing that was really good
Okay thank you everybody for coming out it was really great
Hanging out
I know you didn't get anything done
I'm hoping that over the next two weeks
But we'll have to see what it all
Call happens