Everybody thanks for coming out to the 6th htc-vive live survive live stream
We're still not calling them five streams B's until we're broadcasting from the headset right here it's
Not going to be so this one well I don't know
First torso there been a lot of prep work be done done before each one of the lifestreams this one
Getting to that again because three and four were really rough cuz there was basically no prepped
Time between the the like previous live stream in the current 12 this time we actually had
A little bit time to go back and think with things and get that like
Squared away I guess the first thing we should really cover is some of those things that have been fixed
Since last time so first of all the distant biggie waiter the the
The process by which these pulses of light are turned into angles
Was absolutely terrible and It produced some really bad grass
Really awful distributions of where the angle was and we were trying to average it and
I mean it is no wonder we weren't able to resolve the position in the lighthouse
Better thankfully I've completely forgotten basically everybody's name who's done this
Do you want to go hop in the person who suggested that I was thinking off the wrong tip the wrong
Flash
Then we can start everything off the wrong flash that it was causing this problem
Where it would be like kind of wandering and I wouldn't be able to get very good very good
So I have up here in the Stream a little picture of how
Brought it was and is a bunch of them and I think this was the bad one no that was those good
Maybe oh here it is okay so this picture
Right here is of just how bad the data was when the data was going well
Around the center which means that from sweep to Suite to Suite to Suite
Many times it was producing very very similar results saying he had right here
But because this was not being done correctly
You can see the blue thing down here of it just being an awful distribution meeting sometimes as getting a sweep and say
Over there and was wondering all around and it was just
Producing terrible terrible data so thankfully I guess Metalhead that figured out pretty
Well and then remember who was it figured it out
But somebody pointed out that like no that's absolutely wrong you know
Guess I just ignored them or something and then the data ended up getting a lot
Lot better you can actually see the basically the blue spiked was the only thing there
Oh okay yeah so this date up here this was for a
Single Center in this was a single sensor from one Lighthouse and then the other Lighthouse and it turns out that the stinking was
Wrong on one of the lighthouses in right on the other and that's why one of the lighthouses has spectacular data in the other one
Has awful data and then I think here
You can see I did it for all of the lighthouses all together and even though there's a whole lot of things here that look wide
It's just the way that the graph is done but you can see it's very very tightly coupled around that center part
Now there is an interesting effect that's going on though and that's the date has not actually Center
Has this funny sort of like that like not it's not like this
It's where everything would be like oh we just kind of kilter to one side
I'm not exactly sure what we should be taking to be the actual point where there should be the peak
Or the average or something
A pretty big open question I'm not quite sure how to find the the best
The solution for that another major
Milestone that we were able to hit was that the if I can find that
Troll app how do I search this
0x Fe now
It's not doing it oh wait here it is so one of the other
Problems with that if you wash them the previous live stream and I'm sure a lot of other people had this whoever was using this
Randomly the HTC Vive will just stop giving live survive data like you plug it in you turn on
It was a hundred percent my fault because I was looking at a specific thing and expecting it to be 0xff
But it wasn't randomly some of the time and tsunamis accepting all the data says like
Good I got like data okay cool come on through that works just fine now
Don't go away go away search results so
Has clothes that I hide this maybe
So I hide there we go so
Any rate there was another problem yet and I don't think we've totally found it exactly but
Coming back from the Watchman was producing a funny distribution like this one and that's not
Not been fully resolved I think famosi resolved on just by what do we do
Do is I'm here and I'm going to just ignore that I got all that data so weird
Going to need to find some way of improving the disambiguation her is far as figure out a quail that data just get rid of it
Invite your rid of it I mean figure out why it's there and integrated into the correct speak
So the best are one of the other big point
Is that no longer is the data traveling straight from this with the raw X into any toy
Tools to find a position to the lighthouses rather there's now an intermediate step there is
Data processor so to speak
Survive in here
Under Tools there is a process Rock app and with
What this does is it takes the the data a CSV file
Attach that whatever let's just use this one so I'm going to go take the data recorder
New Roc hat. PSV.
Okay so now it's capturing some data for this 5 right here
Do that
I'm not in the picture
So what this is doing is capturing
Data for this vibrate here I'm not going to touch it while capturing the data and it's going to be about 2
Faucet cannot get rid of
Timeouts fine
Yeah you know what now
This data is coming on in
And I'm going to stop at now and then I can go use process to Rob points and I can
Go take that data at New Roc half. SSV and it produces
What it thinks is the estimate of where everything is TimeWise
And it also produces histograms
Histograms So based on the state of right here what I have is a bus
Bunch of different outputs and so what this is Don isn't taking the raw file
And so at least look at what it's actually doing
Call this new rock app. SSV so
Run a tool here and we're on data recorder which is part of life survive
It produces this right here which is just a listing of all of the lighting effects so the egg
Al White House with the X sweet and this is the hmd and it's HMDI
ID number 11 and this was the sweep time that the event happened at and that's the length of the pulse
Now this is this is great if you want to do something in real-time but it's absolutely terrible if you're trying to do something that needs
A lot of accuracy over a longer time so this in-between tools the process
Roccat takes that and goes and create stew
Newrock half. CSV
So in here what this does is it takes all of this data all of these
Thousands and thousands of lines here
The weather now 126,000
126000 sweeps and it condenses it down into this right here
Which is a much more concise file but this says is on the head-mounted display for
The lighthouse L with sweep X on sensor zero of the hmd
It had 1689 hit which Med from that Lighthouse over
Are they are coming to whichever one is sensor number 0 on here it swept
101 689 1689 X and the average
Which time in sweet this number right here which is actually the angle from the center of the lighthouse being
200000 that's the average offset so that's almost straight in front of it
And then in the y-axis so be like right in the middle if it's in the middle of a little bit
Back that way and then the next one for the for the wife or the El Lighthouse which is over there
Is 174000 that's a little bit back
Just look at the Lighthouse real quick see if that makes yes that actually does
Backwards cuz the lighthouses mounted sideways but whatever
And then the same thing the same. Was also visible from the right Lighthouse which is up there
And 168 X it was able to read that and had that angle off
Which it is a pretty sharp angle to that Lighthouse so that would explain why it was
Who's able to hit the Hawaii sweet but not the ex week for that say rate this is the average
Angle this is the average length of the pulse which length of the pulse is a function of
You're coming straight on like so this is the sensor on the HTC Vive thing and this
If you're going straight on and distance those two things the altar
What the effective pulse length would be and then these last two are the standard of.
So you can see that right now pretty much all the standard deviations are like in the
30s or 20s low 30s which is so much better than it was before
I mean it was literally thousands of standard deviation before and it was Tara
Terrible data I'm not sure how it worked I'm just not sure how anything at all got anywhere close to working
I'm so no longer if you want to go try to find lighthouses yourself no longer do you have to process this map
ISO file instead all you need to process is this file right here which condenses it down to
At Mount display which lighthouses sweep the ID of the sensor on the BHM
Or the watch and the the average time of the
Which is offset from Center in units of 200,000 and soon I'll be walking through the
Code where I claimed what that means do you like the
False which currently I don't use but you could probably use and that could probably help resolve position better
I would imagine cuz apparently valdin a lot of really tricky things to make sure that that day
Data was like Beauty good in does analog magic stuff in the analog domains I don't really
I want to throw it out and then the standard deviations so you can just read this file and then
Crossett today to however you'd like so I think that this is already immediately useful to probably some people
Give me want to do other projects at the HTC Vive so already you can go take data dump it in here
And then do?? Something with it so from there
What I can do is I can copy nurock app
ESPN to find what is it called
Lighthouse find it's going to Lighthouse fine now and then go make that tool
Lighthouse find New Roc half.to soopsori need to specify lighthouse
What's called Lighthouse L can't open a good thing
I'm going to show you guys how to actually get that data in so
I'm going to do is go over here I'm going to go look at issue number
8 which is common data for project and inside of here
I can go download Charles all can fix and then in here it has all of us
And everything that you need to operate like my tool and what this does
It has the same ahmd points and they separated
In here what it is is it's the location
Turn on the headset of all of the point the point 0 through 31
Which one of the sensors on the headset and their XYZ positions so uses this
In order to help determine the position and steel Bellator includes hmd normals which it also
Determine position and that is
Hmd normals is the direction that all of these sensors are pointed in
I'm so I guess I should actually how I can tell what that is
If I'm figuring out these things are
Are writing them on the headset itself to file so
Those need to be present in order to operate the the lighthouse feintool right now I'm running
Lighthouse find and it thinks it found the position of the lighthouse
That's not a very good estimate 2.75 - 1
.60 access that is about right actually
The odd part is the White House is kind of cut probably but survival
John Mayer and the lighthouses in the upper right
I hear that looks like that's about right
What is Lighthouse was kind of talked to the side they're so
Measure the distance from the L Lighthouse alive
What is 410
410 cm
Let's see if that works out
Hey don't complain about me screaming at this time of day I started all the others at 9
I need your improvement peso to 71 cm
* 271 + 166 * 166
7 + 281 281
Squirt 424
I was trying to fake that a little bit look like she measured it really is
Oh my God
Look at that right there
420 something mm 220cm 420 something cm
That is absolutely ridiculous to that one worked
Great let's check the other lighthouse
You want to run that together lighthouse
So it says
Anime b274
7050 what the system thinks
Lighthouses so now we're going to use Lighthouse to find to find the our lighthouse
The going to go do it the thing and
What is this workout too so I'm using the position of the lighthouse that's
48 * 48 + 203 * 2/3 + 88 * 88
Court of the whole thing 226
Ironic
Remember what I just said for that distance cuz I don't remember or we can use my card again
Well I got bad news it's should be
Reality
We're going to have to go figure out what's going on there
Is the other one was pretty good getting data again just in case that
Are actually better yet
Try running that data again
More visible and one thing we can also do is
Look at the the are lighthouses different scenery many entries
We do it should be enough to get it going
Not really sure why it's not working well
Let's do it again so you got kind of see how this work for if you want to capture some date
Live survive data recorder run
PSE
Run To Die. The big sorry do do
Now
Got to turn it on turn it on
Just going to record some data now
Just recording some data
Private there
I think that's probably enough data
No I don't just take my back cuz I don't really have
Any reason to I'm pretty flexible
Cool lightning process Rock
Process 2.12
Dumping in Whitehouse find run to.psp go
Run to top his Fields make sure it looks good though yeah that looks pretty good
Alex real bad okay
Find are against Ron to dupps ESV
That looks about right
So RL
Cuz
From the lighthouses are from the things point of view
About that
So
I guess we'll measure that
Think I can get it
Thank you Dave
Around 303 p.m.
Be here what are we get
296 NM
It's okay
Not
Great
Dial
I almost as much as a decimeter
The algorithm is similar to the old algorithm it's a little bit different now though
I don't really know how to convey what those differences are bull step through the way the code
Work shortly
Tom
At any rate
So I've now showing you how to capture data how to process the data and how to
Using mightily by the way is different than
Is there a two other people that have competing tools which I'm kind of hoping you guys can kind of take over for that
Make your tools really good and
And then
Let me have the positions of the lighthouse now this can be confused
Fahey's 10 cm
No I think I use my units right
What are you what are you just talking about there
Yeah I probably would be better so you're saying I calculated this part wrong and if so can you
Just checked my nap on it
297 still off by a little bit it's not not great it's closer but
I measured the distance from the base so that could add about do that actually would that
Without about well I got maybe about two or three centimeters
Hi whatever it's close enough point is we're getting there
So we're getting pretty good resolution on that
It's one by one
I don't understand this is a m
169 cm to 43 cm
100 that's 1 mm 1 cm
Close enough
Calculate that out 1 * 1 + 16 170 * 170
244 x 244 squirt tonight
Can't even tell the difference
Okay I will tell you guys what the deal is with the Orton now
I'm not measuring from the actual origin of the lighthouses
That's that's a decent point I was not measuring from the front I was measuring from the
So you look at that Lighthouse up there
I was measuring from back over here not from like inside the
The main body of the lighthouse so I know that's not I didn't move
Yeah well
What do you mean by forward equipment system but forward isn't meaningless
There's right front end
I mean for worldspace let's define b o z is physically outfit
Yes okay and actually physically right is here
I would say
So
Here is my
5ive
And Z is coming out the front of the Vive which is the direction of googly eyes
Derby
Anyway
The disease coming straight out exercise decide and wise up
Up and down on my camera which ones are plus right now I think A+ why is that way
And then plus tax it whatever it makes the right-handed coordinate system
Thing work
Right self
There's that
Yeah I really should probably calculate euclidean distance but it'll be fine
Okay so what I'm doing to calculate the euclidean distance all that is
It's basically just like the Pythagorean theorem button three dimensions so if you try to fight you have like a try
Mangle
I can't make that with two hand okay I'll go get a whiteboard
So if you have a
That oriented good for you guys to get looks like it this and I have the light
Health dare in the vibe here
Over here
I want to find this Justin Frank here
And the way you do that
I'm writing upside down so I don't even know if this
It's all backwards
You have the X in the Y
And I want to know
What is this
And this is the square root of x squared plus
Y squared plus the squares
Taking the square root of x squared plus y squared
Plus Z squared
And it wasn't that simple
Yeah I know seriously this is actually a piece of shower board you can buy 4 ft by 8 ft pieces of
Shower board from Home Depot for $9 I think
And you can buy dry erase markers from the dry erase erasers
From the
The clothing store
Okay so there is just now I guess I should
Finish talking about the the aspect of this that we improved so I took the data
Prom after fixing all of these input and rent through the 3D visualization tool again
And it resolved perfectly
Perfectly but
Really really well but I was just a really good good thing
The inaccuracy here is
Is in this actor
It is the the this accident so I guess now is probably the best time to explain to you
Oh no Octavia saying something
Okay I definitely time to explain the orientation of everything based on the ancient gear
That better
Okay
Do all of the numbers that I'm dealing with right now to see what I will do I'll make that bigger
Are pretending that this Vibe here is the origin
I am defining it as the origin
There's nothing else no nothing it is
Right now if that's the Vive
Then what I have is I've defined a universe who is Center is actually
Right here in the Bible that's where the hmd points is centered in and
It's the coordinate frame like the direction for X Y and Z is all defined
By-the-bye distill
So now all the sudden if I give you coordinates like these Lighthouse coordinates
Point gyro 1, 1.6 99, 2.4 39
What I'm giving you is I'm giving you these coordinates
In absolute terms
From the hmd itself
Until what I would say is if it stays a d turn here
His 2.4 39-43
9 up
Because that's D coming out of the center and then for the next term
0.010 so it's just a little bit
But this way
From your point of view that way I guess
So I fixed it though it
That's your point of view
Your guy's point of view would be up
And then this way
This way about a centimeter
So very very off a little bit
And then 1.69 go back a long ways so I'm actually
What does verify that let's find out
What the what the actual
Way in which the report says I'm so I can get some directions on the
On these units here so I'm going to put the vibe right here
And I'm going to orient it such that the L Lighthouse over there
Will be in what I think
Is + y + x
Clumsy
It's something I just put this on the floor here
And I'm going to go run some data and we'll see if that resolves to what I think it will
Crab pretzel
Capturing data
Telegram
The vibe is right there and it's oriented such that the L Lighthouse up there is what I believe to be
Positive X+ y positive and I can be wrong but we'll find out
It currently running
That's probably enough data
I'm going to go process the data
And I'm going to go find the L lighthouse on Run 3 and it
He claims that it is positive X+ y positive
Info this is unusual it may be confusing because if I move them around
World babe off the moves around
But
As it stands with the vice sitting right here
That Lighthouse over there is positive 2.59 X which looks about right
Positive positive 1.95
Why which is that correction which is about right
2.188
Whatever up that amount Pinto Define supposition
Of
Oh okay so the vibe here
Define the position of the
Above it all up
Left all that jazz
So hopefully that makes some semblance of sense
Andy was right on the Vive right now actually no we can do let's double-check some of these things
Survive
Directly at Lighthouse L over there
So good as I can get the view
So I can first
Now I forgot the orientation
Thanks that was it
Boss running again
Braun for
Collecting data
Just wondering is D is the volume for everything good for you guys
Doctor up a little bit
I can see that
I am from from the USA we are outside Baltimore
Dad's probably got enough data is processed 14
Okay
Got that
Naproxen Pharrell light out I think this should be
Play Spotify
Good so from this htc-vive point of view
This is what it is
So somebody wants to take a screencap of this right now and post it to
To the
Can take a screencap of this
And post it to the HTC Vive commentator for project
That would be super cool cuz then we would know always what the coordinate frames for the HTC Vive
5r that would be like super helpful so don't everybody rush at 1
And so he says anything the next ten seconds I'm going to go with science to Josh Allen there
What's Josh you wanted to take it
So you guys posted to HTC vivacious
SKU number 8
They just posted in this thread here
Nope looks like Mr was and did Notch. It
You guys can all posted we can select the best one and go from there
That's a really good idea at least for the sake of of this right here
So I'm going to do is put the HTC Vive on
Honest here
And I'm going to
To see that okay
Is that good
Does that make sense
Going to go light up the Evite a little bit more somebody wants to take a screenshot of the
That at work for you guys
Hi
Whatever
Got it. If you wife want you can take a screenshot of this text you mind getting that
D-do you want to talk about what you're doing soon or
Well
I clearly had tons of more stuff.
For plotting the the results a little better
So I can show you what I've got so far I can connect in give me just a second okay I'll wait
Just make sure that I get the right grid size and maybe Inc
Point of the line with 441 of the things that I'm flying
We can wait on that one window
Okay then do you mind if I bring a screen
Bring up your screen out
I'm going to make you a little bit smaller
320 x 240
Go home
So here we wait on Spotify yet kind of out but let me
Greatest little jarring here maybe I should reduce the
Point size for the grid
You know you're you're alive when you can't
When typing
I have a huge delay
Oh does it actually a delay
Okay you are definitely live now though
Rotten
There we go
So here the Centerpoint here supposedly the head-mounted display
Each voxel here is 3 m
A large can you guys can you hear what I'm saying
Do I need to get closer to a microphone give me a second time I know what I'm going to do is make this
On always visible workspace
Are they say yes so you can hear me
Alright so each box will hear is 3 m
And I'm just taking the result from the
My Lighthouse find program and the I believe them
Blue is the left right now which one's the left and which one's the right I forgot already
Is red okay
Left lighthouse in the blue point is the right Lighthouse and the Green is right in the origin
And I am supposedly plotting both the position and the orientation of a lighthouse
But I want to make sure the orientation is right so
That's what I'm working on right now and I guess
Yeah I'm just working on that that first I want to get to the common filters
Stop pretty soon but the next thing I'm going to do is
Is add some lines to the head-mounted display.
Actors
Add the bearing angles to this visualization to make sure that the bear
Angles for both the left and the right makes sense so that's that's the next thing to try to do
So I'll be working on that next half hour or so
So I guess we should pop back to my code now
Red
Right to read eat to remember
Hard slaps a plan together small demon that reads all the 5-day to make successful Networks
With you
Both can read it live
I wouldn't do that hard actually it's an interesting idea
The website is in the description it says to github.com
Seattle or slash live survive
Protecting interesting idea maybe we could do something so
We have the lighthouse data pretty good we could potentially even expose the
Over the Internet so that when I run the program
I mean I can just actually get this and read the data from it
Suppose that over a pork everybody on the internet if somebody wants to try to play with like netcat
And it'll just give you the data single-stream
Broadcast it out to everybody okay Josh
I'll take a look at that we make a note to do that though cuz I want to do a few other things first, specially since then
Just got here if you're still here stick around for about one minute I want to I want to do something
Who does that look like does that look
Like who I think it looks like I don't know I'm just I'm just thinking that really looks like who I think
It looks like
Did you are
Stevia the same thing
Exactly like a Ono okay I'll pull up the two pictures
Don't even know where to find a good picture of
No not really
Looks like the Quaker Oats guy anyway moving on
Yes I meant Alan anyway
The way in which I process today
And then I'll publish it to the internet the data going real time
Wait that's not photoshopped I'll man you guys are going to
Apparently not Photoshop according to ban I don't know if I believe him
I don't know if I believe him
Anyway moving on
Other people that have been working on the problem at the same time so there's probably
Probably a little bit more other people have different opinions on how this would work
But the first part is when I process the wrong thing
My process to the point that this file right here this is in the tools folder and it part of
The the
Kim Blain bragging Blain brain blanket anyway
Tools process Rock app. Process Rock-a-Bye a process to Poinsett see and those I said earlier that
What takes in the Stream of data and average is it in.
All of the other stuff and throws it out there's a couple of things that I'm actually doing with the data and I think it makes sense
Explain that first so the first one is the
The maxlend time if anywhere larger than that it just gets dropped
I use that to determine the the Peaks and histograms for where and which the data lies
So I go over all the day to begin with and I produce a histogram by putting the ding how
And I find the highest being count and so
What that mean if I have the data right here
And I'm processing it that did not open right
I have a date and I'm processing it
What it does is for each of these Benz
Don't know what's up with that
Well you're here just so that you you see this in case it rings up any bells for you
I did a histogram of the Watchman data and if I don't get rid of the second poop right here
For whatever reason the Watchman I got a really nicely shaped thing like where I think the the app
Actual Watchman is but then I get this weird sort of free Echo that just a
Couple Tik thinking groupings of four texts but just mean it's a very small length of time and get a whole bunch
I thought that was weird
Senator what we could be doing wrong anyway
What I do is
In this code here I develop a histogram and it's to find where the best centroid is
And so for data like this when it develops that histogram what it'll do is it'll keep updating
Each one of these cells until it finds like okay this is the bend that has the most data
With the highest number of points so chances are the the data that centered around this are
Area right here is the right data so I throw out any like outliers
Mom and that makes so we don't have to worry about them and they don't throw off our average
So that's that part of the data right there and then after I threw out all the outliers I then
I actually go sweep over all the thing and I find the app
Average bombs that means now over this little area right here which is a really weird
Confucian I don't know what's up with that go take a look at a different one so I don't get all anxious
Apple butter
With this distribution right here what I do is I find the average in here
I'm not the average of all the points that might not be the best way to do it but since we're splitting these tools out the different tools it's a lot
Easier to kind of
Tweak the algorithm some at any rate
We have a we have that it finds the averages and then I go back over it and I deter
Carmen is standard deviation for both of them and so if we take a look at the
The actual output here
Do under Lighthouse find
For what I have outputted is hmd the camera the sensor
How many points are actually read
And the average of the time in the sweep the average pulse time and the standard deviation
And so that's how we get this data from the huge list of streaming date
Once we have that we can then use Lighthouse find d'usse
So Dave and I were actually going over this earlier today so I think I'm going to add some
More comments as I go
Pause the stage one again
Oh there's a lot of things or not or something
Yeah I'm I'm confident I don't have any Reflections well okay there might be one thing I'll get fixed before I do a data stream
Okay
Okay so going over the lighthouse find algorithm
Stage one here is where we find the the vector position of the lighthouse that
Target in that means that I try every possible position of where the lighthouse could be in 3D
And I kind of sweet this huge area and
Check actually a 45 M 5 m in One Direction 5m in the other 555
Only there's I don't check below zero it's not going to worry about that because for me I'm going to do
Define that whenever you calibrate the system you must have the hmd pointing straight up
And then I cycle a 30 times I do this whole sweep area now sometimes a little bit more accurate than
Whole area 30 *
But you know we'll keep going over and over and over it
Now what we do is we split the space into this many
Groups
Tend
Jeff were on the first cycle we want to do a very linear
And what that means is we're going to check through 32
Buy 32 actually 32 * 264 by 64
32 up and down points into the ideas we don't want to get stuck in a local maximum
We want to try to make sure that we avoid that we want to get the best kind of
Canvas of the area that we had
So if it's very linear as we refine our search
We can then use a more
Binary search technique
Tom and there's a really cool thing I never even thought about that as a possibility for much of anything
But then video games there's the technique called relief mapping and relief mapping allows you to
Basically nothing but you can pretend that there's a fly
Flat surface here that will actually have like shapes inside of it
And
Oh my
He'll like it shapes inside of it and you can kind of tear through the surface
And as the surface rotates so to the point inside now Parallax mapping that is a really basic way
Way to do it is really Advanced because it's actually retracing inside of the surface this is actually
Used video games and the ray tracing that's used so from the eye
High-end surface they first do a linear search checking a whole bunch of points and then in order to find
Define at the use of binary search later so I use a very similar technique here
And so now
We searched
Through the
Whole face
And
Staples confused originally these are adjustment
2 best
The
Fast from last frame
Hey ray-tracing you might think it's expensive than cycle time but it's ray-tracing is just trivial and like I'm free
Things like the Vive like I tell you one of the first things I'm going to do once I get this working is it going to go Port some version
No Euclid to it because Ray tracing is so much easier cuz you don't have to supersample or any of the
You have to do with traditional Rider anyway
So what we do is cycle over each one and then forgiven position that we're trying in space
We go run this function run Opti so let's take a look at runoff d right now
Run off to just says pretending have a camera right here where would it have to be pointed to be pointed at the place that
Pointed in real life so that the data we're getting from the lighthouse would lineup
Does the first check to see if it's a valid Viewpoint and this is where the normals come in really important
So the idea is an active I should really do is document that
TSA sensor is pointed away from where the lighthouse
Where
We are testing a possible Lighthouse position
Get data from that lighthouse
Then we know this is not a possible
White House position
Okay so what that means is
Say say where I'm going to say like maybe the lighthouses where my head is right now and maybe
I'm looking at the vibe right there
But in our data set it says that I was able to see a sensor over there
Like all the way on that side of it
Let me instantly know that
I can't possibly be with A Lighthouses because I wouldn't be able to see that
So all we have to do is just take the dot product of the normal
And the vector between the center of the HTC Vive in my face
And if they if a DOT product is -1
Can't be possible so we can immediately throw that out we don't have to do any more complicated algorithm
Whatever we just know that it's not a valid location
Once we do that
We can iterate
Over a refinement of the angles
That constitute
Irv the
That constitutes
Lighthouse
Okay
And so at this here means is I'm going to cycle six times and I'm going to try to find the position of
The lighthouse
And that down a little bit
A little bit anxious about it cuz it's kind of hard to explain
Must be here let me see if I can stop that it's hard to explain that it's hard for
Remember how I did it cuz I'm not that great at math
But see here so if it's a valid hit
We have an angle from the lighthouse pointed outward and so AXA why is in Radium
From the center of the lighthouse so we have
So if I have a lighthouse
Right here
Oh wow that's really clear now
We have a lighthouse right there and it's viewing
Bring out this way
And we're looking at save the rotor for the Y so it's that one right there
We're talking about
It's this angle right here and then what this does
That's measured in radians and so what we
We actually have is
Seda
And that can be done for both the X and the Y but let's just assume roll
We're looking at the X right now of the fleet
So that's how that part works
Never be correct the cross product
Oh okay
Okay so it looks like what I do is I create a vector
Find
How does this work
So it doesn't do any reading out a vector and three face that is that represent from Imagine
Lighthouse 2000 pointed straight up it's creating a tuple in Normal
Is Vector in 3D space that would represent a real that shooting out from it so imagine that the light
Houses pointed straight up
So positive Z is that direction
And now we have an X and A Y is back into the board components to that
So then we can rotate the re-buy that current estimation
And it isn't the current Lighthouse quaternion estimation
I'm actually calculated elsewhere
Initialize to nothing
Whatever
Is it
The point is that it takes that
And
Now it's really confusing what that means is it takes to be the lighthouse
Find the point in actual space that would represent this Ray and then rotate the lighthouse down or
I could be down towards it and then once it's rotated down towards it
Looks like that's the first one is where it rotates it down
Lighthouse playing up
Down at it but it doesn't know this orientation Sonos it needs to be swept here but once a tear it needs
To resolve this a little bit better could be a bug
Text that
Rotate the left and right and then it fight tries to find the best possible
Rotation for the lighthouse from that point of view
And then it goes and refined that little bit more every time for all 32 times until the changes its
And so that happened
One for every possible place we want to try
And like a factory just keeps cutting in closer and closer so
That's going there
Looks like everything still going well
The next thing that we should probably talk about is
Really run task cuz I just print out the results loading the data
So this is a little bit earlier so that he would be able to load the data
It's coming from the process to point file
And invalidating stuff
So what it does
Is it open chmp points which is the positions of all of the points on here
And I think that you guys little bit earlier
But it's just the XYZ location it reads them into H-E-B points buffer
It opens up the normal the normal 10th indeed Point buffer
Remember that normals are used to throw out unused data
And then poop dooba dooba dooba dooba dooba dooba dooba dooba
Down here
Actually load the the process
Data
Okay
Do the format is hmd meaning head mounted display
Elek meaning camera l
Number of point in that 1000 times
And what does it loads that into the buffer but then in order to calculate the angle that little Theta that I told you guys
About the theater right there what it does is it take the the average time
Which is that number that I gave you mine is 200000 divided by 200,000
Times of Full Circle
And so that's how get that angle in radians
And that's what it confused everything with
So this is the full explanation for
Howell I am currently doing the algorithm to find the physician
Please talk briefly about some of the other people's solutions for this sort of thing
Hello what is going on
How people are chatting in their Fair bit
Do some other people had a ideas about how to do it and most them involve
They're here somewhere
I don't even know what that is why I angle vs Pistons
I don't know where to find it
There's another way that people have been trying to solve this and the other way the people been trying to solve it
Buy this kind of triangle theorem and the idea would be that from this
Point right here if you have to point here and here
Erasing stuff first
If I'm if I'm up here
And I'm viewing like that
And there's two points here and here
I would be able to exit 83
I would be able to use the distance between the two point
And these two point
In order to determine the possible locations of death
Which works in two dimensions and you can extrapolated for three dimension
Hi Mike you said hey there's something wrong
I'll keep talking while you tell me if something's wrong
By using these distances you can then resolve the position of
Where the lighthouse could be
And I think their Solutions work really well too and there were simpler than mine so maybe the right
Combination or
I don't currently have any pull request
From from anybody you know offering this is a pothole solution so if you really need to
I can
As you guys wanted earlier it sounds like a pretty good time for me
To make a data server for you guys
Something that will allow you to stream the data
To yourselves
Let's go all the way to the Bottom now
So
What I'm going to do
I don't know what's going on
By the way this is totally how you legitimately do engineering like
Depressing I know
No don't do that that looks hard to copy
At 1
Click click click
You look like a good candidate for me to rip off
Sure why not that was close enough
Poop copy paste
Play 1000 Maverick can be included twice nobody cares it's fine
Remind you that
I'll have a list
I think they're doing a lot of stuff here that's not really needed but I don't really care
Yeah I think there are some people who don't have the
Quaker Oats
I ate it the resemblance
Just there I I just can't not see it once I saw it
I don't really care who you are
Chris I used Linux Mint
So that I can keep my beloved mate which is also known
Home two or three or whatever it is cuz I am really bad at changing like gooey
So Linux Mint is like Ubuntu except with the old the old GUI
I can listen any you guys you can send me whatever you want
Ignore it looks like that'll work
Send thread hero
Remember what standard in his is just one ft is 1
Right
Don't wait
No piping don't wait to Socastee
Don't know you guys are talking
That's really sad
I didn't know that about him that really were sowing your Wild Oats comes from
Yeah I kind of want to just watch you guys as you can act in I think of you a lot
So I'm going to do that
Thank you
Mr. Yates
Chief virologist
Let's use that
Now let's find out how many years I have
Dash I.
Shred
Eita and thread
I capitalized
Try that okay
Stop
Find
Why is that not working
Should be right there what's wrong with that
You know what I don't even care
No weird
Well I didn't work
Anybody seen my problem doing something.
Poopoo poopoo poopoo poopoo
Thredup
Stop
Oops
Call so I should probably actually disconnect people and they get dropped
Okay see if this works
Is crazy crazy idea works
Ono stayed on oops
Ya look at that data flow in
Totally ignoring our response
Okay time for me to go log into my router and open up a port
I am 11 163
How do you use netcat for as many connections as you want I want to make it so goes out to everybody who
And I hate using different passwords for things
Network
Anybody else know where that isn't open wrt
44 words
AutoZone other is 163
What
I've never heard of NC
The off
What that is
Get a chance so
You have the ls Impala type beats
A rotation around the x-axis
Left to right
If x changes
It is affecting what I consider to be the x coordinate so
It would be x-axis with the higher number so that the laser sweeping around the y-axis
Yeah yeah no forward from lighthouse
DX's forward from the Lighthouse Point of View in the lighthouse
Local coordinates to Lighthouse local coordinates klzs forward and then the sweep
Affects the x-axis
Okay
Thanks
What was something's weird
I am also going to make sure there are no
There should be no reflections
That should be fine
Did mess it up
Okay guys Connect into my IP and see what you guys get
This port 5555
Working for me I would like to know if it is working for you
Who you are getting dropped
Maybe I can open up my buffers thumb
I wonder if I'm just overflowing your connections
So the tweet that affect the x coordinate is called LAX
Yep that's the way I did it
That affect x-coordinate relative to the lighthouse
I don't know what's wrong with you Alex
I definitely understand the need to increase the buffer size though so
Does anyone else know the code off the top of their heads for increasing the buffer size
The send buffer size
Oh my gosh I don't want these balls of text I just want some see code
No comeback
Okay everybody connect back in should be fine now
Even the people who have the slower connections
What's your connection so slow that it just straight-up can't keep up
Nobody is reading Dana
Are we go
Whoever you are
Sad
Oh yes
Okay everybody Can I stack in should be fine now
Even people who have the slower connections
What's your connection so slow that it just straight-up can't keep up
My turn on nobody is reading data
Are we go
Whoever
Are you are you sad
They get going again guys can you see it
Think it's good okay
I think it actually might have been the TCP buffers that wrecked it up so I'm going to not put it at 65536
Okay that should widen up things so it should be fine
Just fine
Okay can you guys also connecting get some data looks like a few people are still cannot
Not many though I will turn this off so it reduces
Okay
No I definitely
I noticed I was doing the best I can to try to keep things going
Still dropping pretty quick
Maybe I actually need to go do some actual effort into making this
Workwell
Don't really want to develop a hole
I don't know man I'll just add the server if when you guys went to go fix the server that would be soup
April Fool
He'll either way what I will do is
Add that to the thing
Oh man
How am I going to do this with
Stop showing my password
Hyatt down there enough
Over here
Dragon
Hoping that you guys don't see my password
Another window to always be in the front
Nope nope
I've gotten it's going to go totally just go hide that little bit
Okay
Careful now Charles
Goodgoodgood hahaha
Looks like all was well actually it is about time for an ad
Let me see all the way in the past there
Does anybody else have anything that we shouldn't think we should go into right now or
Is now good time for an ad Dave how much longer you think is going to be till you get something
Okay that won't be that much longer.
Okay I guess I'll leave this up for a bit I'll play an ad and I'll be back in about 2
Two or three minutes
I didn't work
Echo
Actually no we can do is
She can watch Dave code
Planes actually can I can they watch you code is that okay if you want is everything
On your screen okaida broadcast there's there's nothing sensitive on the screen I have any passwords or
Okay in Plainview and what I will do is you guys can watch Dave code
And Dave you can talk to them as you code do I have to
You can
So I made this really cool function that supposed to calculate which way the head now.
Directions are appointed relative to the lighthouse from the values of
Process
Yeah process data. Txt
And I've loaded all the head mount
Data and it looks like they're only really
Who values
That have
That have all of the angles
There's only two indices
Number 9 and number 30
That have an angle for
The both the left and the right
For both X and Y
So that fully defines
A direction from both lighthouses to the point what I'm wondering we can
Verify is whether those two lines intersect right whether both lighthouses
Exactly the same place though
I'm working on and so now that I've written that
I have to call that for those two
Lighthouses and then the next thing I have to do is
Use the orientation of lighthouses which I was plotting before which the orientation looks Plaza
Possible I'm not totally convinced that the way I'm fighting it is right but it look by the way they are
Kind of wackerly there like mounted like that from the wall so like this is why
Why and this is back the next day you were saying was forward though
Yeah but a black sozzi was forward for the lighthouse on on the way I was just playing and Z1
Was forward for both of them why I think Z was forward as in relatively toward the direction
If they had Mountain it was at least reasonably pointed in that way the way I was fly
The thing was that it looks like they're tilted down and on my plot it look like they were tilted
Almost straight forward not down at all which is why I'm wondering whether that might be wrong but
But we'll see
Okay it's possible we also might be using different quaternion definition I can't remember if my 1st July
Value is my w that makes a difference here
00:00 looking
I couldn't see whether I was assuming was the last but if it's the first
Then that's a really easy thing to check
So here's the quaternion right here and it looks like all four of the values are roughly in
In the same reasonable range so it could be any one of them
Let me look up which one is which because that actually makes a difference
You couldn't think that simple
Does anybody else's got no at the hockey is to like go to the beginning of the line on OS X cuz neither of us know what it is
The old xyzw WXYZ problem.
I need to find this pf454 Mac there is no
Home button yeah the whole story behind the Mac is
That I'm teaching a class on programming and some of my students have Windows and some have
So I needed to make sure I had a Windows and Mac so that I
Help install code on all my students computers and
I have a Windows PC but it it's been six years and it's just got all this
Clumsy all these demons and everything running and it doesn't like that I don't like having a virus scanner
I think that's even worse than having a virus so it's just really
Play old and slow so as backwards as it feels I feel like the Mac is is a little bit
More and more productive on the Mac because
It just doesn't bog down yet
But I'm sure it will be
One of these commercial operating systems Linux is better
Effort
Josh wants to know if you're teaching at UMBC no actually I'm teaching
Teaching
A small group of
Mostly like teenagers like to 12 to 15 year olds
I'm teaching them see and I'm also teaching a little bit of object-oriented design and
We have tried to make things fun I mean would we try to have some of the examples with
Opengl
One thing that was really neat
Last class I was trying to teach them about 50 move you out until you get the
Actually I want to do something else anyway real quick though
You can go pull up whenever you want and then once it's out here
One thing I wanted to do in my code
Palm was I wanted to
By the way I said
Function left and function right unless you're in terminal in which case is Ctrl a
Function function
But in the terminal is control at okay yeah thanks remember
So can you put me back on the
I wanted to just do this one thing here
Oh that's not good
What is it that's fine
Hello weird that they buffer out to exactly 10424 chunks
People who are connected by whatever if you can tell me if the data being chucked you as reasonable that be
Super cool
Cuz the fact that they're all 1024 is a little bit suspicious
Okay got it. Now showing your thing
Oh yeah so I was I was teaching teaching the kids about how to load a file and I was like what is the absolute coolest
Nothing you can do to just load a file so they had to make a model loader and
I made things a little bit easier on them because I downloaded this obj model from
I don't remember who the tribute to but I accept
They do have a tribution to the to the creator of the model but I wrote a program that converted
Obj models into
A really simplified format it's just just the
One vertex after another
And the students had to learn how to open the file
Mitzi
And then they had to allocate the array and then they had to make a for Loop to draw every
Triangle you know the code
If you got to learn how to how to read files you have to do something something cool with it
We did that and we did a particle example they had to figure out how to
How to work with large arrays cuz that's what what a particle besides it's instructive but
You're not the same time try to make the all the concept but try to make it fun at the same
That's what I'm doing and I'm not it's not it's not what I do you know primarily
And I'm a software engineer causes a software engineer
But you know what something that you know I enjoy teaching people and it's fun and then if you can help with kids
I think that's that's a good thing song
Going to go real quick back over tomorrow I think something's wrong with
I have too many tabs open or something
Everything is going super slow when I have your screen up notification
Well
Oh who ever that is
Auto
UCM flyback
CR and LF in putty
Jack your back alive
I'm still trying to figure out whether is quaternion
Is one way or the other
It's in Lynn Mass. Each
Cool macro that prints it out but I still have to figure out which way is which
It looks like W2 last one
Because
You plot you print out three
And it's just your 12
And then when you print out 480 123
But if you'd 012 or XYZ
60/12 is just if you're printing out a point ASAP at 4.
Yeah but usually if it's a point that's because people use the ijk
Directions and leave w0
Looking okay so quiet non is 1000
Happy WXYZ
Fix that I don't know I didn't think to check their first don't know what I did was I just checked quat's that none
And then sitting on his 1000
Let me let me fix that and I wonder why I mean the core the orientations weren't perfect
But they weren't that terrible so I'm surprised that it
I got those backwards rotation Zara wacky thing
Nope going back to you now
All right so I am now loading W and then i j k
Can we see what that looks like
Unless I wrote code that has compilers which I did
That has to be fixed before we can see what it looks like
The Discord is more for whenever like you have ideas or you want to work with other people about like
Data or anything like that you can go there I also do virtually all of the announcements for the project like whenever I
I get something new or something news going on or some section the date is working I'll always announce it in Discord
That's just what we used
Look beautiful look at those hello look what is what is what is
What is y4u oh
Oh yeah
There look at that so that's the the lighthouse
You can't put the screen up now I can't physically to laptop
Yeah I kind of rotate it that way
Little bit down so Riley and the wires are pointing out
Yeah the wise are pointing out to the side that's perfect
So went pretty good
At least visualizing that still want to make
Of the range and bearing angles to those two sensors
That are actually observed by both lighthouses
To make sure that both sensors that. Make sure those lines intersect right and what days talking to
About is the center origin is defined the the the HTC Vive headset
But the the Watchmen themselves were also on during that time so they kind of have their own opinion of where they could
And so he's going to try to plot the location right
I wasn't not the Watchmen so I was looking at the
Although I mean the Watchman would be really good but if you look at the head-mounted display these
Did they show up
You can see that what your York you can see in the display what you're doing all the head-mounted displays
From process data and it looks like only two of them had the l x l y
RX and Ry
Only two of the IDS but those two IDs have enough information to draw
Actual line
Range and bearing through that
Are there any Watchmen things that you can do that with
I didn't look at the Watchmen
Let me let me look
Okay well regardless you can still do it for the 80s
And it could be a factor if it works perfectly for the hmd it could just be a factor of like
Calibrating
To the point that would make that look right even if it's not actually wouldn't mind that you were talking about how
The angle of the sensor has to be pointed roughly like
Toward the lighthouse
Yes so that means that there just weren't very many sensors that were pointed enough toward both lighthouses for
Both to be seen if that's possible
That makes sense
But either way at least we have these two points so I want to plot these two lines right
Thing is even if those lines line up perfectly
It might not be that it might not tell you that much because
I may have already like bias the data of where I think the lighthouses is in such a way that would make those line line
Yeah yeah I totally agree that.
The data
Like that that is actually like legitimate data like
That there's no misunderstanding as to what the angles mean yeah where's that they disagree means that there is a misunderstanding
Exactly so I want to make sure that
I want to make sure that there's also not a problem with my code too so
So yeah so yeah I'm calculating the planes intersect the plane
Sorry I'm back on your screen now
I need to call the function that does all of that
Cuz that's exciting
If I can do the live stream thing on my
Phone and then chat there're monitor chat on that
Do I not have YouTube on my phone
Do you want to keep you up or whatever you want to do
What are you up to now
I'm not actually up to anything right now
Your life keep going okay
Yeah
So that's what we're doing here
Is plotting the X and Y
Calculate those directions
And then we're going to put that into a
For Rob for the laugh
Then we have to do the same thing for the right lighthouse
Between maybe it has to do with the quality settings actually seems like
Time for me to go drink with that
Quickly disconnects real quick
Gospel login sorry
And I can see you typing in Bud call CRC
Try moving around now see if it's nice and smooth ER
Looks a little better oh yeah it's definitely
Plug these into the quaternions
By the way I mean right now since I'm kind of freaking out
I was a pretty good time for us to start like actually chat chatting unless my chat
That is grossly out of date or something I just did not catch it
Nope looks like I'm up-to-date with chat
I got my solder paste from digikey
I did it to reasonable price and it's they always ship it in the nice like refrigerated packet
Any other random questions
I forget I mentioned earlier on but tomorrow hopefully at 6 p.m. I'm going to be opening this
Box right here which if you guys do not know K or the people who
Distribute the best multi M ever made and I'm going to attempt to be hacking Wi-Fi into it
Tomorrow so don't know if that's going to work I have some ideas that I think might work but
We'll have to find out live any other random thoughts or questions any
Oh
Okay I guess I'll go into the the you know what that's a good point I'll spend
In a minute I will go and do an explanation of everything and if you're up for doing this
I'll try right now
Oh I didn't too much. So linger
Try it again
Okay come on guys connect on intake a checkout at the
The date and tell me if it's working
Grief
Can you not remember my credentials
Okay I'll take a look at and see everything it's going
Caso Anthony Monet
I tried the socat that's what's running right now
Tell me if the
If the data looks good
Looks like we should probably do recap in a minute
Working but it seems slower but you're not getting random disconnects
Data is slow
Okay so maybe the snow cat thing really isn't working we actually just need to do something smart about it
What
In the world are you saying Chris Van ryn
Okay I guess now's a good time do you want to be live on the screen or do you want me to
Keep it on this thumb well this should be exciting we have these lines and they're going to you down
So there's something wrong
But yeah that is wrong
Is it possible that I could be
- that the - is wrong I think what's going on
Is that I flip X and Y somehow
I think the xsuite has to be the wise sweet and wisely Pasadena TX waived
That's possible because it looks like hold on green is Y and the gray
Has the larger angle it seems like
But yeah there's no reason why that should be
Because we see a larger angle in the plane
In the yz-plane when there should be a larger angle
DxD playing according to get numbers down here well not yeah
Is that true
It should be a larger in the XE plants receive these numbers here Alex is supposedly the XE
And that should be 20 but the XD playing is red blue and I just don't see
Jack is it exactly zero in the exe playing in might be so maybe there
There's something wrong with it should be about zero in the XV plane should be about 0
Not exe playing it says there should be 20 degrees -20 degrees so maybe
X and Y are flipped flipped look at the pound calculator
I'm doing something I think I'll do a recap then
Which by the way my goal is to make this stream only be
A total of 3 hours in like 50 minutes cuz YouTube makes it a complete
And edit them if they go over 4 hours so we won't be doing that
Who will close some of the stuff too
Do cats getting some broken pipe that's probably fine
There's a bunch of stuff oh by the way about the OS no I've never developed my own OS
I did actually create a raw bootable thing called my OS but that was just for
Making it so I could run like raw code on a processor without grub or anyting it was just like x86
Straight up boo'd everything lives in a small space but it does move it into like a high graphics mode and
A couple other things and put it into protected mode and all of that and it was for C+ plus and that was back when I was misguided and I
Legitimate programming language omigosh someday
Everybody is going to grow up and they're going to realize the sea is the only true path it's
Just so sad how long of much of my life I wasted in C plus plus
Anyway probably time to do the recap oh yeah the automatics
Crlf it's it's under Section settings in putty or something like that
Can't remember exactly where and I don't have putty so
Moving on so this project this whole
HTC Vive live survive project it was because
In a hotel room while visiting aiyappa my friend grey cotton show
A Vive and I was like yeah whatever I tried like all the VR
They're all terrible I don't ever want to do VR this is just dombovy our Revolution is like the 3D printing Revolution is going to
Going to go nobody's going to care that that's just what my attitude was as of before Thanksgiving
And then he got out the lighthouses
Any put them on little stands and I asked them what they were and he explained
And I said oh
Never mind about all of my opinions about VR
That was just wrong
The Vive is the future of VR.
And that was when I just
Like realize like this is something different
And
About a half an hour later I was already on my laptop I was downloading all of the libraries forever working with the vibe
And all of the existing ones were so chock-full of ridiculous dependencies Iran
Update on my cell phone plan
And that was the moment I got so frustrated I said I'm going to make my own
And by me I mean all of you guys so live survive this project right here is an effort
Kind of from the ground up in an OS agnostic manner without the use of additional live
Libraries work with the HTC Vive
Now personally I want to do it so that I can actually operate on other Hardware so things where it was steamed
VR system doesn't exactly make sense I'd also like to be able to take this system that were developing here
And be able to do things outside of the steamvr so I can hopefully operate the
The five on my terrible laptop right here it's awful gut integrated Intel graph
It's just depressing
But I think I can get the bike to work on it
Then when I get a project I want to do is I want to try direct ray-tracing inside the vibe using the V actual like
Head Mount like
The warping factors of all of the lenses as the mechanism that used to select the Rays used for reicast
And I really would like to try to Port no Euclid over to the vibe I think that would
A lot of fun
I granted it would be pretty much unusable by anybody because it wouldn't use steam VR and therefore it's kind of a useless
Thing
But
As far as like understanding it in digging in and learning more I think that's a lot of value
Insofar as the whale I've survived could be used in the real world I'd really like to try to expand it out
Outfield have custom sensors and custom system I'd like to be able to have systems that can save
Handheld system that has an actual camera or not a camera an actual display on it to really kind of make
More of an AR VR experience and be able to interact with people inside the VR
There's just a lot of things that don't fit very well into the existing architectures that are being used by a lot of
What is BR things that I really want to
I really want to explore that I really want to try to have some fun with it
And I also really like to bring in the esp8266 and esp32 into this
They do you want to talk about anything or things just going south
Just having a little bit of trouble with angles at the moment so
I'm going to get that squared away
What do you think your your angle so the way I did that the data sets is
From the lighthouses point of view the angle side to side is very small
So like it should be they should be kind of an opposite sides pointed straight towards
The
Bhmd I'm going to go through a few tricks right now
One thing I'm going to do is I'm going to set one of the planes equal to
Equal to the the normal
I'll set the
It should be the most of what we're doing is in the LX it looks like
Which means that
Which one is X
Axes up and down
So what I'm going to do is it I'm going to sit
Hawaii plane equal to the normal and just see why
This thing is coming up weird
I just noticed that Michael I rolled the my C plus plus statement
I will admit I iconically
I see most of that, clay like I do think people try to fit object orientation into way too many places
But I know for small projects I honestly if I need something with a map I honestly just
Nothing wrong with like using C plus plus for things here and there
There's really not that much wrong with even something like python
Things get a little bit problematic for me when you move up to Java because that requires a lot more stuffed actually
To go run the code
But I'm not whatever that's fine
Like they'll even Ronson embedded devices kind of so
But no like I just
Think that she should be strongly considered by most people as far as like
Actually thinking about learning cuz when I did
That opened up a lot
Owosso Dave
Trying to your conversion function for converting from the input into angles
Converting from the input into angles yes you can see that but I found the problem oh nevermind
For whatever reason I didn't set the real component of the lighthouse returnee in
So let me know
Let me add that that should be that shouldn't fix it
And that's I'm only doing the XV cuz I still have that
Oh hello wait what's going on I was weird it's a little bit of food
That's certainly the biggest problem
And then if I change the y&z back
When was
It still might be wrong but that was clearly a problem
I got to slide you a little bit the side so the
Define
Close though really wrong they're pointed below
Could still be
That could still be wrong
But it is showing
That the x-direction is most of the rotation which is right
And it's showing that the y direction is the rest of it
Can I see your function now sure
For converting
Big data in the file tornado
But pie
Call Matt what are you doing oh wait no that's wrong
Why is that wrong 22nd
That's wrong though I think
V Pi * 2 / 200,000
So I think
But that's Pi / 200,000
No it should be pie over sorry pie over
100000 * pi
Yeah that makes it easier for me to think about I think that's right
Nope that's wrong
Let's let's look at your code
Organic a mycotopia code
And if there's a difference
Then one of them must be wrong right
Obviously would be mine
All right and my code is functionally this eau-de-vie
So oh yeah I over
So this would be 400400 oh my gosh
It is not the same I didn't see that / 2
It was all the way on the side of the file and it might have been that my terminal is all scrunched
Copper something and it went all the way to the second line
Oh that's beautiful
What's up with that it's hard to tell so there's a little bit of a difference but they
They're both really good mm
Although Lee that is right hold on can you
Set happening maybe that I don't know that's really hard
Hard to tell it could be that my why rotation is wrong when I see about the route
Is it enough that an error in the y Road
Maybe I have the Y backwards
Flip the wire round
I flip the Y around
Backwards then I guess I would have to
Well people are saying stuff is one rotating in the other direction cause
Are is the clothes clipping plane too far away have it set to a lower number
I have something else now that's
Just real quick so I think C+
Ghostbusters okay and I think the STL is okay but if you think boost is a good idea and almost any kind of
Any non-scientific programming environment I would disagree with
Purpur Deployable Systems I think boost is way over used
And as far as running Ubuntu on Windows
I think that that is crazy and I have tried using it is so confusing and it is hilarious when you asked
Cutie message
It is really sad that that cygwin never really got that far so
A little bit back to the
The rotations rotating indica
David is napping can I see your
Figure this out
Okay so if it would go the other way then we just get rid of one
One of but not both of the
Or I could just sheep and just put like a
Why at the very end but that would be totally cheetah
And just to me
I'm right
Yeah that's exactly the same thing
So now I'm that looks like it may be right
Maybe I'm plugging in the wrong number
How to check your clothes near clipping Plains near the
The Heather playing making sure the close enough to to your eyeball that you
Meters away so I'm not I'm not drunk lines very long
But
Make sure
LAX and lyr
Different
Is 1 lighthouse
One of these are xry
Call this
I'm a big fan of printer
I think
Printf
Is the kind of thing
Oh there we go
Quiet what's wrong what
This is the problem
Why used
BL sweet angles for both lighthouses
That would definitely be a problem
Here we go pics
Now the right Lighthouse uses the sweep angles from the right lighthouse
I'll look at that look at that
Oh my gosh that's gorgeous that looks exactly right
Well I mean
Create intersection of those two points from two different lighthouses
Is that exactly the same point
That's a good thing
I'm getting chills by the way that they look so good
Right so that's that definitely validates that we're not doing something obviously wrong
I mean it could be that they're both consistently wrong but I definitely look
Plausible given where they're heading out is and and also
Where the lighthouse is all right it looks like it looks like we're in business
Cool
So then the next thing I guess the next thing I know yeah we wanted me to try to do that
Hint
Near all is saying something
I don't know why I can't click enter
That's not working but whatever Mike if you can see the see the stuff that's in my text there
Near all is pointing out that you know what I'll just say it out loud
Cuz I can't click enter
My my frustration with a lot of development environment has to do with the amount of size that the development Byron takes up
The amount of sides of the executables take up the length of time it takes to compile and there's a lot of things you might think like woo-hoo
What really causes a lot of problems like when I give somebody Arduino environment and it actually takes
Computer like
12 seconds to compile it every time they want to change something
That's really detracting so like
Ipsy plus plus was really fast in compiling and execution then that would be
No big reason to use it and I'll admit a lot of the reason it's slow has more to do with historical reasons than current reason so it's not really against the law
Moving on
Oh my gosh so much stuff the a big thing that that just happened
Are all pointed out do you use the face State ho no
Where is it
Do you use the base station Factory calibration data yet
EG the rotor FaZe offset akf calda and phase
No
I have never heard of it until right now I don't know where to get it
I don't even know what it's part of
You can tell me where to find it and what to do with it that would be super
Cool
Add an addition you could also then drop that into the
Data processor
Which could then make it so be applied to everything
Going to need at least phase soon what is FaZe
What is this phase thing
Going to need it soon
I don't know what npm is
So
Maybe
Merrill or or
Or Allen if either of you guys are interested in explaining what this face thing is about to say like a quick
Webcam video or something like a like on YouTube just post it to YouTube like a quick 2-minute video explaining it
45-minute or whatever I think it'd be a lot of fun for us to watch that here
So if you guys want to go like explain it or something like that
Would be pretty cool
Cuz I don't know anything about it I would just be reading the otx page as it goes
Stop posting Discord you're not up for it you're not up for explaining it
Josh Allen wants me to move the headset around
And to see the data in real time
How hard would it be
For you to I know this is not an immediate change
For you to connect
To my demon which is streaming out the XYZ data
Unreal time
Beyond
Draw the lines in your in your space based on that data
Hold on so you want me to connect to your demon yes
And your demon is on that machine
So you're talkin about like a socket
So you can connect by the socket
And that if possible and real-time just draw the lines coming from the lighthouses
Are the X and Y lines
Of of where the headset would be in 3D space
Based on those lines
Yeah I don't think that would be
Are you running it on this machine guess
And the demon
That you're running
Which word program so you can actually what you can do if you have like
Batter something I'm going to just see temp test data. See
Is Jack points out you can stream it in by the console so I can
I can say lb include stdio.
What's going on up there we go
Yeah this weird that it really is a lot slower with us
Dumb
Stephanie's going to add give me a second guy sorry sorry Dave Hold On
I have to add this to the to do so we don't forget about it
Am I still on the on the is my console still up
Okay
I will not go back to your console
I'm a little bit confused as to why any kind of factory calibration information would be needed
For the lighthouses considering
I mean unless there's nonlinearities within the sweep
Like it moves faster in certain parts of the sweep and less fasted others
I don't understand why such a system would be necessary to have any calibration
That's that's very confusing to me
Yeah I don't I don't understand it but I'll comment this and I'll click on the link now
Phase four rotors eurofase 4 rotor one
Tiltrotor zero Telfer rotor one
Oh man we are going to have to start decoding the otx stuff
Bummers I didn't want to do that
Apparently we will there's otx information that comes between coated and data that you don't get but that I get
That comes from the beta the lighthouses and what is OOTD
00:00 TX
What does OTS mean
The name is made up find a real name OK what is otx mean
Lighthouses
Pulses impulses can either be long or short and buy depending on whether the sink faucets
Being long or short
It actually encodes data that way
You'll actually like like a 10-10 it transmits it very slowly but over time
You can actually receive from both base stations Apolo TX message
That will give you a ton of information about it
Including whatever phase 4 rotor one
Oh neat
Omnidirectional Optical transmission how is it omnidirectional
Is it just
Omni is so like not
Geographically know
Cheo
Geometry not geometrically omnidirectional not
Datum Direction omnidirectional
Make a note for that one for narrow
Josh you're just going to have to join us one of these days for these live stream
You're only like an hour and a half away and I know you're not even an hour and a half away
Set includes curve orientation gibbous
FaZe
I'm sure that if virologist knows that all of these things are but
What
Convex or protuberant
Phase of the
I was totally working on something somewhere
Terminal
Terminal ok
Is it okay if I have your screen up some
Years ago you won't need two sockets by the way
So Josh had mentioned that we should be using that you can use netcat to just type it in by standard in
How do I do that I'm about ready to send you an example
So will your code block until I receive the data
Oh that would be annoying for you wouldn't understand weather
I'm just trying to understand what the behavior is so I
Can be guaranteed to read the first float first
Write 20 in the first part first I won't receive this dream in the middle all start with the beginning of History
Putting beginning
When you start typing data
You will get a message it once I will say the x-axis from this this one is this Valley
Yes yes yes so I won't the first thing I read will not be in the middle of a line that will be the beginning
Correct
But then when your code is sending data at your code will be blocking until I actually receive it right
Your code is running
Prince2 netcat I guess
But then
Once it starts printings netcat
Netcat does not complete the print statement
Until my
Program receives the
I don't understand
So
If I start netcasting it in
I'm going to receive the very first
No you're able it will make sure a trunk some
The way I bought for the things so that it won't guarantee it will give you lines at a time again
But your code will be dumping outlines before I even connect
Yes
And that's okay
You can use S Canna by the way
Yeah and I told I just tested it is working
I should be able to just use regular skin do you have
Can you check real quick
I can't
By the way I just so I have it on the Stream
Alan says
I don't like the name to be honest centricity would be have been better without the cowl you should be able to get some kind of
Tracking it will just suck well you know what for right now terrible is fine until we get moving more
I should buffer a little
I guess it'll be a little bit of buffering
That young Fine Again by the way I do not have netcat
You have a soak at
Cfnc
Yes
Connect me let's make sure it works how do I do this on empty space when I
921 6811 163
Nono 192 168 168
11:11 153
And
And space it wasn't it wasn't updating on my screen 55555555
Up there you go
Cool cats really weird with that
Yeah I'm going to do I'm going to try
Terminated
But I just killed it
Try true
Doesn't seem terribly smoothie
Something's weird maybe that doesn't matter so much
Conference weird why is it crashing
Can you put it
I'm still on your
I think I would have to make them suffer no it would justify whatever the most recent is cuz I can just move it
Wait it's just going to be late for now
Is a timestamp built into the the date of the first second third fourth fourth grade element
But don't worry about that
Yeah that sounds good alright so let me let me hacks of things together then
That was
I hate s Olinger I hate s Olinger I hate s Olinger
So what do I have to do
And yeah it looks like a try it again try the NC thing again
Yeah
Yeah let's just not use that so cat
For a while can we use NC
You're fine keep using what you're doing for the sender you can't use unsay
If somebody doesn't mind working on my copy of the the data server and making it so can buffers
Stop batter that would be really cool
Cuz I think that's what's going on and I think that as soon as someone as soon as you like
Run out of data to States put it in and just drop it on the floor
Yeah I know if that's the linger reuse addresses for primarily for UD.
Right or
Or is it for TCP
Address
Yeah real good Anna Moana and a Moen a if you want to go give that a shot that be cool
Do you mind if I have your screen up
Show right now
You know if you working
Side of the lighthouse 5 thing included in the folder
So where is it
Yep there it is
That's my favorite
Except for live survive
All I have to do is just add the. See if I'll tonight
Can you move this window all the way to the left all the way to the lab
Everybody okay or actually or leave it there and I can
Truncate the left part of your screen good now everything's visible
Actually I heard somewhere that the light
Lighthouse does have a
Yeah Josh I typed those in cuz
I was being dumb yeah I think it has an accelerometer so that it can at least tell
Internally which way did thinks this down which could potentially make the determination
Haitian for you could use its accelerometer
What are data to more precisely determine its position because we can very precisely determine the shell
We'll tell you where on the shell it is so yeah that would be really cool for you
Accelerometer for it
Okay
Sounds like we need to deal with the otx stuff fine
Thanks Mom
Okay Alex well Dave's doing that I'll explain why the the accelerometer datamyte
I can get it too so
You look at the actually know what I'm going to do is on a pull-up bar
Box of plastic
So this right here is the graph of the probabilities of where the our lighthouse could be
I'm in Otis house are really nice shell one of the things that could be really done though is
You could more precisely determine where possible locations would be for where the
Wherever you call it where it where the lighthouse could be
Based on that she'll so mean when I go clear it up a little bit so Tuesday 6
Probably not the best number of try
Hello
My laptop is dying
That's weird that's a lot worse than I was expecting
What's up with that
I'm not sure why these graphs look so terrible that's very confusing
Are you stringing out to the
Nonton streaming you
Okay
Yeah that's cool
That's a funny shape that's really cool
What causes that shape
You get a chance
Brentwood again
Extreme you can just pack yourself
How do I
192 168 11
What are the numbers which lighthouse
Which sweep
Make a note
Hmd or
Wmd
And then it is timestamp
Heidi
Then it is
Scroll up song
But actually it is exposed the next one down is the sink ID which can be used for otxo you
Probably don't care about that
Then it goes time and sweet would you really do parabelle no
The time in sweet as the one that converts to Ingles
LS3 Dash
LOL I was about to come up with an idea that you guys could do
But
It wouldn't actually
I think if you want to be like LSM 303 cease or something you could actually get like North so that you could Orion people
Said would be like pointing the Right Way Forward every time
But I also realize that doesn't matter
And you probably North between all the devices you can least get them pointed whatever it's useless let's not think about that
New York closed voxels happen cuz it is destroying my laptop
Hand
Should I make you public now
If you want
Okay
I'm just right now public data
Now the people will get a chance to Heckle you
Move move your terminal more towards the
Alright
More toys make it so everything is pick pick a side and move everything to that side okay
And I will cut your email out
I was not visible by the way
So right now that terminal is off the screen to the left you want to move it right some
Lucas one right yes
There you go now everything is visible
I just
I'm reading in the thread and I'm trying to use proper
Programming practices
Into
Lock
M mewtwo EX
Because the chair resource
You should not need that to update values in a buffer
Do you have it's okay Dave it's fine
Pulsar atomic
Yeah but there's three different floats
Yes whatever
I'm also using a good programming practices
By putting my shared resource in a global variable
That way both threads can access the same data without having to pass it or not
It makes sense
You want any water
I think I'm good
I have to copy the code
Slightly different from this other code
Dutch ecstasy
Global
And now I'm just like using bad programming practices
And
Ignoring my own pound of fines that enumerate the different values
And just
Hacking it out
The simultaneous sampling really matter that much if you have like a an interruption coming off of the IMU
Like I'm like an Allison 90s one or actual basically all St mems divide cinemaware
Have an interrupt pin that comes off as soon as the date is red so it's probably sufficient for
Probably sufficient for what you're after Reynard
Andrei not renewed pregnant
I don't even think you have to use an external clock
I'm about to
I'm going to play an ad
I know some people not good at that is okay
What is your code look like now oh my good idea
I will admit that is one thing
Really annoying about the AT&T devices is that like the Allison 90s one will have two of the things like
The accelerometer and the gyro synchronize but then the accelerometer is there sorry the magnetometers
Deceleration and the magnetism synchronize but then the Gyros like
Phone thing that operates at a completely different set a raise so I don't really understand that
Actually I'm really curious now
You don't necessarily need to rebuild the clock it'll still tell you when the events happened
Because the interrupt pin but
And honestly I don't think it matters that much considering the rates are usually High Enough
Oh actually remind me there's a way of triggering it I'm trying to read what it is there's like a next turn
Conversions
What is the trigger event
I guess I should take the flight I actually know I don't even really know what the lighthouses I know
But the lighthouses have an optical sensor right
But we just can't get the data back from it at any reasonable time
Point is if you have them in a sorry dandb mode one will become the mask
After the other one will synchronize from what I understand
Be like oh he flashed then I'll flash now
What's the data ready pin
Odata enable
So I guess you just hook a date already am into data enable Ag and that should probably do
Something you want
And then you may not be able to control it
But
There is no denim right now there's no d e n
Accelerometer or gyroscope they'd enable yeah you can just totally regenerate everything you wanted from that in the magnetometer
And then you can get fully synchronize data
And it could be what you're after
Love the elephant 90s one
We are watching you now
Such careful locking and unlocking your data structures Dave
Yeah Live Free or Die right
Okay
Theoretically
We're good
Okay
I've no idea what's going to happen
I do
You're going to Tyler
Oh I didn't even think of that
Yeah
By the way it's not that you have to use a pipe
Yeah I know but I can't even oh you got more compile errors
The tenant to fix the compiler like this variable called Shay
Define
Arabic I thought the invention part had a worse RMS are than the Ellison part and it's like
Two or three times the price
I don't know
I just never trusted the events in part because it did so much magic junk behind the scenes that I didn't really know
Read hmd
HMT angles
989 I must have copied and pasted the erroneous spelling
Someplace else
Oh I didn't know you turn that stuff off so the invention 60/50
Emu and it was I don't know what tonight
I knew that does a whole lotta magic inside of it that I don't I don't know I play with it for a while and I was like I don't
Really like what it's giving me until I started using the Allison 90s one it's a different IMU
And Alan Yates just pointed out that you can just turn off all the stuff but the crazy
They do inside
I asked cat space type O I see you're doing
Diesel works
Can you move that over some I can't we can't see it there
It's definitely not showing anything for whatever reason let me see what's going on
Now something's hosed I know it's going
Oii transfer problem I'm only going to
81 Lighthouse at it I'm only going to show one way right now
Stream was actually down weird
Disco fun times are you guys can't see it now you guys can use the thing over some
Disco fun time there's something weird going on let's just pick it up and move around
Oh hey oh that's a little bit crazy I need to make it
Phase-out overtime I'll put a frame numbers that keeps track of train
The last time was updated
Yeah
I'm not deleting old data let me let me to buy phase out the date
I would not have expected that
All right out the old data and if I do
If we haven't seen it in the last like for friends or something like that
At that autentica weightless by
Guys haven't seen it
He has googly eyes now
There we go now has eyes actually pointing in a reasonable Direction
Don't forget you can use
OG get absolute time is generic okay I can do that
That works too
What 0/0
Sorry that was me I'm due. Sorry that was me LOL something's hoes with
My laptop right now
The hack
I can't switch desktops anymore
There we go
Check time 3:37 so we still got 20 minutes left
So what's up
What's up what's going on
Oh I was just thinking about how to write multi-threaded programs
It's fine just don't worry about locks
Just don't lock it just set it back to zero like okay still like operations on the ends are all the Thomas
So you can just have them 20 and I just updated from somewhere else
Okay well then we'll just
If we're not worried about things
Then yeah we can do that
But I still should probably eat
Know somebody's
But
Why does Dave have to phase out all day. Okay so Josh the thing going on there Dave wants to
Phase out the old data
So that it's not
It's not shown still with line so like if you haven't seen a line in awhile I just doesn't show it anymore
Picture of the same data
Looks like it's still sending data
Then
It is it's just throwing out the older data
19 minutes ago Dave
I'm just messing with you it's okay if we don't get it in time
Oh by the way I didn't check are you making sure that if it's below if it's at zero it doesn't keep decrementing or incrementing or what
Oh wait no you're adding right you're sitting at 20 and then adding yeah we have like
4 billion frames we have a problem but other than that will be okay
Alright
I think that ought to do it
Change my name
What about you
Oh you can't have equals
That is true
Hmtv
Wait GCC does that are using clang
No I'm using GCC supposedly
I don't know whether
I don't know whether Apple somehow play sgcc is claims
Are the licenses compatible between the two
So that you can cut and paste code from one of the other I don't know
Close
Alright
This time it's going to run
I thought I had my myusername is all lower caps I guess I never I never never changed it
Alright
Oh that's that works great
Yeah
What the heck did I do wrong
Underscore ID to be outside of the range
I mean I can check that
Is anyone else DVR
And reynaud says that it's likely actually climbed even if it says she sees it
Yeah that's that would make sense to me
Freeway did you build a clean
Elway doesn't matter you are using C files
Global
Well
Actually
I betcha
Why
Won't
Disco.
Play I don't see how that could cause a problem
Well if it wasn't
Clearing out twice as much memory
Sex should be
Phasing out after 10 frames
Wonder why it's looking all wacky
That's a little bit too crazy
It keeps deleting because it had doesn't see it with him so you know what I think the problem is I think your accent
Why not you're asking why your lighthouses are flipped
Do you think that I'm putting one in the wrong
Let me see you know it's possible
ARS
2 + 301
Anyway
R4l
I don't think it's going to look very good
That looks worse right I can't even look the same but because I think
By then
The back
Oh yeah I know it's crazy
Yeah I will
But what happens if you move it something's just hoseman what happens if you move it
To the right of the
Are you have to move your window more to the right
So office working up is kind of right but there's still a lot of arthritis wrong
Something just doesn't look right
Yeah I know something still wrong
Not sure what it is
Is rotations here
It's saying the rotation
I should pronounce Lighthouse switch
Home
I have an idea for dinner idea
Pick a lighthouse tell me which what which light house to pick one
Can you see anything coming from the right Lighthouse now
I can see something from both
Well that's definitely wrong then
Oh I see what I can think of what happened now
Yeah so I'm not phasing it out properly I'm not phasing out the old
I need to phase out all four values
Dino technomark oh yeah the way we're doing this is this data
This data coming into this live survive contact is being sent to Dave
As well as to the screen and if you like it can be sent to you as well
You want to make it to A-1 as X and Y in the other is why the next
No I just need to phase out all four right but I'm saying you switch to your Acura indices
Change that back
You have sweet no stop stop look at that up there up there at the top
You go sweep Nam then none Suite
Oh yeah that that's what I was planning to
Did I do that the same
Wait a minute
That's the wrong one
That's right
Oh yeah sweet person numb right
Yeah
I mean look at how I'm using it
H&B angles are sweeping
I'm sorry guys you can't see that
There we go
Okay
So that could have been the problem also because that that could have easily caused the problem okay
But I already changed it to make it better when we finish
In fact yeah that is the
Is it no it's not
Maybe it is
Wolfie
But yeah that that that that's that's definitely that was definitely wrong with it was
Need to go up to where I initialized I need to clear it all out
If its Global variables that always start zero
Yes
Always
I don't believe you but
You know
Alright
I need to check Ollie's
That should fix it I'll give it a shot
Oh my gosh yes okay
But it is only works if it shows both if you could both White House with the same that is true but I'm okay with that
Persona floor
But is that lady that always coming over this way
Oh yeah okay over here let's see if we can get along here
There's gotta be a way I can make a quick change of the code
I can get it
But it shows one of the other
Okay go for that
Just ask video
Uncommon all of the checks so uncommon all those if things if the the time than this
Justin commented trust me
This one
That I know I know I know
Okay it's definitely 90
Give me a call I'll move it move it more towards the Sun
Hey are you telling me to move it in frame
Okay
Okay yes this is exactly right so if I hold it up here and I make it every point
Isabel
I can talking to buy
Thanks
This is perfect
Are you also going to call to tell me to move it in frame
Frame okay
Perfect is working okay there's still a lot of stuff you need to do
Spectacular
Oh yeah versus down here
Alldata
Oh okay thank you everybody for come
Coming out will be doing another stream tomorrow to hack multimeters
I hope you guys liked it
Oh great thank you everyone
Five minutes left of any any things they want to do
Actually I guess I should probably
Keep playing the song forexminute
We can do it now so
Look at it but they don't look glorious
Beautiful so wonderful
Okay
Hello
Playing with the code that you wrote is more fun than writing more code
And that's when your like maybe 6% finished with the game it's more fun
Play You're broken completely not ready yet thing
Then it is to write more okay with that being the case for right now and I'm okay with being 6%
Okay thank you everybody for coming out hopefully
At least a few guys tomorrow