Thank you for coming out to the 7th alive survive live stream and things
Cooking along I was just really surprised by how much people have gotten together online and just very
Things that we found out we've needed along the way and really this project has been so much
Bigger than I expected it to be I figured we just get some like no scandalous and lions and just throw it in there
Turn the light white
Let's for the hmd and all the Watchmen are and everything else is working really actually
I'm only going to room always assuming and the smallest person there that really ready to admit that I'm not and this is definitely
Close x
The problem of what does the HTC vive is doing is a lot bigger than I thought it was
So one of the things we ran into towards the end of the last live stream was
A comment from from Alan youths basically like well I guess it's the best he's going to be able to do be
Cotx kaldata
Really is it really that important in the experience yeah yeah really important so I had
Joshua he was my roommate in college for many years we are
We actually worked on a game engine together for several years to
Can help answer all the answers like yes you can be killed some 0tx data
So for those of you guys who don't know what it is is the
The data that comes from the lighthouses because there is no
There is no mechanism easily for the lighthouses to send data
To anything else except for
Peruvian true the white coming out of lighthouses in the sink passes
The sync pulses artist
Guess what can you find find the video and will pull
I'm in anyway pointers it's a fairly complicated protocol on dealing with a lot
Wacky did stuffing stuff just like the crazy bencoding on the Watchmen and Josh
Take that and turned into something actionable
Arm
Soa
I think you just do view imgur whatever it would probably be fine
So you still pulling their dad
So see here sorry about all the streaming issues earlier to
Anyway so thanks for coming everybody so we've got a number of things people are coming up a little bit
More recently than before mw10 is really happening in his too
Project initially we were going to do everything strictly with the headset and the Watchmen
Looking kind of important that we do something a little bit more generic
On to see guys know
I just pulled up the imagery here
On this is what a base station looks like this is an early version of Playstation in specifically the o
The X8 is what's included in these flashes which are specifically coded length of time
In order to actually transmit the calibration information about the Watchmen
Actually works one bit at a time so each flash you get one bit
And then there has to be
Reveal the entire free
Talk about it more into how how you do
Basically the weather at work's is
Digital console it looks for the
18 preamble 1700 by 1 and once it picks up on that
It starts pushing the individual bits into a buffer and once it reaches
Transfer device
Has a call back and let the library handle what it wants to do list
What's the date
If you leave it open for a minute sorry the people didn't see so what was going on is this
That's right here
And this the two rotors but it's this flash that happens and that is a
Play coded length of time
Ok and you can pull off
Thesaurus
I said this to always there
That's good yeah
Ok so some of the things that are that we've done since last time was that and another big one
Taking for me at least I don't know how big it is for other people
B
Call open the Sky
For me I was able to
Calibre
So right now what you guys are getting
To see that clearly
Stop
Scanner
This should probably be
It is a broken fan laptop sounds like an engine
Sweet just means I can actually monitor while
Ok
This
There's you guys can see what's going on with it
So right over here I have a
Play that we've been using for some time
Is the X and Y you from each of the two lighthouses there in there
As well
Here
On
Turn the camera off
Surround you can see
Changing the time
Sometimes when they're charging
One of the fine soon so really happens here is
Are we have
Survive Albert
01652 you guys can see it
Thank you
Good for you guys can you see everything clearly
Is that
On going to assume that selection with smallest lights
Ok that's going inside of survive cow it contains a state machine which
Through all of the
The the different states in which we would want a cow
So I'll walk you through it looks like right now
So I can just rang calibrate
Piranha headset
And if I
So now
I have Watford won in Watchmen 2
Start that again see you see what happens when it first starts
Look at the very top of the screen it is collecting 0tx data 0 0 and then those numbers count up
You're counting to b number in which the OT x is currently receiving
The base stations
Please watch while I can put down on the ground
It's going to try to find a common of point on the Watchmen
That was a little bit quick
Probably not gonna work out
So it's really a collecting sweet data internally
I'm so this was something that was kind of done before in a very Emanuel fashion
But now it's pretty much automatic
Search collecting the data with the Watchmen in the hmd underground and all of that
And then what it's going to do is going to go round the find the Lighthouse find algorithm
I'm the date
And B Rock
Think that's probably kind of wrong but that's no reasonable data
For where the where the white houses are stores that back in the data structure
Your life survive so now it's actually able to do a room calibration inside
Self
It doesn't really do
That
Match the artist
So that's that's really kind of like the new thing is that now we can
Inside of the
Inside of Life survive itself there is the mechanism for self-calibration
Now this is only going to change because I was mentioning mw20 want to be able to use this
Stone hardware instead of just specifically they are Watchmen sorry to Watchmen
And a mean
So we are going to have to change some of that
The other thing I really wanted to talk about today was the pose estimation information
Until right now
The way that we actually do the camera finding
There's only two ways that we've been playing with it one is the way I do it in the others the way that MW Charlie does it
Why does it using a series of Tories like Taurus
Where is it difficult to describe and see if I can have
I can pull that up here
By the way if you're curious about hopping in and getting things going on the github issues are pretty good place to do it
Here
A solution for this
Add much more to do with finding the relative distances between
Quite so - much more to do with
Simulation of an environment in the moving a camera and a whole bunch of places in trying to find the best possible location
I'm he's on the other hand
Has much more to do with
I think it maybe it was good
Leacock
Sorry this two guys confused so frequently
Looks like my Chinese so for his it produces a series of possible
Armed forces of where the where the lighthouses could be
Armin goes from there mine is just a fundamentally different way where it simulator
The lighthouse on
Oh my gosh it's so smooth on this compare
What I do
What does show us the probability of where the
So if I do this he owes me
The chances are that the Lighthouse for
The lighthouses probably somewhere in there
And
Dr Whitehouse is somewhere over there
Canon rock solo
Show the doors going to be some more work done two
And resolve that
But doesn't really two different approaches
Yeah that would work that way
However I really wanted to go into though was the discussion of what's really going on
Here with mine and why I think that is kind of a fundamentally bad way of doing
On
So what time effectively trying to do
Is I pretend that we have at the origin
The hmd that's the head-mounted display that sitting right there on the floor
And I'm calling that my origin
And then
What I do is I iterate through an agency this is Vauxhall so it's a bunch of
On the street like checks I say if the camera or the light
What was at this point right here
Right there
Would that work with that produce a
Is that visible can you
Can you put up on your screensaver
Does that work
Sodium
What do I do if I try it every single but possible location and I say will ok
The lighthouse at the origin with this particular properties and move around and
And all of that
Then
What is the probability that that's where the Lighthouse could be
Can I produce the scrap of all of that
Now that's that's the backwards way of thinking about it turns out
What I really wanted to do with the use that dissolve with lighthouses work as we do need to know it like
You can also use that to determine where the headset itself is
So both directions back to a comment that telling you
Play the end of the live stream I believe with livestream number 3 when we had
Single lighthouse pointed it headset and he's like yeah find out where the headset is and Michael that seems useless
We should have two lighthouses in go from there but really if you can figure out
Where are given object is
From one lighthouses point of view in figure out where does from the other lighthouses point of you you can go a long way to
Solving with the actual object is and I think that's the direction I want to head
I think I wanted to scrap this solution and this mechanism for finding the lighthouses and instead writes
Code
Try to find a location of an object based on its angles
And then use the code in Reverse to find lighthouse and then use the code
Normally once the Lighthouse is fine for everything else
So
Armex that one change I want to make
We have anything else at the moment for the introduction summary
Demonstration
Let's see what are people chatting about right now
Yeah like survivors Tron really low end systems goal is minimized
To use minimise requirements
And yes potentially even run on the
Run on the
This visualisation here of the probability cloud cannot be Run in real time
Are as it is
But it's most because there is no real data for to be processing in Real-Time
I think it'll be a lot of fun to try to figure out some way of streaming data to a web page dynamically
That would be a lot of fun
I don't have any data to do that with right now
Arm
So
Not really sure where to go from there
Some of the other things I wanted to mention so right now all over wipes survive is
Lovely status
So if you look inside of
Survive internal that age
On there is a structure for the survived contacts
Which has a line of basic stuff in
I'm in here there's a lot of this
Functions and another start that have to do with really
Specifically headset into Watchmen data
Like here we have
The data structure that contains
The
The headset in The Watchmen
And really this this should be switched out to be much more of a
Over
Of various arm
There's really no reason for it to be
Hard-coded in here
Have seen heard wrong button before tab
2fb
What is that
Hello are we out of sync
I guess I'll wait until we find out what people say
But yeah Vauxhall tastic was not meant for dynamic data but I think totally wrong
You know my other favourite technology websockets
Arm
So one of the things that were going to need to do with people that have driver registration in this is a scimitar
From what we used on on coloured cord
And what that allows you to do with something like coloured cord let me go check that out
So what you can do is you can write code that will be a driver for giving device or
Actually a calibration system
And then
Instead of having to haven't like a bunch of complicated switch statements or anything else that will check a certain driver
You can simply
Register
Your driver
And that can just be done right here
And the really big benefit of this is you can simply link against life survive in
Be able to have your own drivability and you won't have to recompile live survived and custom new hardware
Or new fundamental ways
Doing things and life survive it will just be able to be registered in with the driver
The other thing is that survivors finally getting big enough now that we really need it
Systems that's what I was signed by Josh primarily
Do you want me to
Go over there right now
Remember they can see the whole thing
A little bit bigger bigger bigger bigger bigger
Arm so do you want to talk about it
Well basically the way is going to work is it going to rain
Data out of a json file
The reading light down yet
With the writing stuff
The past
Tower 2
Haven't tried it out yet so it's Friday crashed
Search the interesting get around doing that
Play configuration load
I am unfortunately work I never the point now or needs a little bit more boring stuff to get there
Get things moving well
Yeah I don't really know where does suggest from now
Hello this was
I guess it was intended to be assured livestream I don't think was intended to be this
But I have everything on my list checked off now it's
I know what are we
Yeah we do
What is
Amiga 1000
What does it have 68007 point 16mhz
What if I upgraded to 28
Maybe
Is it is 14.4 unit
But my I have a 60 30 that runs at 25 and it has a 6881
OK that'll be fun
Do you have a c compiler for it
Like a modern development environment
You can code it in tested in a reasonable length of time
My question is can I can I work on my desktop and say
To that end
What I mean it could be on the network so you could just walk on it
But would you see like to be ok
I don't know
This pretty benign
I'm trying to figure out what you can set a reminder because he obviously certain things are just not going to be support
When was GCC 2 created
Larkin you sorry
Lemmy
I'm curious will I be able to do GCSE to
I haven't done enough with
XC compiler for me go as m68k
Stop in 34
Does no ogc forex does not support m68k
What's 2.95
You're talking here I want to know why all the young people use for tabs for space tabs
How young is young I used to
You'd better be making them tab
I know you won't be working on because it's so
Brendon like spy finally hates JavaScript just
Just
Yeah I don't get Brendan on
Ok what else to test right now then we can fire blight survive
Medela
Morning Rose working on earlier was getting the
YouTube
It's still running
I was getting it so that it would actually be able to find all the lighthouses in save in
The
Play that is life JS is love
How are you people are so weird
On
Yes it is
Linux 68k
Would you get the Omega to output to the HTC vibe video
That would be a slow like framerate
You know what you're playing if you're playing the live on in Omega you're probably get expected
What times are the best fare
I think my laptop on a standard charge
No lights or 5 is definitely going to stay and see when I went out doing any other
Problems
So data recorder see if it still runs yeah does so I can still up with this data
Actually no one thing I really wanted to do was
In here what I want to try doing
Is
I want to try make me to output the imu as well because right now it's just not doing that
To see if I
I just fainted in running
Earlier in the week talk about
Recording
The live data
We can play back later on it simulated by
Continue developing ok that seems like a reasonable time for us to work on live
First I think I do when I get the
See how that work we probably want to make it to you can stream
Because we have this right now streaming to the terminal and then I wrote that to last time
Which farm
Call
Data server
So
Can you try taking the Samsung it's a little bit more robust
One thing I'd like to do anybody who's up for it I would like to try to run the data server again if somebody on the internet
Connect an and just try that out
I think that would be pretty cool
On
I had no idea as to what I think was causing the day that Dropout 3 bad before
Arm so
See if I can
Don't
Ok
Yeah it's been raining pretty hard
What what kind of weather
Were you were
No he describes something pretty pretty crazy
Weight recording format does does the HTC vive always support actual recording
If so I did not realise that in which case I guess I'll be up for trying to
Make it
He compatible
Arsenal voice in Southern Ireland and he was
Get a picture on Twitter of something crazy happening
See where is that
Here
Yeah that's definitely here that's really serious stuff
Sorry that was the strat
Something I need to
Someone I think there are venue
Phone of job but enough people wasted they could have experienced that you could make a video of VR experience
Wednesday at work
On
Yeah yeah
Brendan says Dad eventuary Rider counting just as software instead of accounting
Show
What am I doing is I'm going to make it so it's possible to drop
Packets if you're connected
In
And if you do drop them it'll be ok for a little bit in there and if you keep dropping on
It will eventually kick you out but I'm
Sea settings protobuffers
Actually never really worked at protobuffers
Protocol buffers
I'm guessing it's what you mean right
Protocol buffers the Google Play
Someone start a collection to get that laptop fan replace
New battery in a CD drive
Give me a moment here
I'm going to have to login to my router and open
Portcullis computer
CD drives in broken for years
Why is my Akira
Seriously why is Mighty wrong
That's me
Firewall
What 4 words
Does anyone from the internet want to see if they cannot connect in
Oh sweet that actually works you can ping home.st law.com
So you still a Telnet to
Silicon Port 9999
No
554 what have I done
There we go
Ok
Yeah and see if it's or if it's dying to like it was last time for a lotto
That was sad
Turn on the lights
I think I might try to do right now
Make a
Alive survive
Front end so I can feed data without actually being hooked up I guess
Ok
That's right now feeding data out
Just edit piraino just to get things moving calibrated see here
Saying anything
Are people still ok I can collect it works it works
Is there discord yes there is discord
I will
Yeah actually I can still hear certain links never expire
Person on the Earth
Ok
Yeah we had a power outage sorry
Everything's back up now
Vibe survive
Hey it's like everything is fine
Restart the data server
That was going to post a discord
Laptop laptop anymore it doesn't
Call
Server data server 9999
Ok
Looks pretty Spanky
Somebody has already connected in two people have connected
I think what I want to do right now just for the takeover
Things here
Are Ben one thing you might have missed a little bit earlier as I do want to change the way this works I think I want to do a little bit more
Like what you guys are sending out in the second or third livestream where
I find a pose estimation thing based on the camera space information from the lighthouses and then
Used to determine the location of the lighthouses and other poses originally I wanted to be able to combine information
Lighthouses in name creates a single pose estimation but I don't think that will work very well
So I'm going to try doing a switching to this other one and it is probably more in line with what you and Alan have been
Before with on the pose estimation
Which I feel embarrassed that I'm doing things other be fair what happened was I thought I was smart
Going to do some clever way and it turns out the clever way was the dumb away and then I found out ok this is
Better way to do it you guys right whole time so
Ok are you guys getting dropped forcibly or you just disconnecting
Play Attack without above ground cables
On purpose I got disconnected ones still getting kicked
I know that would be there would be since I started back up
Calibrate quiet ok so in here
Well I should be able to do is just shut the date in through the default imu process and through the door
White process so I kind of wanna try that now
China's be the beginning of coming back
Timer for the data
Yeah
Remember that actually works I think it does
Everybody get dropped all at once
I was weird
Can you just the first too many people connecting away there's somebody who's just spamming me
Who's 4666
Who is Dad
Hong Kong who are you
Somebody from the Netherlands from the Netherlands that is spending the server
Clearly Spelman
Whatever you guys are having fun I guess that's what matters
Oh you know why
In order to test so what am I
Try running another instance of Life survive so like this one's recording the data if I try
Playing it back it has to first connect to vinyl
Rape but I won't run for you because it won't we can connect device
We should probably fix there that's definitely something we have to fix sooner than later
What is an interconnected device
Because like you're right doesn't know what to do if it does
And that's totally about it should not have a problem with that
Lights to five should survive without
Kneeling next to the five
I'm thinking of pluggable sources thing is not getting more and more
Is there really sad that before you can do anything you find out you have to do like telling things and then to do any of those other
To do like a million other things
Mrs check discord
Disconnect
I don't understand what am I supposed to be looking at them they're saying that
The address to connect to
Oh yeah
Do I have access to New
So that's going to be a little bit you know whatever was trying to hack it in real quick and see if we can get something
Headless
See all that work
Data recorder
Expose
Surviving col
Can we make it so if we are in a headless mode we don't do anything stupid
Like trying to hold a USB
Hey sweet ok
How is a lot easier than I thought it would be we didn't have to go code an entire subsystem
Ok so what that means is this code just runs on a little spin loop all the time
So I should
Tabs
Why in the world would that be defaulted on
Ok so
Debtline
Play I'm jet wind what is that syntax
Are cats tbnr number
Actually so you know I gotta get your thing
Rayburn saying I want to get up your arm
What's your IP
Ok
Scanner
What's better than il2 somebody else's code that shows you how they did
Washing the chat for me
Yeah yeah now I can read the data
Paranoid
I can't hear it
What happens if you put it on something fabric
The one two
So
First character
Yeah it might have been reverberating to the table because it feels like I felt like
Feeling in my arms when you are running it that way so
Stay here
Light data
Just trying to sell his studying
A scanner line
Is this the right number 12345
Will this work with Sam
Calibration also yes that's right now
Turn into the calibrator
Yes that is the goal so this works like as I expect I should be able to tutor
Tell the difference
Timestamp a code
BA code x a code
ID sweep
IKEA
Think that's the right thing
House can be a little tricky
Think that's the right
Use for everything
Headset and white man
Putting the data recorder
Goes
That's all
Do skills horribly wrong like I'm noodling the data in the
Place it's just
Just wrong well I might just typing the data from the serial terminal into the function call but I would not
And I guess that makes sense
Hopefully
The first one is timecode
I don't think so cos I'm going to be the only already be processed by the
Most two figured out what the type deltatime should be this is after does the December duration stop
So it like it knows like this is when in the sweep and happened so
Why am I blanking on the mile
Santa idea which one is centrally this
After timecode
You know what a reasonable names
A code
Ok that gonna work that is totally Alan
Wait is that
Yeah is that I've only ever had
I would like there's just world
Well let's see if you come
A solution in then I'll get this committed and you guys can go have fun with this or something
Can you tell me if it's constantly crashing on you
No it died
Pilot crash
That was weird
I know why crashed
Cos it doesn't know where the points are for the headset because it can connect the head
We should probably also stored below the point locations in the config-file somewhere
Down
Is it going patience
Whatever it's worth committing now
Trash how to write
Ok do you want to see if you can find it off network wise
Ok so this is my cock you survive here
Give me a minute
When did I just use Nana
I just use illicit seriously now
Oh yeah yeah yeah that's true so I have your screen off
Holloway everything inside this fox is visible to the world
So I just artificial I drew it yeah you can go play out there now
And see what you're doing are you to be calling and then
I'll give you my IP
I don't know what my IP11 254 but I don't know why I don't know
Sweet potato
Turn on my starting
Clientele from yeah
Cal underscore choir
I do not have device connected to my machine
The network
Latency
Does not what I would have expected to just work but there is interesting
Does give us another reason to distort the the point locations of
In the config files that's going to be a pain
Yeah cos as soon as I get to the final calibration step it's like I need to know where the points are in and it just crashes
No hello site no I do have a bit of an sp30
Private garden playing with
See if I can show that
Network
Carragher
My car's coolant cap without dinner
On
Hey I'm actually I doing a live stream right now can I call you back and I'm guessing an hour's
Short live stream
I would like to go out with
You're ok he said he's up for it
Yeah 2-hours he said yeah we be funny done by then
MC hear you see my camera is just hose
Hey there we go ok
Settle I have actually been playing with the esp32 as
Come on
Whatever
China's I've been playing with esp32
Pretty premium so far just little things here and there and I take
Play am now able to print circuit boards at home down 2.4 mbsc discount
Oh another thing that we did with the HTC vive stuff so
So before there is a thing we were completely tied to the fort
Tn25 itself used on but the problem is that there's really no good source for 48 mHz
Turn the ESP so for on collecting just regular data that was not going to fly
So loud survive does now actually have on
Configurable time basis so this has to do with the disability waiter the VAT is that all
These will be provided to whatever speed you actually want to operate at so right I'm in media
Please realise it has
What's going on
Cheap recommend
Is asking for PCB printing
Can you use a pendulum p2502 w
A super cheap
I'll pull up and I will show you guys just how ridiculous
Play cheap
Is my internet not working now
I'm streaming they're alright
Yes yeah I think it's
Am I streaming now
I think the internet here dropped out ok
No I'm definitely here is still here we don't have a power outage and I know where that was
Add this printer right here
When I bought it was 3699 3799 new and came with the
3 decent size cartridge and I bought another cartridge for it they're really cheap
Really nice
There are plenty fine for PCB printing normally I have to double up
He doesn't have enough turn aside to like
Double up transparencies stack them but it's fine
I now switched out my LED process my process for exposure to an LED
That was going to slow me down but it turns out it exposes in about 4 seconds so that's not an issue anymore
I'm leaving now to do now
So cold is right now for the most part
Going to be working on getting a I really want to do ESP tags to begin with
And after that I can go to switch off to whatever but I do want to do
Want to try to get life survive running on an esp32 so I can create kind of in a r
Environment where it'll be like a little screen that you can hold up in like look through and see
Around and be able to do that very very inexpensively I think there's some really things you can do with that
But the first part of all of that has to do with fencing on the ESB with you thinking I do with the esp8285
And be able to do it that way with that does not directly involved like survive
Dune Buggy asked like super stripped-down so I think that would be fun
Oh no not really have anything else to go over right now
Add some data running we can kind of processor
Yeah
4 seconds 4 seconds
You have a video of their just couldn't look so ridiculous it's done
Ok I don't know
Not really I feel like the only working when we doing is to do some of the more plausible stuff with
Divide really rather not do that on livestream I think that would detract from it
Yeah actually so I should have clarified that with the yes peas on the what I want to do with them
Is it going to be using the wrong packets from the ESP so you don't have to have all of this overhead
Connecting up in staying connected instead it'll just transmitter Warframe whenever it's easily white horse
Immediately just send it and then I'm a computer and it'll have at least two probably
Real text just sitting in passive mode listening and whenever a message comes
ESP it just goes in processes that right then and there that way you don't have to worry about staying
Connected you don't have to worry about the added latency of a wireless network and stuff like that it's it's
Stream Lilo latency when you use the red packets cell that works out pretty well
Are we have anything else to you
Ok
Yeah yesterday 32 well 3.5 is 10
Without spending amount and I'm shipping yeah esp32 is a lot more
You cannot get a lot more easily you can also just buy the sky for you too
For me at 5 of them for 14.99
Yep yep
Sorry I guess most is anything else based on what we had said you were going to do or later on in the Stream
Probably just going to go call it quits
Thanks everybody for coming out I will have to find a year going over different things
Difficult to get work done right now if anyone phase of it
Alarm
I don't have a colour laser printer
No that's Josh Allen
Thanks everybody for coming out this could be a real quick thing
What we still haven't gotten adarshi by Lady to sell him to me
Sometimes getting things from people in China's a lot more difficult than you'd expect
Ok bye everybody