Where can I get something
We should make a display
Also my cat are you serious camera it's now 10 appears
Scratch
Bad
Ok
Existing
Uvc camera camera one
Christine would you mind at least popping it open on a laptop so you can moderate chat
Plugging the webcam in a different for here
90s live
People in my liver offline now
Hey there is a uvc camera now
Do you have a laptop
Can go down here for right now
Everybody know that
Are you in the live stream
Whisper
Are doing this live stream from my Josh Allen Excel crashes else he's the one who's been doing the configuration subs
I'm also trying to sell him a virus from somebody at work but we're having trouble with that because
The song
All the computers are awful here
For some reason he has a house that is why
Bad for the vibe I don't understand how this works
He's got this area over here
Which is like a huge area which is great for the vibe
Channel 4 start
Radio
What is
Reflective
Or something
Quiet
It's just
Snooze like Echoes and stuff of the violin
I have to figure that out and tribunals going on here
So right now his laptop there on the floor
And it's a sous laptop and right now trying to hack my tits in
How to get into alpha to the HTC vive
Because you want to take that and show them what options you get normal
I am only getting
Who options for
Resolution
Is either 641 for radio 720 by 14
Ignoring my bowes-lyon
I'm not really sure why
And so I think it has to do something don't like
The max clock it is laptop not being able to us
Can I see that I can't really
On
Brian are trying to figure out some way of hacking the
Do the right thing
TV
Can you go see that text clearly on online is bad arm
Is this reasonable
Ok
Can you read the text that is on the
The
Turn off the lamp
Ok
GoGo
Is 15 seconds is it
This is what in Eden set
Early descriptor
This is just a needed descriptor right here
What I'm gonna do is that dangerous can affect arbitrarily changing a to come and was like
Something
I'm using my new PC it's
Sitting just out of you down there
Are actually pretty if you want
Camera down
Towards the computer
You are not using they're not on the side there you go
New
Arm backup
Sure
Seeded code
Corals
I'm in so when you run this on the heater to give you these this information about the Egypt descriptors
This is information is normally stored inside of the HTC vive
But if you go into NVIDIA settings
You can then go for like the specific screen
Will be over what we doing is doing
Arm
Alright now or actually trying to get the HTC vive to run on Josh's or laptop there
In my run on the vibe I mean
Just output
Display like it all anything would be fine
It's very frustrating
Then you can do that on a divided self
We have that now
So I'm trying to get her to eat it in order to make
A mole
His computer is that would actually like
Run
So
So I was started doing they started changing these numbers willy-nilly
Like in 1774
And save the file out
And then run this
Complaint about the wrong checksum but you can see the change the the clock
Paris
Decode
You can see here I'll tell you somewhere
Play for
The game for
Something you did
Maurice Keating
Yeah
Yeah I don't know there is something will actually tell you what
What Hz screen refresh rate
If you are 128 MHz pixel clock
Noticing summary
Actually asked them
Would that be like it
You can't
So I guess I should have
Somebody else's succinct summary of what's going on in the answer is right now I know but it's
Or is it a document that I should be riding somewhere or something I should write into a description
If you do that
We did it took awhile to find out
It turns out there is a tool called he did the code
That when you edit it will actually tell you with the checks on should be
So we've been kind of London you're having a dark until I found this one is like you should change your checksum 20s
So right now even trying couple of different modes so 128 MB I was like to lowest
Yeah that's right now
Oops Clark 04
Yes
Play
Ok so
The problem with Josh's laptop has is he can't
You can output to the Vibe
Because apparently has a Max pixel clock that is lower than 297 mHz
It's just your HDMI
I don't know why is laptop just don't want to do it
I'm trying to make it so his laptop will send jumped the Viber lower frequency that might be good enough
I could use my
Tesco
Which is upstairs but Charles has stolen the man before
If anybody is near California Maryland and has a monitor we would really be appreciated right now
Don't have any way of making this work
Really good music common location and get them on her that way
What oh that's weird
I just did something
Massively
Let's try to a foreign see what that does
De server checksum should be O2
CFA exam so checksums are valid
To do now is I'm going to give this to Josh
We need a hand dryer
Because I can't pull out from Gmail on Wi-Fi
Prime now I don't know it
Oh yeah I know this is this is not near Baltimore
Is an hour and a half away from V maybe 2-hours from Baltimore
USB drive
Make sure
Nothing
It needs to be formatted just for now
The other thing is really confusing to me is it says that an axe Dark lock on the
5 is 290 mHz
But it specifies Clark that are way above it
Ok
Console
Skip the max Clark is 297mm or sorry 290mm
But all the Motors best 54 297 then
How long the world does devised work at all
Like I just
I don't get it
So I'm going to go coffee Charles II did that and I'm going to give it to Josh
How to get more
Received you think that
Enough
So Josh is right now going to take this file
Ok
I hope I'm online now
Boxes
We had a bit of a rocky
Joshua's wiring is very confusing
And whoever confusion here in with panel lights which they got turned off
Skip the computer and everything so that backup
Visible light 3 streamdale we had a power failure
What's the time
Charles
It was at Reed
Pause
Charles
Code
How's it going there is like atd tools in only one of them does white
Mum and the truth here
Screwed it
Play Castle
Reasonable
Is it
You can select me
52hz
Ok
Laughing virus still very sad
Can you set it up to use the whatever is the resolution known as what
Play the itself looks like it's just us but we don't talk to it
Enough
Ireland 60hz
What's 90
5 Hz and see what happens I have forgotten which feel that was
Shut up
Something is real
Play broken here open up the 51 and then
He has the wrong number of bikes so it's super super
Don't worry about that was like
5-minutes take up 4 minutes
Christine how much you don't care about protector tarot and everything
Useful files
This is the wrong number of bytes
All the vibes needed for me again and copy it to the USB drive something is really wrong
Guitar
I might have had the wrong number fighting that anyway
About 20%
Connect to outlet
Yeah can you can you just pull the
What do you guys have a pulley and he did it
Over here you know what
Lights
Turn it down
Turn off my computer
Ok see you have it now I'm driving
Ok listen here
Take a look and see if that's filas
Or something
Please turn that down
No it had the right number of B I had this set the width wrong
There we go ok
Everything's fine anyway
Save this into
Charles Eden
Place
Proprietary
So 250
MHz would be ok if the current one what is it it's
297 is 99 FPS
7 x 257
5.75
So we could do Carly do 75 and try that
I figure if it's not gonna work at 75 MHz it's probably looking for eggs
Clean ID
Places like
Profiles does it I never heard of this
Inshot can you link even in chat
Maybe I'll be in a second
I know I don't have black eyes I just naturally have
Exactly why I don't sleep well
So in here
Say what is it right now 253
Set 63 is to 53 what did you say was the needed to
Ok 299
÷ 90 x 75 + 200
Change July
Yeah we are worried that Josh's HDMI port could just be sad
What kind of like a jam ride
34th 320 I don't hear from her
The megahertz is by email
I'm just guessing 249 64 getting close
Is 24
Play 96 UK
So maybe 58
249 to DA7
249 17
249 16 17 17 closest so then
Who is Maiden
Check song should.be 0 and that's despite right here
Ok
Connect to the work ok
This to the USB drive again
Give a text to Josh
Changing random by
Over trying to change I just can't experimentally found that these can you buy tripe
Those two b control the pixel clock which is
This number right here
And this number right here controls I'm guessing how fast that shifts the day to help the HDMI
I actually don't know that much about HDMI
Set alarm that part out but we have found the Josh's computer just absolutely
We'll light output to 297 MHz on the HTC vive
Has in its display modes which is a 90fps signal in so right now or
Mountain knock vlps down there were sending to in order to make it so he can
Output this computer so
If all goes well we might have the only HTC operated 75 mHz
B floor lino
HTC motivated turn display just won't work unless it exactly now yes so
This could all be a blast
What was the name of the rating on that time
9.1 70mhz
Which works out to 7 /
7 x 9075.5
Matthew on
25th
225 what we have done that before
Display my laptop can do 3:30
Wait a minute
Change the resolution of your display on laptop
Yeah
This works I'm not to laugh so hard
What is the artist for sitting on
Turn it down
What is going on
Play music
Rolling the dice
Looking at his DP it says get one is 165
Is an EFT 2
25mhz
3:30
Station of the HDMI port
YouTube am really curious to see if that changes their
So you said it was not 225
Turn on
65%
Volume five
What's the
Just make it to 25
Give me a give me a second
U225 now
Yeah I guess
Programming mode
I'm guessing if I write to 2500 57
B47
Next sofa anymore ok thanks
Like
How do i NE
Knows how to find out what the max pixel 4 keys on the HDMI output on Raspberry Pi
That would be super cool cos I would love to know if it even technically possible for a Raspberry Pi to help put
Add needed resolution
Good replace
That's should be one day
Check someone's one be valid ok so copy that over
Play Jack
Ok
Playlist
What is up with
What is Max 1 is
Can I try this from us take the screen over and watching
Ok chat
Why is not showing any signs of life so there's mediaburst
68 hours
We can go HDMI 48
Max B
I just want to know that doesn't actually have this problem hand
Do you think your dad would have an extra monitor somewhere at home
RC chat so he says
150mm solo clothes
How do you help for 1080p 60 on a Raspberry Pi then
Is it just pixels x
What's actually 225
MHz
No
What's 68 minutes on your computer
Calculator
Turn on my hotspot
Yeah
Bigger than 1920 pounds
1260 on supporting
Me on come on guys
Well at least you guys are now calling my Hubsan dreams before I have to get them qual by Force
Does anyone else know if there is another Raspberry Pi like object that
That is that actually the right version
Josh I think this means that you're going to have to go back to me off
Pilot
Yeah it's just like it
Render
Dim the screen
My laptop screen
Can look it up for the Raspberry Pi 3 to see if that's the same
Baby really need
No newer versions do not use the same GPU
I will check this out
Search for people
Put it all down
Some fun taxi
4k
Interesting next
Sounds expensive
1280 or 1920 by 1200
What is the visor resolution again what should be like right on the cusp
2160 by 1200
Turn this off
Ok will look at all these pythons later
Ok
The second fight with yourself
On Windows go back to broadcasting from my laptop and then
Wikitest whatever we wanted
Someone said you are so can't use reduced blanking on device
Odroid C2
No I have the chat off now so I can see it
By the weekend that makes me very sad but I understand
We will look into I make a list of device
Is to look into a list do that right now
Wait what
Do the
Come on Jim up two Factor authentication
Am I I need a text
What about now
Is there an echo now
Resend code
Come on get up
Come to my phone
Muesli
I'm not sure
Better
Values on the right audio device
I mean it should be fine can you text me because maybe that started through
I take my phone outside and text it
Google Authenticator what is Google Authenticator
1 time
A text
How short is that guy
This tab probably check
Tell the truth I can actually create the issue until
I was just commenting to Joshua earlier today that when we were young
Promoting College whenever we would have like something we wanted to do we just start working on the problem in here
Start coding and we would finish coding and we have like 9 hours of coding in a day and decree
As we got older like
Like getting started to get to the point where we can start coding kept getting pushed further and further back
Yes Josh so now we work for like 8 hours so we can code 41
Ok I got a code
And you guys gotta see the code
Is it what time is it
Yes
Resend the code
Education background
Ok so for instance today in order to actually start working on this we have to go move
Air hockey table out from Josh's do you want to pick up the camera and point of this area had to move It air hockey table
Turn off Joshua's basement in order to get an area big enough to work with the five
The home via thing we're having a really big problem in this environment and we're getting reflections weekend
What from so we were sitting around 4 like until 2 a.m. last night like blankets covering up random things
Prove it
Go code things you just go like do the thing you wanted to do and
Like life is just
The fact you're getting older or it's Christine pointed out or maybe just a factor of
Do more complicated things
New issue request
Oh my gosh
I left my infrared camera at home
Wait what if you delete from now
That's fine I don't need any
What was I doing that's right
Life survive issue new issue identify
Minimal hardware that will be able to
Wasting time
If you guys on chat one-and-a-half any other
Translate you're pretty sure I can drive the Void let me know and I'll add them to this list or better yet go
Add to the ticket anything that you guys can find you guys don't mind and chat who were able to give
Play some of the information of the pixel Clarks and stuff like that you can add information to life survive ticket number 35
Are we going to do
I'm going to switch to my laptop leaving a code on your finger what are we doing
Yeah we didn't plan to be doing is coming up with a plan
What you would do with Farrell
Check the config file because
Camel Lights
Jason
Calibre can you put me into the UFC on five
Hey stop
Play also
Remove the star star star
Dad
Also bring up chat so it's kind of like down there
I'll pop down to chat
Think I don't really need to close it
Yeah I actually I want a mouse Now is very strange
92 Darcy ga
Oh yes that looks really clear for me
Put a chat one another
Actually be broadcasting the Chad
Play Kristoff
They looks great
Collecting that is fine so the one thing I really want
I wanted to try to bring Davids
Will my household things that I didn't try to find a white houses and then I want to go Paul
That data that can figure out where the object is based on the Lighthouse
On and then find it but there is a funny thing that happened when we were
I think was livestream 3 where Allen YouTube was like ok now thank you adopt someone Lighthouse
Between the two houses and then finally just now
Not a good idea how many months to finally realise like oh the right
You just figure out the right pose from each lighthouse in the news that you resolved the position
You guys for ride the whole time
I'm hoping that she's that but something
Realise like the least there wasn't that much that was wasted on it
So how is your dumb
Ok so for you
I don't have the configuration file sizes
When is it
Programme
Turn the volume to do that
Question
It wasn't raining just because it was crashing so bad are you are you Googling that
You guys new the entire time that's the best way to do this was to find
Beyond the poses for Three Steps to each lighthouse and then figure out where you are relative to that rather than trial
Between the lighthouses
Now we still need to figure out the positions for lighthouses but the way would you actually solve the problem
Planning on
Even close it
Where did you put the stuff
Survive ex
I'm guessing you develop your tyre algorithm around the idea of having one and then you have to like oh my gosh cool now we can
Turn a better idea as to where everything is
32 are pretty sweet I'm still for
I stuck in Sealand because I'm Charles and I don't really like Arduino
Where does it
Call the make it
Sea
Survival
Survive where do I get the stuff out of context
Nctx
To the enemy
I think it actually wait until there's a problem with it running
First policy to actually be there
Turn on
It's inside that's ok
They've closed
Cube Bolton
Wonder
And then survived
Fantastic
How much to say
W e l l put a file
Ok that's a reasonable file
Thanks you are that's by can you write that into the configure she or the HTC
5 issue thing
250ml to steal too slow
297 is what we need to sort some point it was like
Old turn it on
Do you want to turn on the turn on and make sure there's at least right now make sure there's no point on the
In between houses
You're putting one on like
Turn off
It's still like getting a try moving what is that
Rotating rabbit
Is going to have a point today
Collecting the data
Is it going to change the way that works
It's just go away now
I've never read the book learning C The Hard Way I don't know
Fpga for a while
Why would you need nappy ga-fc and I'm being facetious fpga is a perfectly cromulent solution
Closer is the name of the configuration volume
I've never seen that something must be wrong
Houses
I don't understand I've never seen this
It says that is accurate to within
What's a micrometre
See it
Is it actually it is micro 10 - 6
No I haven't how
Mypos reclaims to the
Logie normally mypos or comes to like
3 mm
Bye
Continue layers for something
You have the last there's a really funny thing
Here this week I was working through
B&Q to check that
Ok so
The longest time over months now we've been trying to feel like it's just not right
So close but something's wrong and what's wrong we don't know it's never able to resolve that well
I could not figure out the life me why my lighthouse poser was just not
Because it should be just mind bogglingly good
Show you a commit
Oh yes Iceland
There is in absolutely hilarious
Event that happened
It is
How do I actually know do I blame the file that works rate
What's the crazy thing was in Lynmouth dotsy
Surely there's a b in here
Play inland master.cf unction
And it was you guys are gonna laugh at me
Right here
What inverse magnitude so if this is used for is determining the inverse magnitude
Because you can calculate that and then you can x component lies by the particle contain Ian
Normalize the quaternions the problem was
That I wasn't taking the square root
So around everywhere else pays and somehow
Off this like kind of sort of work
Did actually like
I've never run I've never won the poser with this and it's perfect it's
Oh my gosh information I get with that do I get
Let's look at the never seen this before voice
Fossil cast
Expected to see
I don't know what's going on here
I really don't know what's going on here
What is this loaded the density map
I think this is wrong I think it's not accurate within 6 micrometres
I was so excited for a moment there
You know we can see you
You know what that means
Yeah ok inclusions
Data may be pointing tool
Tacular
So what's going on here is when you run it
Script outputs the the centre number
Which lighthouse in sweet number
Hideous and then gives you an angle in this
This is the angle
It tells you the angle from the angle from offset from centre of
The greatest show
Hypo in default does not really matter what type of guy
Yeah
CEF no it doesn't matter
You Ltd
UL
Everything you need to do there
What would you do
I didn't think about asking that well
Also completely preoccupied with trying to get him
Arsenal I'm trying to worry about getting a monitor
Figure out what was going on with them
In general in this room yeah that was pretty bad
On
Something else what does it think the Lighthouse
No it didn't even write those information
I'm saying I've never seen it right who's information
See how that works
Here this runs all the code
I feel like I should probably print out the values of everything in then run it against the date again
The results are
Yes you're right I'm not actually writing up post here right now
Alarm
Friend
Print0 variable print
Searching for very hard
Lighthouse Lighthouse 032
I'm Not Waving you internet
Wrong
Also the position for the live
Yeah
Don't move it out
Vehicle Street camera see what's going on
You're some I'm going to show them where all of the lighthouses are offended anymore
Is pointing forward 24-hours at my house up there
The Lighthouse
Please put the lighthouse on ceiling
Reflections off the wall
Ok
I don't know what I'm looking at it has a number that's really loud
Power to stop
Play
First one is just which is
How to basic food on how to cook
Did Kinder see the infrared but it wasn't like a really good infrared camera
Again the saying
That's definitely what we need northern soul was going on
Search really small
Guest p
I forgot how the messy
Fastest movie joke in college we needed to determine the pitch of something and
Stayed up really late
And
When we were done I had her when I was done it I had a piece of code that could tell the frequency of something
Open in Visual Basic
And it had online that down stopping down and it was pitch but we don't know how it works and somehow
Turn around
Peaks that were correct
Ok so us to target HMV points Whitehouse pass
Put the honour of the computer in the bottom of Thomas Barnardo
No
Go as the YouTube video on it
It's not for today
Anyway
To the Gang
Knights
Cast up to the wrong thing
Lighthouse quiet race you now
Why ask what is our current destination
Ok so what is cold here does is it takes a ratio
So here
This cold right here create a
Vector
Creating normalized vector
Are pretending that you are inside the White House in your shooting a rail at whatever angle
That was that actually shout out so it says that you were shooting at like 2 degrees this way in 5 degrees
On
A create a vector in 3D space is that then it rotates the Lighthouse or round whichever
And then it off said by worker thinks the Lighthouse is and then it takes
Can you find the distance between that line and the point that it should be heading on the hmg and
Cross product without the distance between it's like a wine point difference
Racing point line distance line defined by Lighthouse parts
Fraction ratio and then it tells us quite off from that line it is
Bad wolf from r
Blind Justice
What is it say here it says a bunch of crazy stuff
One of the easiest software used for 3D
Cross price
3D
There is an ex right there
So cross product of us the target in the ratio down
Heater
Why
Remember why
Released
Ice realise solide √ 6 micrometres
Which is like bigger
What's the square he taken out square root
A square
Pretty good 1.9 ml
What's the transfer of a volcano
What's going on
What was modified 3 minutes ago
Weird
20811 house
What's the answer that thing first
Hopefully this will work well
That's really good color
Actually yeah
Adult binding Bristol
Computer hardware
7-years old
Sorry now I'm trying to figure out if my my pose
Which is a really slow post fight
9 and 10
Ok with this
Away it's the magnitude
Internal combustion
Take a look at this data now
What was the last time is worth
I don't know
I don't want to start going back and looking for version history
Yeah that's fine
Maybe I'm supposed to be
X Factor
I also used to be normalizing that return in here
Probably do that
And a half sleep
You know what I've done
Where am I sitting that then
Actually
I know very well 1111 is SE14
Union 1000
30-seconds
1 to 12
.5
And the other one was 9
B a b y in 99
5 x 12 / 39
Sunday security
Oh my gosh
That's not the identity that's just a random one sound effect any
Anyway I still want
Stata normalise thank you
Yeah we did in mercury to also had that bothered by the way
The bird riding have the magnitude figured out right or whatever
That's why I don't want that
The Night game engine rawangi
5 years there is a bug in a library file
A very very long time
Quiet sounds like a fruit
Put these somewhere else Mr screen to get some how to do it
We actually don't use matrices here right now or using onions
Easier to do math with even though matrices are faster when you get
Like if you have a matrix need to rotate .5 that's fast and you need to rotate
You're right I do need a kumquat
It does need to be square
I'm thinking that those changes to the quaternium library and cause liver problems
Play the changes correct
Euro to zloty
Turn off Reedus
That's what I do if I take an arbitrary or oil there
And I generally from the boiler rotation and I convert that to a matrix and
Generated from The Matrix and I converted into an oil vector and then I create a
And I rotate that point by the quaternium factor than by the way it's really neat and
Put around the first point and then I rotate that back by that
Italian the radiators so I'm thinking of operations in between
Hopefully pretty good
Arm maybe something on Spotify
What is the
Us
Plastic surgery
Yeah that looks more like it ok my thing may be bad but
The results are
Supposed to be 3.69
Search
Hey Ben just wondering
How close should we be able to tell her the how far is the lighthouses are they really are
Exactly
All of this is going to get turned into a poser
Posing system
No I actually wanted to do but then Jackson pointed out
And I had written 1111
And the problem is that 1111 Catania is not valid
Measure how far are you from
You really are you can measure how far your solution is from minimising Solaris
No I can measure how far is the White House is from
Bedroom light the distance between the Lighthouse
The actual distances of 2.92 m and 3.6 m
Anyway
Elytra diastolic on this is not a valid
I'm in that doesn't do any read rotation is a 100
Onion where I get Steven a0001 cottonian or
That could be above library to
What is msdn
Alarm definition
The same order
Ok Google
Because if we was 0 it doesn't matter if you have like an episode 1
I think all the matters is
Yeah I think
But if if we is 0 then you have an identity Catania no matter what is well
Right
So like sorry TW10
Can't make any rotation motion
X5uw email manage Microsoft
I don't believe you I'm going to test
What's create a new guitar
Not that I have any reason not to believe you
I just learn something new
Is your party victory handle input
Not sure
Don't you mean like I can say
Onions is that what I thought it was
Plants of the new everyday
Can you repeat the same as the input
Why
Play Rotate the doctor is it actually copies it anyway so the input can be the same as
Back to work work work
On your phone
Oh my god people are riding they're all over the place
3:00
Yeah he need like 297 mHz
Turn guys
When is got to make a board that can do this
Ben I definitely think that that is the same way a lot of people on the Wikipedia page for
Think about it
That is all kind of messed up
That's the probability cloud from where the other lighthouse could be
Which lighthouse is there my house number 11
No
As one that would be
It's the one that says see
Do you want to come out just to see if it actually is it
A really good point
That's really close to one of the lighthouses
Close to that one
Oh hey David David Chapman came up with a
Play good so I want to get my working for the calibrate
David Chapman came up with a poser that can compose a system even though it's not perfect but
Composed in about 1.6 microseconds that's micro
Little you
Night light
Little us are so I really want to try to get that in today
David art by Dr David Chapman sorry
There's so much stuff is going on in the technology is getting so head of Us right now and we don't even have a second monitor so Josh is
Free of charge can do
I don't
I don't want
Benner saying a lot of very interesting things
I want
Live chat
No the live chats are not saved
Encourage people to read the things that then it's saying
It is
That's White House wine
Take a look and see what the date is coming off Inverness
Survive survive from or resistive
My effective wallpaper problem
I'm yo we need to do
Somebody else is on their setup
Turn off Darren in livestream have access to a on
Have access to a set up with a by and white survive so you can just runs against it
You're getting this really weird data
Don't be really
Really nice and helpful
On
If you guys can just anybody else can run this
Really appreciate it
Another 5 hours just in case
Actually interesting thing Josh is going to be buying this in once we find something disastrously wrong with it I've already
Play Mike order for a second vaidisova Josh so
Something about his basement
What time
Bluetooth
Blue lights on
Ok so first thing's first but we actually have to do
What is the actually have to convert Dave's code
Do not disturb my code into a opposer
Set
Poser
I'm not going to say anything
Play I'm you on I cannot accept anything from the wife but I will accept full scene data
I can go hopefully copy and paste this pretty much Hulse
Upstairs
Trash is there seriously nobody you can text to get another wrong again
Is there a best buy nearby
Bestbuy.com
What's a see how much monitor is we might just go by Martin
Video
I love meatballs but you have to make sure the sauce doesn't have
And make sure the Vinegar like the meatballs are you making yourself it's fine if you get them made
Yeah no beginning
A cheapest possible monitor
We just need something for Josh to use acres
Radio 2
Play store pickup Lexington Park toilets
Can you install getting accent in Chrome
Is it not Lexington Park is there another one closer
It is the Lexington Park 1
How do I tell best buy that I I wanted
What was Wonder in stock in stock
Pick up today
50-99
I don't care about much I might buy it
1500 by 900 are you ok with not having hard
So in here poser bouchara
Yes that's it
You can see what you're doing to other than that
There is one
Nobody's a fire marshal write
Ok suppose you're 14 data
Are you changed
I'll make sure
Everything works fine now
Is citric acid vinegar
Play twitch livestream this is number
No do I say in the title
What lifestream number is this guys
Whatever from the
Live stream
Ok go for it
Does it mean to buy into
I didn't bring my watch
Tell you why you don't actually need that that chat
It's like a survive calendar
Src bad cold outside
Stop playing
Online
Yeah
Bathroom
You need to get stage 4
Directions to have sensor on a Russian
Play the priest
Just trying to get into flower forward
Useless Carol
Weird
Underscores disappear
It shouldn't it's all 5 times it does the new 5 times
Richard say good or something
How to make a turtle advanced
Ok I don't know what to do with there I know they can be done
Alba age
And that's not
It's going to be
Replace all that
Cheltenham
Story
Forgotten which way the stages go for the calibration
5 Cal data into
Staying here
Skip stage 3 or 7
Play some stage that you have to collect 1024 date
Turn on timer
Goodnight
Download
Good night cleaning your face
Anytime
Poses / survive
Tell know how is your
In with
I will compile
Charles that c95
The Lion King
Yeah it was a typo
What's
Vauxhall plastic plastic
Yep
Nearby ok you're something
If you was looks interesting I will be up for arm
Vnc
Turn off the lights
So how does that work
Bin calendar
David 68
Look in your calendar folder
GL2 9RU
You have to type in 32/64 to 432 and then you can move it
The size of what is expecting
So disposal function run after work on the way that works
Lighthouse
I'll take a look in a second
Bending over
Whatever it is
You actually should be able to get it to work
Windows what what exactly was missing I can't remember all the details
Include on a generic is part of the core bills so we don't end up using things like you sleep in German
JJ 1110100 if you can see what what
What's causing windows to need unistd Dulwich just come get you nicely that agency if it goes
Thank you for compiling it for Windows
Is necessary stopping Sadness
Play Capital
No I don't want to do by Lighthouse
I don't know the rest of the network to 168
Ok am I going to scale that's because your screen is way big
That is superheroes
Close it right now
Else
On the A12
That's a good point so live USB in Windows requires you
Play have an answer that you can you can kind of get away with that you can use live USB generator fake driver
It has
Make it less than 720 by 12 / 70
Plastic bottle
Turn the screen off the windows
Are you going to change resolution
What am I supposed to do
The forest 61
It's ok so what
See you on the same window
Probably fine try changing your control
Howard said the clear to-220 and the your pics too
Ok maybe make the opaque 240
Ok that's not that bad
Steve Chapman
Alex Green
Which one is that
Where are the one
Oh yeah but yeah you wanted narrow it down tighten up
Aren't you
Oh yeah windows subsystem for Linux
How to get like live USB working on this for windows that would be super swanky
When I move you off to the right Josh
Ok
Play you're not going to rain again
So I need to be here
My code
Is that really
Available
I think so
The big thing is the angle has to be
Play the same
You're out of you do you want
We have to be sitting next to each other on the floor so you're going to run it out run it
Running this one
Houses going to work I remove fat from my build
Hopefully I didn't break do a boy
Now give me Gimme minute
I want to blow away
I don't want to search I want to know the way
Yeah there's no the different even there anyway
Play
Ok now I'm going
Can I bring up yours so we can watch them at the same time
Ok
I don't know what causes the distribution might
Alright
4 cm in 5 cm into polyfine
Ok that's not that bad
That's pretty terrible that's very terrible
Is that one of yours
What's 0
How much you have a database
Can you shrink your window significantly
I think you have to start clearing 0
Song
Yeah I know
Epicentre
214 180
I just paid my matches though it's interesting that they
They are different load one
Yeah
Now
It's concerning
It's ok
Opera restriction make it like 200 and 250
That's really wrong to 15200 sorry
That's just absolutely wrong because the angle and that will have to be pretty Ste
Very shallow
You know what
I just realise we Cameron David Chaplin's orthosole Gonna Let Me Go try to do that
Hey David are you still in chat
Farm
Feel the copy HMV points in
TV normally into Dave here
How do I enter a date Stata
Hi hi David
Multipliers ok
I don't know I think I have it now I just couldn't figure out if I got to run your thing against existing data so
Premier
Diagraph this again
Hey that looks interesting
Matt Grey
That's one of the lighthouses from this point of view
Grande thing with the other Lighthouse
The problem is my broadcast to hold desktop and the screen resolution is much higher
So it it makes it hard and it also uses up more bandwidth so
Make my defined solve into my Galaxy
Lara points visible
That was even
Search lighthouse €2 that would BBB would be the one of the time visible according to this
C a one says boy
Play houses
That is rough
I can do
Play Rangers
Equine
Visible
I'm getting really close to just dumping my mine altogether because if his thing comes up with the better
The mind then it's just pointless
Minimum
Reasonable
A headset headset so what we actually see here is the
Expected anchor sorry the bluedot
The actual positions be received by the by the headset from Royal lighthouse thanks all the end
Star and
Irish Rotary the red dots or where David
The rhythm thinks they should be based on his matrix for what he thinks is the
Update the whatever is of the White House the White House
Sing pickups fearful David Chapman do you want to
Turn the battery
Play me a number song
Tell me everybody
I'll let you know
Click the phone button
That would you can get your fine so
Add David Chapman where is
3.1 m and
Lighthouse sea
Is 3.58 a real life
Hey David Cameron you care if we call you in then you can talk live
Actually we could Jack him into the computer
The headphone jack
You have a headphone jack year
45 cable
Measure of the
Where's the tape measure
Do you have a measure
Couch
Putting on the couch esino tape measure
Christine 3-year she just
Quiet
Spell
Go away
10 inches
1 years
10-piece
Is
Set 3.59 close to 3.64
And
David Chapman just friend
Say David Chapman can we call you
So he says
Harsh or I think he said sure
Ok
You said ok ok will call you right now
I'm going to
I'm going to see if I can call you in my phone
Still there
Hold on I'm going to just make him I have two audio sources
Give me a second Dave
What no what
I don't even have
How have audio
Carolina volume
Play gm20 for a girl
HDMI
That's really going to sound
Jimmy USB audio
Finglas
How to use that sorry Dave hold on
Oh yeah we never rains code against the other one
Switch off by 3 cm and off
That's pretty good for a z in fact I would say that is within our measurement error so
I'm going to do right now is completely abandoned trying to port my code over to this and
Story about 14-days code in for right now we'll just call a good enough
Is there as level
Yes my name is label
I need a place I can
Drivers
Identified it
There's a lot of value that might be so sad
Idea secondary device
Play say something
Play speak in Birmingham
So Dave I have no way of hearing you
Whatever you say your wife
In the night don't know what you're saying
Oh really I haven't said anything yet and anybody hear me
On
Ok
I think you might be good now
Anyone yummy
Dave
C3 get the sky
Yeah I can hear myself on the shelf ok so
Ok this is better
Chelsea
This
Here
David can you say some
Sounds really hard to hear
No David David you're going in and out hold on
Hold on David
I know he can serious
Beyond Skyrim
Ok you're really
It's really watery David
Ok you can turn off your microphone I can't turn you down
David
Ok
Ok almost perfect
The code that I wrote it
Assumes an orthographic projection or an axonometric projection
Stool for a poo
So it would be really cool if you brought up my Wikipedia page that talks about the X Factor
Really funny pictures of some paintings that you can make a nose
Apology the basically I am assuming that
The screen space
Point the point that you see
Inner corner system of the Lighthouse
But those points are some non-linear functions of the points that you have
The offset
Overhead mountain
I've had the headlines today
From the device
But then it is clearly just the approximation and the reason for that is because it's really hard
Tell the difference between one and address is getting smaller because
Verses when it's getting smaller because you're moving it on for the returner away
The idea that moving an object further away from the camera
Looks a lot like making it smaller
Mean that we don't really have to tell the difference
That
When you get smaller because it's too early which isn't reasonable but just make sure it's ok
Girl by the sea
So then how far away from the camera does it have to be
Any chance
That
If you want to figure out
What the poses
Allowed to change in the paper what you do if you drop
Hold on a second pull up some of the stuff
I found a while back a picture on animated gif on YouTube
After that I think really help
What's the picture of the house do you remember where that is
I have remembered that there was something on and Wikipedia and I forget which Wikipedia page was one that
The difference between
A projection where you divide by the equal linear projection
And some of these
Axonometric projection
Ok you've had it is the picture of the house were they
Be kind of show with the two different extremes
Yeah so that picture that you see
Dictionary
That you see as the house
Really
It shows that there is some dick
Particularly when it's really close
The further away you move from the camera left at different
And even though there is some different it can still pick you up about patient more or less
Even if your sumalatha graphics
Project
Terrible
But it's basically
The approximation is basically where you
I have a 2D sheet of paper
I'm going to try to realise that aren't orthogonal I'm going to call 1X 1y and onesie
And then I'm going to say ok that's what it is
Ok now move it back in 3D space and figure out
How far away I have to be for that too
That's basically what it does and it's really really really fast
So if it's good enough
If nothing else it could be
A starting point for an initial guess
Iterative
A very good initial guess but it might be good enough so
I will what will you need help
I think there were a couple of cases were the best
Disability team Aprilia Walsall
How good is
Yeah that's what it go
So I guess my summary on this would be
Generally taken from
Is
If a point is closer to the camera
A small amount of emotion with cause in large emotion
From the perspective of the camera
And I use lighthouse in camarillo
Like mixed
Yeah sorry
That makes sense when you get closer and closer to the camera
Looks like I'm large and motion to the camera
What happens is different points and the head-mounted the head man is like right next to the Lighthouse
Pretty much the worst case
The Z co-ordinate for the best for some of the points on the head map display
Are different than the Z coordinates for the other one
Assume that was lead position for all of them is pretty close together
We're it doesn't make very much if the difference in terms of the perspective divide
Then it should be alright
Sorry just clarify when he says
What is actually talking about in this case is the disease from the perspective of the camera with z
Out of the screen
So
If you have a home match
Here
If you have gone from your point of view
Some point very close up here
Like this
And some point like that so very close and very far
In this approximation works out very poorly
If most points show up in kind of the same plane
Then
The approximation Works much better
And that's because the difference between things being closing fire and how that size change
Really kind of
Doesn't matter if there points are kind of all McFly
Are you saying all the same Z points
You saying
The distance from the can
Yeah I think that's really good if there any other questions about
We pretty much take a picture then you know it's a 3D dry
Etihad A380 painting
And but you have it drawn on a 2D page
Then you you take the you drop down there that's the origin
And then you draw line and say that
This is the right direction and this is the forward Direction and you dropped me line you say that
That's what it is
Well we know that there's no way
Three Lines
Intu Derby
That actually map to the three lines and comedian
But we're going to do it anyway
And it's actually not too bad
And the funny thing about this project
It said it's been around for about 400 years
In the artist red original
Originated in China
I'm still
McCann I guess say that is the cheap Chinese way of doing it
And that's it a little bit
Making a joke everybody finds
Aberdare
Yeah it is
Is the originated in China about 100 years years ago
End
Is there a really interesting paintings
With some impossible drawings
Drawing where you have a staircase that leads around on its
I am repeating
There are some really interesting corner cases
Where does projection
I can do something to don't make any sense
What's mean about an architectural drawing
And it
Good enough that if you draw something in that projection
You better a person looking at a picture to look at it and say ok I can see what this is
I thought not bad but you know I think for the
Make the invoice Prague
Figuring out what the object is giving the teacher
Elijah
Are they trying to stop The Fall
Play together
The approach
If it's good enough I'm hoping
If I do
Application
What are the stars
That weekend try to Italy
Come up with an even better
I think that
That could potentially
I'll be very good approaches we have a really good initial guess Lynn there are
Message
The try to
Atomising function
Ok
I tried writing that but some told that after miserly or function
But I wasn't using Lagrange multipliers
And I was starting from
The identity
Doctor so I didn't have an initial guess and it's ok really what is 2 million iteration
So hopefully it will start with an angel it's really close today
Van Damme
The next step
From this
Start using the starting point
And then we're fine
Yes
And just to clarify I don't know if you saw the results Dave
On but I can period so these points that are on the screen that I have operate now the blue points are the
Absolute
The red RV
Arm
If we use his gas
No we need A299
If we start with his point as a gas
This is just
And then we create a quaternions and position rotation so pose out of his
Calculator
Then
This is the results we get
Batteries
So right now I think what I want to do especially considering he get on much better answer for the disk
Lighthouse tonight
I think that you really want
Completely dish
The Charles
White House
I think for the rest of time here
I think I'm going to focus I'm trying to get Dave's code
Into a pose finding situation with life survive
In order to use it in the rest of the cyst
Fingers crossed everything goes well today
We might actually get your ID your stuff in in test
Sound good
Sounds good
Ok I'll keep working Emerald ranch multipliers
The I'm sure it'll be good to have it is
Salou
Rocky boxing and then but I can finish them
How many seconds are in
Yeah
Annoying
Ok well thanks I guess we'll get moving around here
Taxi
Wake me up at 5-minutes
Oh yeah you're right there will be an echo
Ok that's all
A good view
Sure is a fine view
People do we have right now in stream
Fig
Here
So everyone time for us to just ditch my thing on the floor in Friday implement
You're using Dave's code
Silver going to be
I think you can do if you are
Is trying to figure out
I want to find a way of
Looking at the code
Is coming out
Distance
Alexa
I don't know why
I think so
Turn it down
Is
You like I am us twisted the resolution divide was a little bit lower
Quiet
I will
Reduce the volume
Typing value
Hello
Hello can you hear me now
Fighting ok
Sorry
Turn it up so that
Hello hello
Early morning me
Survive underscore
EDC la pack
Dcl lecac in the league
Folder
So Dave Road is only your mouth library that's what Sheila Packers
Thomas based off of the idea of normal apocalypse by you know
Flashes of White
Yeah
Off main Screwfix
So I'll talk about what's on your screen right now for a second
Can you move your window all the way to the left
To move your
You're saying it's stuck
Overlapped
Ok so the box formation it's making that's fine
The problem is when we have lights they're like all the way up to one side or the other
Like if you can leave the window bigger sale
Step
What just happened
No that formation is ok
What when you have point satellite office
That's probably fair
Happens were the other Lighthouse
Yeah I know it just jumped
What is going on there
I don't know why
I look for both
All the thing everything that I have a light bulb what does this mean
Ok every now and then randomly does
What's good to me really good to me
What are the other
Area of terrible
When using the voice that something other than 90 MB refresh rate in it just would not
Mikey B
Play Gaelic betway
Basically said it's all one of the points in the middle of the sea for one of them
Skip
I'm good right now
Ok go for it
I'm not going this afternoon
I'm going to go hydro window again
Who is Maxine that is blinding
I can go for it
Stop
Oh my God what's going on
It's freaking out
Now it's fine now
Can you move along the back as I can see it very
Just did it again
Totally wrong
Freaking out
What is going on
Now
Stanley freaking out
Yo what is what
Ok it's definitely consistently broken
Did you see it to produce like a diagonal line
I wish I was wrong with this
At least consistent
Turn off
Do you mind working
Did she eat food my work
We have tried playing real live games and it's totally does Twitch app
Music
Reminders
Turn on
On your computer
Sure but I can't because I can't really do much right now
Add
JJ
Yeah I said that we had tried playing it still liked witching hour
What's waking I think that means like trying to run it a lower res
Iran
Oh no it's blanking so what it is is there is like a garden area around the actual
Like this like that the actual screen size is bigger than the visible screen size
And reduced blanking I think is when you take that and you start pulling that down
So that like you just have left texels that are being sent that are 10 in the blanking periods
The blanking period as when like is when there is no data currently no visible data currently being sent
Figure something out if I have a font size smaller
Why was there be a sensory name
55 to feet
4:35 55 is
Ok
I don't know why they chose to do this with the five but for some reason when they sent data
Can send flights
That's not actually populated with real data
As far as I can gather when you get a tooth teeth ITV 5 and there's nothing there
Play this is non dealer
Play spring it up
Yeah
Turn it up
I don't think so the reason I think it's because normally that time staying
Matches that of a previous packet
So it looks like you're using the same buffer to keep sending the data
But then the alarm
Putting the like say Hey by the way this actually isn't a valid packet
Hey Dr Chapman I don't know if you still listening but you really should be taking on the
The normals
That's really important
The normals will let you quickly weed out any complete nonsense
Suspicious what about
55 ways
I don't know that for a fact by the way this is just a bunch of gases that you're in charge
Joshua
My alarm
It doesn't matter
How long does it take
What does x for rap
Whatever to the 32/48 millionaires
Sex
Two 32/49 seconds
You want start at Smyth's wants to know what HDMI version you have on your laptop
I don't know that
Set a 9.478 seconds
Maschine problems
He says do xrandr space dash for Bose
It's hard to believe the date has all this code in all of that runs in 1.6
Scream
How long is Chapman
Dr
TV shopping is your mum doctor to I can't remember I think she got it right
Thomas Morris right now up on screen years David sorry is Josh's
HDMI stuff where do you find out the version from this
My controller song
Intuit
Maybe
Thomas Morris to give you everything you need
Thomas Morris is no longer here
How he says device plugged in
Ok I'll bring it back up ok
Call down song
Thomas Morris Sawtry looking
Set alarm Batu number dimensions
Operating a 225 mHz
Atvi
Terribly figs
Can you turn it up
How do you have so many pixels on your screen
Oh I have keep scrolling over because the right side of your screen is divide
Your screen is 4080 by 1200
The 05 he says it's version 1.3 or higher
How do I have you minimise until you tell me I can
Turn on TV
Which is to be fair my dad
I am not to be trusted
That would make sense OK
A * 3 +
It doesn't come in before this invigorator
Time is it
What is that you went 32
The time
That's just the fairy TV in Pokémon the headset
I can't stop staring at lights
You're a white dealer Kia imu data
On
Set timer
What's the time
The IMDb only you
Because he
Oh yes that's also possible because
It tells you when a light is Erwin etc is no longer illuminated
Top 1 sensor gets illuminated
Then another sensor get eliminated
The first one turns off
First one gets eliminated second one gets eliminated
Yeah no one turns off then first one turns off
Is the start time of the second monitor off was before the start of the second hand
Number
Play How big more than
Oh that's weird
No
Italian
Also
Check to make sure it's not an invalid data point
1.8 look at the ID and the satellite and all of that
NG14
What's the central time
Compiled
So you think you have valid data that's coming in that radically out of order
Play open up your screen again
Turn on the lights
I could leave it at hops around sun but it shouldn't have around a whole why
X 10
Roundup
Log into some fireworks
They are
If you think it's crazy one
Play frozen some distance away
Or timer something
Another 10 minutes
A little scared
Somebody else going on much more complicated one but I couldn't get into work right so I'll end up just abandoning it
Jack of just loaded o
I get it now like survive
Phone
Turn lamps off please
Turn off dining room
Sandra are you into a programming as this is a random you happen to stumble
Thing
How is the age
Object survival fake contacts
Survive cow
How did you decide on the car
Which ones
Play Halloween 80077
So if centres 200200
And
Centre and you can only go so far to one side or the other
Sandra have you ever heard of an HTC vive a right now trying to
Basically code that same sort of thing
I like the software that runs on a computer for it but in hopes that will be able to develop her own hardware that we can
Use with basically the same sort of tracking systems that the HTC vive
Muses
Lights lights off
At the end of the line
Apple opening screen
Let me know can even open it
Ok
What am I looking at
He said it
I would describe four words used
So
Now
Broken
850k
Not using that function anymore
Map
The Casting CD error
Forecasting
80 x 8
I don't think so because it is so drastically wrong when it's wrong
Tod activator with a slight changes
Yes
The otfc only just seen your video on it
Ok
And by the way I don't want to do that when you get there that would be super cool
Looks like it's a lot of travelling in Berlin
Steam Gala so we have that data from the existing data
Play
Override
Yes
Sometimes because displaying beer
Lighthouses on the same screen
If it's a update the apps from that lighthouse on giving sensor and away from that Lighthouse
Stop saying Santa
Displayed over here
So uses this lighthouse is that in this lighthouses why
The wrong lighthouse into a displays in the Wild Place
That would be in calibrate dotsy because right now I'm using this
That's just for the user presentation
It's just trying to music
Mulberry.com that up
I just throw out which light outside is probably the wrong way to do it
Ok
For the people in that
That's just a random yeah that's it
No no it's actually for the data when it's getting the data from that level up the program
Looking calibrator seeing the call back
Celebration
Yes I think I think that's it
Australia
Downlight
I don't know
Crawley Camino
Light blue
Now
Mum said the 0 Moran is because
It makes it so it's like homogeneous with this because I will have to add one in this case I will won't have to add one
I want to Mark off the debts actually can't like yourself no to that's going to be
This is access your own data access one
Multidimensional array
It here
Morning
Version of heads
That's ok I can get the data
Calibrate
So we used to require a Watchmen thing
Common point on a watchman but we don't really operate that way anymore
Doing it this way just obliterates
Can you set an alarm as done
Yo really would be nice if the things didn't keep flickering I really don't like that
My house
Stop
What do you mean by Thomas
Thomas
Goal is to get the thing itself to be able the process that I have stayed with peanuts
St. Paul
Go away
It's just two days working on this
What is the app that
What are you are
What's confusing
Confused about
I don't know either
Because it's the White House Whitehouse Bureau scared out
That I do understand
Yes
Complete before it starts
B it updates the position of the point in tax
This lighthouse this frame
They renders
So because this one just moved it this now we have this lighthouses ass
But we don't yet have this house is why
Rendering
Yes correct
So the idea that we should be using is store the pixel data
Is a bigger a red glasses big
2 months since I wrote that code
Stage 4 succeeded but it didn't run Dave's code
To do that
Fingers crossed
Are we done we can go it never you're ready by
So what is working on right now you know some of those lights are flickering
It's because we're overriding the data whilst being displayed
What we really should be doing is making it so that it's stored in two separate so will be able to get really clear picture
What dislike houses in this lighthouse is
Tell me the music policy
North Wales
Isolating the trenitalia
What is Dave saying say
Dave's coach says
Is Kodaline of crazy things
Do you use SDL from the debug window
No window
Ride Rise available
It's are completely OS independent runs on just about anything
You can even actually like
Browse by category and TV 66 you can you can use rather to do
3D rendering on
Potters is
Farm well
Is coming up with the answers 3.8 m
I guess ok
What's going on
Almost there Josh
Ride ride is very fast
You could use Ray tracing really like SDL light
It's just really small and you can just included your project and it's really geared operate on light
Peanuts
Latest free you just say hey rod rods play was bottom of the screen doesn't
But you got to put in the bathroom
Ok that's really bad why is everything not
Everything is not a number
Why is Dave's closed so broken
Actually also cool FM 1024
Play Motown
Pl
Stop playing going into Dave's code is Superbad I don't know what it is but it is time
Break
I'm sorry
But I'm going to go on a break now
Ok what's going on
Try running this
Code
Turn off the lamp
Open
Storm
How to makes you not like a sensor that would be visible from getting see when you
That are not in the two main things but they're on the same axis that means that's all that's coming from
Ok
Play add quick
5-minutes
Weather today
Actually
Play a song from Brendan because I'm actually allowed to do that
Indeed
So bad
Oh I need the stupid
Are you Nova upright Ford
Why is sound always so painful charged
Spensify girls
Yes no
Ok you guys get this for like 10 minutes
Looks like the timing workout
Which probably play Samsung Gear
Play Miss anything in chat
What is that
Play ad
Play nana Like Beckham
Have you guys the figure had a run the Bible that would be soon
Swanky
On the vibe on a pie
You know
What is causing your problem
Play charges having with the five
Is clear that something is reflecting off of something else
It's sofa flexing
I feel bad that Josh is spending $500 on a used 5 and
So annoying in his house
Brownout I'm doing I'm trying to just print out a bunch
Variables
On see what exact
Is going on
Why is Dave's code nanning all over the place
Using try to find the nan's
This particular revive I used in home when it for the week in the word
Glitches
That's pretty good
Excuse me
Trying to get these CO2 nut crash
Why is wine on
Dave
Protecting the variables
If you take a square root of something that's like almost exactly 0
Not quite zero break everywhere
Hello Dave's code
Livestreamer
How was
Do you want if you want a back that back out so you can see Josh and me it's probably best
Like all the way
Oh yes
Name It Up song
Mordaunt-Short
Back up some more
Ok Google now if you import starts then we'll be able to get to buy them to you
Ignore that
London E20
Yes
Barely looks good outside of that that's fine
I like Elvis basically also become like everybody there's a budget
Related
That we may end up a dressing like a few weeks down the line so like
Why can't it in for a Dacia way koda
Skip data access
Which function is it
Nazi
Function
No that's right
You can definitely tell which one it is from the a code
I think 2 and 3 is one of the lighthouses in 6 and 7 is the other Lighthouse
Yeah
Can you explain your reasoning on that
Set an alarm
My reasoning on that is that there are total of 8 different possible a codes
You see that 0 and 2 and 1 and 3 and 4 and 6 and 5 and 7
Are all the same things that means that's the data bit or the one bit is the database 10
0 and 2 and 1 and 3 ride to the x-axis in the y-axis of both
Accordingly and also write to the x-axis and 5 and 7 write to
Ayx at 3
Correct
News houses jump offset x 2 + 0 office time 2 + 1 John offset x 2.0
I think you should be times 4 plus 0 times 4 Plus 1 times 4 plus 2 times 20
No work too I really have to get out of bed
I really have to go through a code in like a bunch of places I used one dimension
Personal data
We really need to switch it over using multidimensional arrays have an iPad
Turn on the light on the sound down to one
Ok
What is
Sienna g10x that's work starts drawing text
Parent controls to text location
Why do we care
Location-based
Maybe it's not
Another reason behind it
Shopping list
It's no reason to do that Dave
Is it good
Screen
Occasion wear
That happens
From around
Oh so there is another thing that I do where I if you haven't gotten data from a sensor in a while it's
Is it to Black
Here is something close
Yeah that looks like
There's another girl that used to light time the day to help him to throw it away
By the way
If you can possibly I'll put with the pie that would be pretty cool
I'm disconnected from your screen
How to play sonne Grande's going twice now
Nearest stop to 189
Staying on box light
Strong
How are you know what can you wrote
The headset so it's 90 degrees is right now
Explain why it's probably much better to do that testing with
New Tyler set up the grass though
Why do you describe this
I don't know why it is sometimes his thing
Just make everything off to one side or the other
Whatever I'm going to go in 2-minutes staying in I'm going to go through to him that he can hopefully fix it
See you next Saturday love
7-years wrong
Exactly right
This 12.3
Not too bad
IKEA
That looks much better
Turn on the lights
They're actually pretty quotes
I can believe
Committed so that it doesn't confuse everybody as it is right now
I don't think you will make Square things around tomorrow
There is definitely some data points
What's like rain is ok they shouldn't like freak out your animal and they are sometimes
Start morning if your stationary is fine
Add points
Your problems my thing than anything
No it's all something there
Hear it
Moving around again
What's the terrible corner
Yeah
Hey stop
Stop go back a little bit
Ok
If we met that have a more reliably ok then we can find a source that can be it
Ok you're gonna
Which lighthouse is the one on the right
That one
Ok so let's try to get to 3 Callaghan
Something environmental to move around again again sometime
Drink alcohol
Do the things for rotating Rachel that seems to find it
Turn off light
Next song
34 off to the last song
Turn lamp
Stop go back song
Play look around
Down
Just find it somewhere else
Hey there
Next
Will I find out which
That was weird
Disappear
Turn off now
To get the stuff
Still going on
Happened
Maybe you're causing it
Incisors farting ok
Will go away
On our way from here
Genesis
What's going to come down
Turn on
Turn off
Starting dieting
What's this just be somebody this whole time but we never really paid that much attention to it so now
The square pants song
Ahmed
Changes
Direct contact with the director side B fine
How far is it to print centre number
You have to set the 10 X and Y and then you have to do cmfg drawer chest
Call Dave cook Goodenough
Alarm
I've not had a bit but I haven't
I should have to go from there
Play Netflix
Training 13823
Tell me too much I'm moving back son
Decided
Website
Sorry about it
How do you start work if you want to invert that hose
Really far is e
S
What
WhatsApp it's a quiet and a translation trying to figure out you have to move
Do I have to rotate the translation by the forward quote
That will be on
Translate translate
Yeah that thing
Why am I so bad as I have never got good at that
Somebody trying to do
I have a position
Oven
Of the White House relative to the object
And the orientation of said Lighthouse
Orientation
Position is like very big Anna wise
Where the object is relative to buy house
NHS
Somebody's actually installing a minimal on a pipe
It's so hard to think about
That's going to be a very large why
Selby from the lighthouses point of view
Where the object is
I'm trying to determine
The pose of the object
Daesung
The lighthouses point of view
So that might actually just be here
Yeah
I think that's actually I think we can do that
Coronavirus
Tell something about yourself
So
That's the final
So do that
The Matrix holes
X y and z
Is actually going to give exactly what we want
Get the position and orientation of the camera
Misinformation
Carried interest
So that's definitely
Add position from the cameras point of view
Is that right
82.7
Around
And get this done
That information I can go back I can stop it in the object
Which direction
Travian by 10:30 then
Another hour
See I have survived Close from my house close
Positioning rotation of something
It's a different thing than like a transformation
Used to be under 50 Nations because it can only effect rotation and position and nothing else
You can't steer
UK
Paston Road
What's the time
What's the end result will be today if we can get this to work
Able to move the thing around the room and it will tell us in 3D space
Where are the battle I have sisters and would that like aspects
Play right now if that you can figure that the origin
Yes and then we pick it up and we moving around we see if those things are anywhere close to Somewhere
Great thing
Yeah that happened
Position
Ok so
Timer light out and divisor and looking up right now
I'm up
I want to know the position in rotation that might
Ratatouille
I have to rotate that vector from lighthouse to me
Why is that one way and will try to
This way
It's worth just doing I'll make a note though that we might have to swap so
Navigation
Translate
Play sleepy soft
The rotation of the inverted rotation
P3
Not doing anything
Do you know we're doing either
Paul Martin so what we have is we we
Now have a pose pose information
Of where the adjective is relative to
Lighthouse lady
The translation is almost always my the actors in frontal Lighthouse
Where is the object relative to Lighthouse
But we want to find out where the White House itself is related to the heart
So this is partly configuration
Stage on
Search for operating on
Ok
Scrap on diesel by 1
I didn't say that
We will basically pretended right now
Survive
PlayStation has a pose
Call CeX in Harrow
Function is entirely too long
Saying I need to text
What is the address of it charge
Upset and doing more
Ok
Write lhp from the members of
HP error
50l half
From La Roche
Are we due from LHR pass and now I'm gonna take it from
Ro0 x equals negative
Around
It's also made
When did forget
What's the biggest soda first cow will do this
This really offer and I
First Capital Connect
Not not
Ok rotation of
Relative to Dad's did the rotation care about that right positions and headset
What is the first car to do with anything
What is this for
Not first cow
Alright so the first time you calibrate expecting to be face up
But there's every time after I'm a pretty things
That to something else somewhere
Did you see you first
Kick off
Initialiser to
Derp
Episode 20 at some point
Time
So now what we do is I want to
Position in 3D space
From the lighthouses point of view
Position
Havana
Moving on
TV air her magic star
I don't think that's true
Not soon enough
I want to rotate
Position by on lighthouses
Orient Aviation
That to a new position
Every time
Don't think so
Everybody happy with that
Moving on
Ok there is no way this is gonna work what I do wrong ok
Problems
Put some more properties around
Maybe
Bad guys re
Will try and both ways I will try
Thank you Josh I will trust you and if you let me down
Serious problems at work
Off
Ok
Connect Four
Getting closer 513 + 1
Ok let's collect some data and see what it proves out
I think Josh is wrong
It should be printing the stuff it's not
Outside
No will do the file
Anita Slater
Ok
What's going on why is it not printing
Maybe if you wasn't wrong
First car
You know what
Skip it
Ok let's try this
They are different
Barnes
True
Ok
Take like 2-weeks just like clean up
Zeros where are they all zeros
Age 46
Volume
While light
Call Mamas
I don't know
Ok
Oh you know what there's a really good test for this if we run this
And it worked
It should say that the object is back at the Warwickshire
To see this and if he'll put his back if you are which is absolutely now
Then is perfect but it's not ok so
This rotation first
By the way Great Chart
Older people just wrong
Difference Ethos Plus
Add store on that still wrong
What is a do in Seaforth fast I can't remember
That looks interesting
Really good
Position
Can you trade a tilted on the street up and down
And oriented so that the white house is like that one
Can you check one off
What is the temperature
Volume to two
Like in the middle cancel it is oriented to this pop is pointed towards one
90 degrees but move it has physically in between the two
Close
I'm trying to oriented so that it's almost read up and dance
Next Spotify
Ok right now call there's some point in it
Can't actually can be useful
No I'm still writing the everything's fine nevermind
Call me back
Ok
That's with the matrices are
Really does look but it's not believable
The position on the lighthouses point of view
I want to get this tonight at 4
Fortunately
Very good wine
I forgot to do
Family
Lhp ok
OK girl
Where is like 8 things that could be reversed I don't know what they are
I think everything's there now if we just keep reversing things on be fine
That's tough one
What are these things that's gonna work
Just got to try and because I'm too tired to figure out which it actually should be
Alarm
Lights on
How to get from the lighthouses point of view
So we're starting with the internet
Turn off the lamp
Something people can see you
Restarting with that way
I am the Lighthouse in
Why
Why goes into me
He goes into me
David
Why did you have to make wife forward
How to transform from that
Yeah he's using wires death
A right-handed coordinates that is on the front
Wires for word
Forward
It doesn't affect x
It means that it would be
Still the only things can be clicked
Three times doesn't mean anything
Ok
Totally wrong but
I'm making progress
One way
Alarm
Lights
Rotational Whitehouse Whitehouse
Zia
Ok we can solve some of these things buy
Play Raining more test program
I am going to make a castle point
As long as it is from my house today
Why not
Around
Nexus 10 in my little way for the vectors
The decorah point in the opposite direction in translate that lights
IPads apple
Walking around as easy as the time of 1
On
I just realised something
This should be the position of a lighthouse
If it's off by that much that means I can't possibly be right so something is seriously
The position about lighthouse Realty
Headset should be
Positive positive y0 Forex
The other one should be positively negative why
Positive y negative Z
Positive lion agency that's super wrong
Hey
Cars of the 90s
How often do you think it could be 0.7 m off Centre
The line between them
Half a litre
Maybe
Am I try on doing the transformation that Dave
I'm going to try and do in the transformation I made that tried to cancel that
Don't touch it down
I'm not sure they started word I'm seeing now from Dave's code
That's something that
Looks relatively good
Cos that's a positive z and negative y a positive Z
A positive values for x
The Producers
Stop
Lights for 5 bills on the freebsd hi to once you are you delete the make fire with it
Spell very wrong about takeaway
That's the Mostly right
Perpendicular vector
Ring light
This is one Factor
You have to have another factory Nutella and now
Can you call Cody about 9
It doesn't have to be exact
I can be like this and that's fine used to normalise re-enter
It's easy to change the code and look at the party changed the whole thing
All wrong
Set off
Start radio
After to do something like the pose
Do you know what
I'm from BrightHouse is point of view so
Cancel
Very wrong
Idea
I'm doing the same thing I do love down here
I think that might be the key
Two
Because they should know if I am
Feels like this is algebraically wrong but maybe we can
Pressing on times of that happening
Ok
Houses.co.uk friend
Phone
Upset
LEGO
What which is just that sell
Lhps
Cip sorry
Throat is from 0BJ from that
Second time
Inside of Dave's and his giving me a different answer every time
Everytime
I could leave it there is some cold it's like a chameleon sometime
41.84201 1.4
2.3
Wonder on here
Pause
Show sing x route should be the same date of the heating
Changing
Play it down I stupid
Turn off
I know
I was looking at this number
Compared to what the code of fair is getting so it is the same status good
On so
Until
We would rotate by something but I don't know why yet
Ok
This time it was accurate with the same answer two of them mm of the last time that time I've got with in a millimetre
Ok that's something here
Yeah that's moving so now he had to rotate
Degrees
Around any perpendicular vector
Cos it's going if I move that way it's gonna move with respect to the White House
Ok so move it to see the plus x on top moving plus extra x
Ok
The chairs something out no it's getting a bunch of Clans
Starting at 8 again
Ok
So in one case included in the boss xx in the other included in the minus x
To the Lighthouse
We have to rotate that by the Lighthouse Factor by the
Sieve Factor
What's the percent vector
Play
X 12 happened
Somewhere
OK to use it back
So
Destiny -1 one
Positive why
B and m
Irritation
I guess just why
Brought it to myself
Not right
I'm back
Well
So close
Five minutes just five more minutes
Are so close now
That way
Ok it's out of order
Rotation translation
This one does not work I will give up tonight
Turn all wrong
Ok what's on Dubai
Is part is all wrong
Back to 0
Guitar guitar
Ok
What's the least try to think about this so we have
The vector
The headset as the Orchard
Then days code gives us
Where are the position of the headset is relative to that
The Lighthouse from the Lighthouse is the origin
Ok
Dan
From
Peter athletics position in 3D space
What we do is we take
That vector
Here to there
I had that that's why I do do 360°
The victories yes yes
The weight of the vector
Down the hill yes that's all we have right now
It's not working because when you now were operating within white
Pretending that's at the origin so would move that way
Removing around in 3D space from that point of view
So how are you
Why are we moving at lights
Anywhere
So
We start with
Caroline has one of you better
Occasion
Around so now I have the 3D corners of the lights
Yes
So now when he sees me something
It's from the point of view
Are the Lighthouse change so of you change an extra to the Lighthouse
So
Why are you what is that
Because
I don't know how to explain that that's just the Way It Is Right Now
We have to get a roti
We never rotated back into world
Rotation
We've been stuck in
Lighthouse rotation
Which should be fine with that will get you the position of that in Whitehouse rotation
Maybe we get that in the rotator
By the station
Is only get the position from that it's from the lighthouses
Like I said a whole rotation like thing going on
And Israel now when you move in that like that way it's saying Oh I'm in that direction
Relative to my thing which is totally different in 3D space
So it may actually just be as simple as a notation
By the object so
Do something useful to begin with
Ok set
That time
That's just because that was a pretty good waiter test something
Thoroughly freaking out ok
Mouse
I think something is really trying it offers on bed are you
Still looks like it's being rotated
Mia forget it I think we might have to roti like ahead of time and then do everything world
Something like that is right now or operating in the local space that
I'm sorry guys we failed this was a failure or we tried it's good things come in
Turn on going home
You can stay if you want stuff in the morning
Add
Skip
Almost 14 poser information staff
Long stream 2 live
Goodbye
Calibre cleaning
Why is it crash
CTS driver seat
Do I speed at night
Broken
Survive for me
Keyline 201
Did not pick up the device or something
No this is the contact the contacts couldn't care less if the device is turned on
Are you die
Calibrate of a calibre line 177
Why did you set this B up
That's good that one
You didn't
Receipt
70 x 3 Radio 2
Is it sunny tomorrow
Angry
Somewhere
Recently freed
Innovate somewhere
Nazi wine 201
Can you set the alarm
Code
Start something ok
Something in Calgary
What do
Turn on my lamp
Just look at that map
News
Turn fast set times to turn half cylinder sensor ID
Stuff
Yes the start already
I remember seeing a dead one and two please
Hey
Fixed
Find out why that was negative
Actually the post
This sometimes
Never crashed before that's a really good question maybe a lot of other problems before had to do with that
Do I don't think I'll problem tonight at to do with that so
That's really nice Josh actually that really is nice
Is don't trashed
Next Josh's accidental
Charles and Jack