Hello everybody welcome and thank you for coming out to the 9th livestream here I just kept leaving
Lighting this after all this time
Has been done by a wide variety of people people like E-Class her over
Discord have been trying out for 5
With different pieces of hardware such as the Raspberry Pi the odroid various internal cards in video
One of the things that even though we don't have anything right now to put me into
Codewise
We want to make sure that we're going to get this my charger as possible that can output to the HTC vive
Now you might say oh but why don't you do like a really powerful video card and the answer is flat out no
Alexa which isn't very much on my Intel card and so that's one thing I know can work
But right now trying to figure out is there any way to get the volume to work on a raspberry pies they're really really had survived to work
And all of this other stuff
Can so he's been doing a lot of work figuring that one out
Additionally mwtv I don't actually know what handily goes by
What is doing enormous amount of work with with having the the steam tractor and being able to get that
To the rest of the system but not done in wireless mode
Additionally live survive now has support for windows and OSX
Random Windows it's Portsmouth PC if you don't want install
Visual Studio
Visual Studio both of the 4 driver registration models
Different drivers further 5 can be written and just use
Are without having to change any other codes you can just go Linkin and you driver and it just works
And yes no not 1080p definitely not actually streaming from my laptop
There I'll be off working on my computer
Quiet
That is because hopefully will get it least trying to print a circuit board and maybe seen what
Turn alarm volume looks like I only have about 3 hours so it's going to be a bit of a stretch but I still
On
Those with the steam cracker od2 Chapman has been working
Plus way I figure out a better way to do
David Japanese been working on a poser so the the lights
Systems
The first are part of the system is where you take on data comes from device
On and these devices are called things like survive underscore
The source that we actually have and what it does is it collect
Light pulses in imu information
And that into our survive data and survived
Guess these codes in handle lightcap
And another thing people have been working on newer disambiguated
Stop going back to that comes from devices
Is Dan goes into something called a disambiguation
Finger yourself please turn I saw this policy right old is Paul Stewart old is pulse hear what the angle of view is
From the Lighthouse then from there you can go into either the calibrator
The rest of the system still under process the data comes
Ian from the Lighthouse
Arm and then are we haven't actually coded yet but theoretically we were going to be able to use the base
Do you know txt
Which I think is a pretty good idea what does
Can I have to trial and error 14 little bit further and once we can actually validate
So it will take the data that's coming in from the lighthouses
And then we'll see how does that producing good solution bad solution to good solution well
Then we have a pretty good idea that day what we're doing to handle the information from
The lighthouses is correct
Otherwise we'll just have to keep troubleshooting that
And then the data is passed off to on either
Will right now to cast off to posters and the calibrator
And we have poses
Such as ortho or poser troll slow
Are which candle are angle information
And then compute the the
The orientation and all of that all
An object based on it so one thing I can do right now is me
Reporter pipe
Voice 05
IMessages Dave's mechanism forearm
Visualisation here
Stop
Again
Try that again
Ok so here
Is Dave's auto part trying to use a transformation
Figure out the pose of the bike headset
Until the red points are the points that were seen from the white house is point of view and the blue
Lights are where we would think we should see those point if we are if we were to
His coding answered and it tells by the way
Is right here and it has this orientation and rotation and all of that
Is there still some bugs so it's still doesn't line up perfectly specially glancing angle
Antonia prequels
Put ninja pretty good so I think is far as will really need
Solution is almost there
Sets going to be really cool 1 seconds in a day
I am a hardworking guy and a microcontroller die
I'm going to finally this the first livestream I'm going to get a chance to do I want to do
I want to do is Bilton hardware
Stop
Questions she just doesn't require calibration did work
Does not require calibration data
The latest simply gives you right angles
After that you have to use the otx data which we are collecting from lighthouses and restoring
The we just don't necessarily know exactly what to do with it yet
Is it actually stores like the Earth cafes at khaltat kilkern atkal
Whatever all these aspects from the Lighthouse for storing we also don't have the posing
Station coming from the Post information that Davis provided
Bye Dad just a matter of you know some of the people on the project getting together and figuring ok we got
I'm putting it in there so things are really
Please
Using
Probably not crisis still on
Yes it is possible
I didn't he knows which way round with her a p32
Anyway so
All the stuff is great everything's great
I think it's me and you you can totally just buy this chip from whatever it is something
Which will take in light data
And basically give you a on
How do you describe it it's it's basically leaving
Arm steamship
5 shed
Nope no no
Does anybody have what the chip is cos I actually like me cannot remember what the chip is that you can come
Bye
But the problem is
Install paint
TS 3633 that sounds familiar
So digital converter for steamvr tracking
So this chick right here
So what does it takes in the infrared light with the bias and it
Reduces a in envelope output and on
Take a little bit install
Hi weed
No not gonna go
Are your part right now at least not until I give up
Trying to do what I want to do
So what do you actually get coming from the the lighthouses
Something that looks
But it is a modulated signal so
You basically get this infrared coming from the Lighthouse
Arm and Wetherby sweeps
Already flash just have this modulated signal
And it's going to look something like not quite like that
And the reason behind that is because when you have an isolated signal you can use a high pass filter
And you can Dan only work for Life that's been transmitted about 1.8 m
Yeah that's cool by arm
What are really doing here is some some 30 electronics in order to take this
Ignore right here and then I'm boosted up
And then what I'll do
Is don't take this boosted signal
And I'll pipe it through a diode
Arm reality but like I dies is it means that you'll have the
Here
And it will output kind of like this envelope
Sing
And that the envelope shape depends on the
Where are these things start where they stop
On
And and you can pull a lot of information out of this and you can actually really get like the Pulse length and
Other information that's all past off
I'm in all this is actually done in an fpga inside of the series 5 controllers Wetherby
Controller or headset or whatever
And that's fine and dandy
But I think I can do better
Like I don't actually know if I can do better but it's one of those things like my mentality is like
I just always assume
I come to the table with different knowledge than anybody else the same as any of you guys watching words
You never assume that oh no somebody smarter than make him up but this I can't possibly contribute anything
What's the time in the final
Let's just check this
So instead of doing this I want to scrap this chip all together and
I want to try to do an Irish probably going to cost more in the end but considering
Kia d285 switch oral lichen esp8266
Built-in flash they are not even allowed to say how cheap they are there left
20 dollars and 10 cents
Firelight on that's the lowest I can tell you
The number for on and by the way if you want you can buy some new cd285u single chip
Like Wi-Fi solution for Wi-Fi but they're really cheap so what I am
To do is I want to have the signal right here
I want a pipe it into a high speed of
Arm course I'm gonna have a little bit filtering and stuff like that
Propaganda look more like this
Baby bath
What's going to happen is I won't be able to get the signal out and what I want to have is something that
Are fairly big signal here and I've known to use the Schmitt trigger on the import of
Esp8285
Rdi to
IPad and 12
Hey do it's going to take in this wacky signal can it's going to digitise it into
A square wave for me
And the cool thing about the east pd25 is it's got in 18
Register on their soccer so I'm going to be able to sample
This incoming signal at 80 MHz Snapchats is or I'm not going to be able to keep up and processing
Navigate to drop back for tea I want to see what happens if I look at this input signal
I tried to figure out more information about what's going on
Maybe I'll be able to figure out orientation may be able to figure out much more accurately where are the
Now when the finger sweeping
It might be sweeping from here here and I like might be visible from there to there
The the wave started right there
Or maybe the wave started right there
Armin you haven't had her about 1.1 over 1.8 mHz
Arm
So
Yeah I know no fpgas
Esp8285 better fpga for what I'm trying to do
No way I can use an stm32 why use those commercially cos they're expensive
Also that ucd35 can totally go faster so I have absolutely no
Basically when when the sky came on the scene my interest in anything stm
Went down the tubes
Especially esp32 I kicked the snot out of every single thing St has to offer
Anyway so what I want to try to do is that I want to try to get
This this thing work
And I did what I want to digikey
I did find an interesting part
Actually I bought a home by 2 p.m. so I'm gonna try them out
Quite what I did find and what I did buy the sky
On it's really cheap it's 27 equality
And it's pretty good game out of fairly high frequency
Which is really useful to me
Armin so what I intend to do with the tray used this guy
And have it also
One problem with this
This part really requires a plasterer - + - 5 volt a swing
And I would be able to this I'm 3.7 V batteries
So one of the other technical hurdles will have is I'm going to have to have some sort of charge pump or something setup
In order to take the voltage of 3.7 volts or 3.3 volts I guess which is coming into
PSP
And take it up to something that
Well I can actually use
Arm
And so and see if I can
Log in to
Set it
That's what it is
Tell me move over here so I cannot
Open church pump
So what I intend to do is have a circuit it's a little bit like this
Only use to the gpio on the esp8285 or for this purpose
Esp8266
And I'm gonna go try to drive this charge pump so even though these only go up to
See what do I set up to
It's actually impossible I'm
Develop web pages like this
Next step
Scroll to ml
Pause value 2.9 so the
The means with the voltage on
If I said a probe
So what I can do is by passing these on a graph those two things
I can actually get
Are you cold
Run
Transit response let's go for it it's probably right
This is a negative
Send a site fine just to see you guys can see it even though all I have is easy
V or a 2.9 volt output
Arm
This circuit can synthesise
Oops
How do I zoom out
At the turkey can synthesise a -6 volt voltage
Arm so that it's going to be really useful in order to be able to use other types
Of RPM spin don't do real the real
Don't know if it's gonna work out
Meeting is if it does work out I'm going to be able to actually use this in other designs where I'm
Have negative and positive for teachers
That m that I want to make
I can actually if this works I can feel radically dump the 9-volt battery and
Make the ESP synthesise the negative voltage required by the voltmeter
This is one of the two designs
The other design have to put some things around which I probably prototype
Before I am I go to back while
Resistor DAC
I don't know what you're talking about ID
Something something
Anyway
So this is one part of the charge pump
We have to create another part of the charge pump
But I will have to
Turn the tide out
So Steve as charge pump
Arm to the plus side of the charge pump that uses
Something that looks a little bit like that so instead of putting it up to the ground rail to the base
What we can men do as we can help hazard of real
Two are the basis and parks in words
You do that
Just do it's going to be none
3.3
Connections
Does not seem to do well with
On
I think all I have to do is put these around and it should
Produce a circuit that would do what I want
No
I usually don't actually do charge pumps normally what I do in more commercial things as I used a
An inductor in actually make like a switch mode power supply
But whatever I don't think I can get this to work really cheap with indoor
Verso
Tell me not gonna try
Thank you Mark I did not realise you were watching Mark
Mark we're going to have to have a heart-to-heart about life survive because I really think it's getting close to the point where
Anyway
Can I give us a shout now on it
I've no idea if this works
I forgot to probe the output
Probes
Ok rhyme
Sweet looking at thing it's producing 9 volts ok
So this looks like it probably about what I want to actually use them
Nothing is here just guessing
Hi supersoaker oh my gosh everybody hello
So what I'm going to do is Amir take these two circuits anadrol mop in
I can hear the use gpio
14 for that
To do it that way am I going to do this
Maybe
Probably not to just operate the soccer
Wouldn't be able to go all the way low
That's ok
Why bother doing something right when you can do something that might work
Even if it's really bad
So instead of having the negative side I'm only going to have a positive side for my charger
My somebody something is really wrong
Thing
This is bad so let's just give it a shot
So gpio 12
That is actually the i2 Si
Armin that is specifically the pen that you can settle at 80 MHz on the S
Take me to 66 / esp8285
Gpio 13 and 14 are gonna be the ones that I'm going to go
Noodle around in order to make the charge pump work
All the breeding if you guys a curious on charge pump
Look up the Wikipedia page on it'll actually just give you an example circuit
Looks really similar to mine
And what you actually do they make it girl
I got it really does look so I got one last stage
Just a little bit lower
So we'll have to do is turn off in on 13:14 timing doesn't really matter I can just do it on
Something like that finger up something eventually
Sofa right now let's go figure out how this is actually going to go be all wired up
So it's going to be there there there
So but I also have you
I bought some Diamonds to so I can just use those
This order
Communion
I think for the first one I'm going to use this one
Spectacular
Madhouse um dia de Reyes date
Libraries
This is a new installation
And I don't remember had it in for you so I'm just going to go make my own
Say pirate on
Play It's A 223
And we're gonna go through some things in here
10 one is + 1
-
Two
Riaz Common
Yes the circuitry will only be able to table data from one photodiode but it's so absurdly cheap
Why not there's another big benefit of this
I having only 14 processor it means that processor can then be used to process the data
From the photodiode
Snowfinders some sort of tourists I can use your magic can code
That would ordinarily be prohibitively difficult
I would have to spend time to go do it
If I code an object with 32 sensors
That has 32 esp8285
32 esp8285 is actually
3260 MHz processors for an effect of 5G
Whatever it is
Drystone mate 5G
Skips skips whatever comes of processing power right there on the things that are able to pull
As long as I can do pretty quick
It's going to Green
Please find me a lot of extra computational power in addition all that
Maybe I could send higher level things such as running the disability later inside the sentence themselves and
Only passing the angle that out
I'm so let's check this data here
Yes yes ba2570
Put it into a buffer for you and then call it sweet and done
123 ok
Stop the folder in half
Wait a minute
Are you crack I did that wrong
32 x 160 is
No that's right
So I could run
Only two Solutions I could use for this one I could use the esp8285 at some stupid icespeed
300 something MHz and then use the ice Squirtle SLP and
Can you sing like a code division multiple access output stream which I will define and software
And then you can just use a little software-defined radio to receive all of the signals from all of the tax
That's one option but it does probably vileda lot of FCC rules I don't really want to do it
Do intend to use speedy 25 normal clocking Nutkins
52 Wi-Fi network but using related to 11 frames to send and then I can have multiple received
Intend to use diversity with this so I'll have 3 or 4 receivers so no matter what
Set signals going to get through some stupid hirade like send me to Magor
It's so it's going to use virtually no airtime so I should be able to slap in like hundreds
And it shouldn't be any any real issue
I don't think I don't think the esp8285
Going to be able to do Solutions but I could do is to say I can make it on there
Material pens my pens call go21 esp32 for specific device
Esp32 with the help of all those a speedy 25 is probably
I most certainly enough to do post solving in so much so love to do is Take That
And then have two more that Drive high-speed only displays I make my own
Whether or not I can do it
What's office thing one step at a time ok
Go now
It's not good what did I do wrong
Dad dad
Sorry news
Whatever you put in there
Everything in here
All I can do is I can use this allot 3.3 V thing there
And I can use to use a capacitor array
A10
This right here
Have one more of these every year
Please two guys together
So that looks an awful lot conveniently like
3.3 volts in
Soda b801
This would have to be crowned this is not
Whatever
Call 12 I'm going to have to figure out how to get blue slime
Install bind
Sierra people.at in chat
Yep definitely don't worry this is Kai god all the way
Dad
Developers do colicky kata something weird like that
It's also try to protect this
Drop him that RPM that I want to try so that's this one right here
Call somebody's tabs
Are the esp8285 does not have an appeal
Esp32 does have an fpo now much to my frustration cancel
People who make carrots actually cadence now who make the CORE for the esp32 the
The set itself is proprietary which I think is insane I email down there
I responded if anybody else has any contacts and salad or anywhere like that they might be able to get the instructions said that would
Buy however the esp32 through other means we
Has reciprocal filling point square root and other things like that
Will they can do these operations instantaneously like to Clark cycle do something to do reciprocal square root
Floating point so it's it's it's stuck behind
What is proprietary John like you not like you just can't get enough to date instruction set for the ESB
It's not a specialist fault it's specifically to intelligence fault and I think if they want to start
Probably sure they're gonna have to make their instructions set open like
Why is the secret
Anyway moving on let's go make a park for this other guy right here
Drawing Pirates
Yes I know I did not finish installing
New Cork in this part is called a
Mic90 y85
And your ears
1 +
Two
3 - 3
4 is
5th class
Ok so that's kinda with that she look like
Let's go to draw a little part around it's two people actually be able to recognise it
1 unit
That goes there that makes it impossible to read ok fine
Long pin90 bus number 5
2 FM
Ok looks like a fairly reasonable Park
Background
Yz50
Mike 20
Ad part b head while
I know I did not like
20 wifey 5K what I'm going to do is dumb
Now I have in minus in in plus
I wanna play with them if I had to guess
Probably if somebody's are for it but I don't know if anybody in here is
I want to make sure I can actually
Differential voltages at the rail
Can I use real the real pirates I don't even really know that I'm looking for here what I want to make sure there is that if I G
One of these two just ground that it won't freaking out of it might
But worried I forgotten what the type of thing is called though
See hear
Probably want to probably want a garden that I want to make a little bit safer
So what I'm actually going to do is enough with Ade
Find 1 of 1
Is wire for the rest of the stuff right now
I don't know what I'm going to do with the negative side there I got a figure that out
This is totally good for up to 12 V not actually 12 but it is going to be pretty good
And this is going to come from a connection
To do this
Radio
The Milky
Moving line
App iPad
See what is chat saying
2 lb 30 way too expensive I'm telling you use PE28
Are cheap wireless built-in
Just saying
Input common-mode range
Perfect that's what it's called voltage
They say a girl
From 0 of the Fall ok
Oh no 3.25 3.25
Ok so it looks like I will have to have at least like a Volta something V and a half
I actually need to do
Come on
Hi CAD
Ok whatever is now we have our library
So
I have a day out here going to ground
Going to be put friend
Then this one here I need a connector
Adam is playing some video game I think the Witcher
Pharmacy here
You're biased
Is almost certainly going to need to have something
You might replace this with a
Initially
So what I have going on here is I'm making a time for makeshift high-pass filter but it's going to be an offer
Who knows maybe this will work maybe at the lot of things
Is aggressive is I want to try testing today considering only have 2 hours left out in half hour
Left on this lightstream makes me nervous but
Just give us a shot and see how bad is going to be are we going to be able to do this or any night
Play I am
Find parrot
Hold on I know you guys are actually telling me useful stuff
Alperton by the maximum output sink sink the short circuit
Not insured Circus that's good very high impedance output
I know all of these things should be fine on because what's going to have
I keep the sink locally and everything is going to be able to be kept in sync by the
By the White House itself so when it sends out of Flash I'm going to give it a watch that flash and singer
I do not still use
Papa it's just I don't know I feel dirty whenever I use it
I wish somebody like an open-source free version of it is just doesn't exist right now
It always changed
This close to here
All those look fine on what's using my
Ep 117
Yeah I switched my components mid way through and you just really shouldn't do that
I really don't like free router it's just not
It's it as much work to get things into and out of keypad but it doesn't even give you that
How much are they are like
I can rap better than all the time where is with Copa every now and total give me a run for my money
There'll be times from routed this perfectly and then Topaz like now I figured out his passed away
Oh you punk you are incredible
Now first of all would pick up some sot hello
Where is 23 SE12
Is that match up with the dealership here for that dice
Sea
3023 the wrong thing
I should have noticed because picture is different combination of four diodes
Play something
Bosch 23
Let's see here and see what
Yes
Really make that stuff visible
October is
Read up unbelievably good I just do not know how toper is as amazing as it is
Saying Toba can actually be me but like
Something like all teams
I know some people who tried to use the old pier Motorola in it
And basically all the commercial operators are just terrible but somehow tobi's is just
Believable and I can Crush any other routers
Read there's a lot of stuff
Slight redness
Stephen something
I'm mysterious what did Dave Jones
What is he come into with the the order Rattigan
Have you ever used it like I'm really serious what other people have to say about the altermodern
Because my parents have just been so hilarious
See her so this will go around that way
That is not
Comfortable living room
Hi Adam parking near the rooms playing video games with the noise
Try this calciferous
Do that
Too late
One of the ways a lot of people I work with you'll get around Altea
Eight layers why is needlessly
Do you sing by hand in 2K
Ladders
Really the only way back
Totally
You should be sad
Waiter
Big
That's entirely the wrong footprint let's just use it anyway spacing is right
Try this combination
These
Tackt-isle
Tile
By the way this is different from offer land
We tried with them
Stop the bags that Magnus badges and that was what messed up so I'm just gonna start using it now
Because I'm off to bed
What's good switches my summer in there
Something like that
No reason for this be contact
Nonsense we don't need to get really
Design I think I'm going to go loose knob somebody's eye animals
1.12
People commenting about you
Richard yeah yeah by the way
Going to be much much lower latency than normal Wi-Fi
Connected through
You need to make light jumper there cos these are already connected like by metal inside the park
It's not like I sometimes words you actually have to my connected otherwise terrible things happen
Hi sweet
All this chocolate come from
Marshmallow
The Wonder Years
Flowers
And something something next thing we have to do we're going to have to
Tango to digikey and we will have to figure out exactly what part put princesses
Pretty sure it's not an sot23
I can just play
Halloween night
Violate the rules
Ok clearance 10 ml
Call Viola
What's pretty crap
I didn't know that was he
Get there is a ton more like
Go design something in build something and have it working and it's still less than 5% of the way to
If you like 1%
Just because something works on the bench you are light years away from a function
Like I can go on the shelf product like
Polite neon FM arcade game that we made beautiful type done in like a month
We've been doing on it for 3 years
Remember what I'm doing
Yes done
Disguise
So let's find out what the parties
You'll probably have a third can which two more that has ground and on
The power as I can get to that probably going to be useful
I actually say that
EMC testing is complete
I am using Linux Mint
I'm good go
Plead yes done ok
Over here
Going to work
Don't know where they're going to go
That would work homeless up song
Definitely not
Like a boss
Mrs probably tank a
Make a margarita
Weird anyway I do have a current
I don't have a current feedback loop but that's because
As the Frequency goes up the amplifier itself so ok this is a really
The interesting thing about engineering when it comes to these sorts of parts in general
Component a lot of engineers Put Em and a waterfall are really really unnecessary
SO41 if what you want to do is give us much pain as you want and have a lowpass thing down here
And you have as much as possible up here like a game you can just
No feedback basically and then it'll naturally take off the higher frequencies
Talking about I don't think City opened
At lower frequencies is going to be enough to mess with Adele
Roll a resistor in there just in case
Just in case I don't think I'm going to need it but
No say no population right now I don't think of
Yes I'm using exactly
You are correct that might not be sufficient that might not be the way to go I don't know
Really wanna over engineer if I don't have to
You like that
Here
Who's going to be hard the plan
Might not be able to do it this way
So close
Who actually
Ok we're getting there
Probably go like that like that
No
Heart
I'm going to just have to scrap
Really wanted to use that but I can't
I was trying to avoid using an extra capacitor by Frank use this year it's not make any sense
Play 11 like a third on that is not gonna be enough to get rid of all the nasties so I
Really do need to get my dad to capacitors out here
Hoop happy
East to use a
Maybe in a 10 likes I can be enough
It's going to be rough
Really going to be rough
Really have another one yeah
That might be my sister hope for the best
Repercussions
I need to move some of the surround
Probably be on one you are so I have here
Trying to because I have a charge pump it's going to be super nasty
I don't have any 22 Mike 0051 ce20
You're probably right that would be that one
Don't have anything like that in any boxes already done
Turn my again turn my account
Set a router
Between there
I think this is all I need
I don't really use cutie and pretty much addicted to raw
13 silkscreen that's not needed
I will do though I will add AR
What you call this
Crown plane ground plane
I wasn't quite far enough
Dispatches the 80 MB War
Make me sad poem
Write about
Ok well pass DLC
This is I'm trying to write
Design am like a test to see how hard it's going to be or if it can be fees
Alarm for me to read the five my house with really Ree
Cheap awful parts I just don't know if it's going to be feasible or white
I'm going to give it a shot
Yeah I know
Calcium plus looks like
All the big nasty areas are not covered with brown blinds just play
It doesn't mean
Speaking actor that's fine but a 10-mile that's 10 Mike
But somebody's are on here
Pause my 10ks
Probably right with somebody's in here are my
Probably be about 20 k I really don't know though I've never
Use these photo diode having be using them in the reverse on reverse bias mode
So we'll have to just cry going to be 10 and
Is it going to be
Volume one
So much is just guesswork
Don't know the electrical properties in so much of it it's just going to be
Myers bus
Probably know I don't really know
That's going to be a 1
Live
That's obviously new ski to whatever
This is probably gonna work
Work work
What's ok I'm sorry I had it off screen
How's eyeballing this looks rate
Good
Sync
Whatever only got 2 hours left let's try it
Oh no Adam
Why did you have to do laundry now
Amazon printing circuit boards
The dust from the laundry messes up well
Whatever maybe maybe
Hobbyist engineer problems
Ok yes
Power with app
My friend you can know I'm going to show you why you put when you can riddle
Anyway actually I got a bunch of designs I want to throw out on this one
What's going to do all the designs at once ones that anytime kidding white
Oh my gosh
Is King
What's TM
I am going to have
To switch accounts
Give me a moment
Network
No files go
Weird
Ok
We are gonna take you guys and slap you
Sure
Promo
Are we going to do is to say no reason for any more than that
You guys are curious these boards here esp32 boards
And I am just trying out a couple of things with them
To see if I can actually get it to one layer without any jumpers at all I don't know if it's gonna work out
I think it does
It's not me this time
Do I put my password in plain text I didn't notice
Ok just do it
Best friend
Actually remember all of my settings so my gosh
Sweet
At once on regular paper to get it warmed up and then I print it twice
A hard time
Discount hard for you guys to see that the
Quality is below right now
Another on
Wrong with you
Are you so sad today
Clever what does try it
Play will work maybe it won't
Set exposure class
It's really weird though
Astatic maybe
What's the temperature
In spend $37 on you for nothing
Getting worse
I have never tried printing face down
Today's seems like the right data do it
It seems just fine
I have never done this before us what's just tried putting on paper
No the tires out of lino
Blowing it up
Yeah I think that
No still awful
What's this to somebody online said I could take regular paper and put it face down
So
What does the shark
Hey you know what that was on there that said why not middle
Might be a time when
Will I will be better
Something is wrong with my printer
Ok
Time to disconnect from the power sources and go downstairs
Let's hope that are this works
Sophia Burr
Washed resume writing
Play WhatsApp
Hey
Mark lifesaver you are a lifesaver Mark
What points are they supposed to design
Hahaha
The machine the start machine in the Hotmail
Ok what's this
Look at that
I need more paper
What are you doing
Just keeps getting worse and worse
Can you return the favour
Amazon
Don't get it
Whatever
Take my phone off
Such a bad brand
Hope the directors process is forgiving enough
Navigate
Cold water when using the sun microscopic makes things very sad
No that's fine
How to wake me off
Everett 1642 right now
Oh yeah good idea
Turn the light off
What's Razer
How many viewers are in right now it says I think it says 165 rate
I wish I could get spray-on resist oh my gosh I want restaurant positive so bad
But I cannot get it in America and I don't know why and it is so frustrating I want to
I want it I want it I want it
Do not know how to get it
So I have never ever exposed wallpaper before
No idea this is gonna work
I cannot use a transparency right now so
This is my only hope
What's the office works
Just like that
Alarm
UEFA
Yes Mary S Arena
Academy Corby for you Paula
I don't know maybe I can use in one oil baby
Uncharted territory
Ok knew that is just made out of magic
Get a text
South night one of you guys telling I just did something drastically wrong
Help
You guys probably have not seen this year
This is my UV light source
It is about 50 Watts which I did not think was very much power
Boy was I wrong
Tom I will need a pair of sun to it I'll just close my eyes
Two
Three
Four
Sex
It seems like in the band that restart is sensitive to
The ball was about 100 times more powerful
Oh my gosh
My work
A little bit pain
Condition of that for a second more
How many the truth is I can work other one I think it looks like it's fine so
Ok
The best
Quietly cardboard
Are you going to close the one in the middle world now
Cancel
Is it going to be fine
Walmart
By the way that's all sodium carbonate so it doesn't really matter like when you do when you wash laundry with it
Goes down the drain anyway
CIS currency
Solicitors now basically plastic on the surface
Timer
Sponge
Hi sponge the 2017 and then
Mr sponge
Spongy sponge
Sponge
No
Worked I think maybe I should start trying to switch to a
To a transparency list system one with I just use paper face down
That would be
Simple
Also if I waited 7 seconds to set of 6 Seconds of the development stage
Can I neutralise with every meaning
385 NM 101 LEDs
Come on
Don't have sober and why do I need child safety things quite a child safety things
Oh you guys I don't want to watch this
Lower rubbing alcohol
Get rid of any of the residue
Turn 13 minutes
Ok 17 minutes
No I'm not that one
Ok
So now I've got these boards made sorry for being quiet for so long
If I can figure out somewhere to let other people control white check
Actually I might be able to do that maybe next next livestream will try that out
I'll try to make it to you guys can control white text
So all I actually care about here is our boards
That's all I will be putting parts on his are towards
Please
What like the connectors to fuel the come off the end
Barrister
Support any of the year
What does ASMR mean
You are free to continue laundry
Normally have
Yeah yeah
Have you having already been doing it
Google I'm more parts on here in Ireland putting on here
Take a lot longer than I'd hoped
I have an hour left
Crap that's all good
Actors to he is anything else we have to worry about yourself
Mr I've forgotten something in there
I will not build the space dispenser but if an automatic paste dispenser appears on my just I will absolutely
Play music
Oil tankers
I actually don't like building things I only like designing things but no order for things that I do
Find me
You no physical realisation I have to build them building is simply for me and necessary evil
That is the 10 Micro Farad cap
Are these originally came from jameco is far is more nothing else like it exist however
Does exist so if you need boxes like it you can get boxes like this
This one is that he'd text Brian but I believe there are several different brands
Screen repairs cost
Will not have any time now period
Ideal home
I was 22 nana ferrets for that big one
20K
I got 22
Do you need a
Big capital
Completely the wrong part it might work
I never porkpie sofil board you can't trust the part
Just to rescue
Mean if I'm in a pinch and I need the part and it's on the Old board I'll take it off but
I usually avoid
So much can go wrong
Ok I'll be right back
Hi Ben
Maybe another dragon
Ok puppies
Deleted
My gosh turnover
Turn my area
More caps and
To-do list
Need one more when off do I need
How
Find one in
Ok Ben Jackson that is correct
You intend to use the Express bus is a high-speed 1-bit logic analyser
Can the big thing for me is I want to try to do it without
Having an envelope on the front end just Trader
Show the data in the port and see what happens
How long I have 24% battery left
Yeah I think if you were used Captur compare you should be able to use an stm32
The capture I think about is money at 16 at 1 but I want to Loveridge
The power of the essay on computational power
For my well so I can do processing on that on the other thing I'm really
Hoping for and I don't know if it's feasible or find you you know a dreamer but I want to see it
I can get extra data from the signal that's what when you envelope the signal I really think it should be possible
Turn to go get more information out then it's currently got now into the the triads
My gosh hands are so unsteady nowadays
I think I might have any Wi-Fi dad's upstairs
Softer home things
That good
Have to go shortly but if we have enough time to leave
If I can get that charge pump working
Go for it was going to assume everything is
The turbo sumption dry make it frequently
That one is received
I'm actually burn something useful
Ok
Brian ellicott by any chance no I grew up in
I definitely do not move it is
But now I'm not I'm not I'm in southwestern Baltimore
Round positive
Reorient everything
Hello I'm well aware this is going to be bad News Bears everyone
Don't worry
I don't expect this to work but I expect to learn something about why it won't work
Cloning the k multimedia project since it is pretty similar to what I'm doing here
The forest trying to catch on medium-high speed
Saying not happy
Do I not have Ono
Ben I'm also very serious off the size for testing I'm really hoping that after 4
Generations I get something at work and I know this generation is gonna be useless
I'll see if I can do something like this in there
Rhys Lewis
I'm going to happy my fingers salute
Meat
That did not work
Star Trek
You're right the character
And it
I need to plug in
Six-pack camera
Drdo
Hello
Quran audio
Testing
Do you have to go on about 1520 minutes charge pump going
Set the volume to 66
It does not boot
I did something bad
Don't know what it is
Actually have a better idea
I will try slightly different years to you that I know work
I just might not work
Adds not good
Light on
I'm going to wait
It's not short it out
That's fine so weird
Great son's wrong with my development environment
How old was messing with something I shouldn't ask list
No it's not about wrong by Drake
Bedfordshire
Let's try and basic Project
Play Adam do you want to go to elevate worship thing tonight
Bother the contemporary worship church
It starts around like 6:38 ok
What is flowing on how is everything so broken
Oh weird
An old version of esptool
Working
Tidy office right now
Flashing
Spell Howie
Try different project say
66 minutes
Newer copy of the SDK
My coordinates
Don't have permission to do it
This was never built
Please work
Harley My build environment is broken on this computer that just wonderful
You know
I'll just use my laptop here
What's the best thing in here
Really
Ok so it is actually just a build environment problem and it is with my laptop so I am
I'm going to put this away for now and I might actually be back later on tonight if I can get
Golden Valley not working on my desktop but nobody wants to sit around in my some training with coronavirus working
Hope you guys had some fun I'm sorry we didn't get to do more interesting stuff maybe
Will be back later on this evening thanks guys