Just getting things ready I found a bug
Turn my thinking it was just I had built the 1400 different user identifier bottom experimental
Turn off
Hey ok this is part 2 I guess of live stream
Number 9 really important one I designed
Built some of these forests if I can get it to focus here
Earlier I got a 2
Boards and got them printed and populated and now were going to see if we can flash
Wilson firmware and see what some easy analogue signals look like if I have any hope which I probably don't
Being able to see what the signal coming off light houses look like on
Honestly I think I'll be what he just to get the thing to the sympathise next with voltage real tonight but
Let's just started and see where we end up going to plug these in
Power and all that that one ground
Brand new
Rebooting while they like I did before but that's to be expected
Reset it here and I should
Harm
Eircom
Ok
Irish to English is right now I think it's fine
Pair
Move it
Belgrade
So maybe I was wrong there is something else going on that would be really disappointing
I would feel really embarrassed if if this is a boss again
I just programmed one it just worked
Am I doing wrong
And I hopefully get moving shortly here trying to figure out what is going on
I've actually never had this problem
Just my family that works
Play actually be a hardware problem or something maybe
Crowned
Broken in something is wrong with this one
What is going on here
Between some plans to check between that and what should be 3 v it looks like
All the places 30 should be matter
Really matter
How to check the rear 0 volts should be on gpio 15 which it is
3.3 that's weird that's gpio to analyse
That's fair actually no I could do
I try shooting
Donedeal
Effective
The same bored what I was going on
Yeah I'm actually I just never seen this problem before and
Yeah yeah
Use the A66 you know you figure it if it was a prob
That I wouldn't recognise it from you know song something they like every time that happened with that
Listen wrong there's always problems in the world
Find another board
Try this one
Definitely
Sing is definitely harder really ok I guess it's time to start busting out something that the bug this
Unusual things and doing I don't normally set it up this way of gpio
Arm wired up this way but it shouldn't be a problem
Virgin on my famous last words but you know
Nasty pio2 there
No hun
The other thing I can do is
Have any starter and short out gpio 15 sometime
Have that shorted
Passata
Nothing
What weird
Ok I'll do that then
Actually as it is it isn't changing anything this before it you know should
Do that
Call Kirsten
Backwoods
Stop
It looks like it's just the wrong boot mode
Doesn't make any sense
Vegetable shortening
Country Roads
A
I bet he never burn his lips
Yeah I do have
Get me anymore
Are used for cameos
Repository
Somewhere I have the
Turn on my laptop
Telling me stuff ok what is it telling me
Interesting
Thank you for telling me the search that as it turns out the
This is a really good point dry scalp feature is differently on the
Hardware
Reset different ok maybe actually part of
2xx
No I do it over at
On 27th
Ok where is this used
Tried it
Ok
So I shouldn't probably do is
Fnbr
Yes actually
And yes
Think I just can't believe this I just loading
Yeah riding the new Den so it may or may not just work it just work
Play Paul thank you for that that was a really good point I really should have just tried to see what it was
Tell me normally I'm just too lazy to execute the 1 commandments which is the Barbary to the Buddha portrait of 74
Ok now we can ask to go do something
Until I'm going to add a user
Are you to remain that say and in here I am going to
Enable the isporter subsystem
Cos that seems like an important thing to half
Then I think what I'm going to do is build some sort of state machine
Handles from the inner up
Hear what I can do I can edit the on
That is to do my bidding basically
I'm here for now comment all this out
Hand on piano
Turn on stat = 0
Something on my clarinet
I'm going to want to do something in
A 2TB hard pumpkins
What is r
TPI 13 gpio14
Over and look at someone to accept
What number was he did with that basically huge
Anything is anymore
Add see hear gpio
Complicated
Yeah that way
12 13 14 12 13 14
How to start work
And a news Iman when I do is configure
Beyond configure the
Better way of doing this like the new way but I completely
Anyway once this is configured or something maybe
I can learn go and in here changed mother's life and close this tab
I'm so under is teacher include
Sexy till
Out what I can do
I can specify
Or = BD13 or BD14
And that will enable the output
I'm sorry for you
I can search the output
I think it does should drive the two cans high
Exit 1st of May through the two pence well
And then we'll drive and high so here
This plan is very high
It's not very high why is that pin so high
Songs
Nothing on there septic pasta
That's weird
Please
Ok 323 and
163 that's not right
Here
Somewhere there is a gpio just work
I thought of a problem though that might might be an issue I don't know if the ice cream last boss
If you remap the pins to be
Gpio that can't be gpio so that that could be a problem
Gonna have to take a load of that
Right now
Thank you maybe I should just
Stop
2 12 13 14 to 12
TPI 13 x 14
Play
Oh well
Sharpies pens
See 3.3 V and IC
Rewind 3 v also make sure that they are up to still firing
Update still firing
I'm so now what I can do is I can then some outside
Setting up clear
And what I can do
Is inside of this code right here which is being executed just continuously non-stop I can use
Beyond bank
It's supposed to go -5 to 5-year
Play gonna get there but we actually get so so charge
To the signals have to go one off to on off one off to on after 1-hour
22 off
I think that's what's the try Paternoster what happens so switch
I'm totally hotspot
Would be both of them off so came out clear
It's 1234
14 + 13
Can I clear them again in that the other one
Turn the lights on
Charge pump 20
Poole Quay
What happens
CW on timers on the ESP
We are not a normal thing so
It's just not a friendly
Even though the actual system is normally nowadays the used the firmware
Are they don't even use the real one that's like coming directly from a sweater
Is jerk esp32 now that's got a ton of real every like
TV Lands and all of that
Clear cd13
Search
23.3
And that's super lame
Play 5 volts
What's try different what happens if I turn one on
Hot train
Set 13 set
Queer 13
Getting now
Still pretty bad
The circus doing something
Uploaded maybe I should be working on this yet
I'll go spend 5-minutes and do that right now
56 Whitehouse
Open
That's such a let down the charge
That Lane
Just have a bigger photograph that I expected
Forgotten how to initialise
He has an example in here somewhere
Charge pump failure is probably a blessing in disguise are you suggesting that maybe something is going to use at the time of current
Was working I blow it out
Because I totally believe you
On
Curved really don't have that much protection but it's nice to see you 66 cans are like
We tallaght to higher voltages in Google High Enough eventually no clampdown
You get a girl pretty hi before messages of the chat
I think I think lava the problem
It's ok there is really two ways I can go about this the one way that I was thinking is I have
Pull-up in Charlestown
Armin prefers
So the first I was thinking about having it is you have a y
Spy
Let's a master for a whole bunch of these little slaves
Armpit all
Sitting out here
In what I wanted to do was only have to run two wires to them and have the charge pump sitting in them
Reading light stupid idea
Especially since you know it is going to produce your signal
Play music by be able to arbitrary have a single one and be able to provide the power locally
Would be to have
A battery
Along with the this guy
Are they 82
Hey baby
5 and then within here have the
Really terrible thing going in but have these be completely self-contained and they also have like
I am you
And then the charge pump becomes much more attractive so really wanted to least give it a shot first
I was hoping to just
Tell yes I thought about using one of the lower lower voltage but I just
Couldn't find any good ones when I want to digitally I actually made an order for several of them I do and
Can you try them out eventually
But I haven't got any chance to try them out I was picking up flight just in general purpose off
Ok
12 MHz 1
I've got to do
15 MHz
Voltage
This one word
What is just
I know I wanna
I want to crazy things I'll try it out this one will operate within the right Ranger not
I might be going back to it
Viola
I just don't know
I mean
What's the temperature range from thing first cos it's funny fails miserably ok I'll give off
So you know what
Probably happening way to slow what's increase the frequency of charge
So
Filmmaking
Open off duplex in us to play
Oh yeah
Not the 5.2 5.3 volts
Just not gonna cut it
That's interesting the second stage isn't getting anything
Ok time for us to go get out
Play Guns and far is La Zenia concerned
I was able to borrow
Will seal a logic analyser
I just realised I've never installed the harbour for the offer for that on this computer
I have to do that
Also while on adverts
Probably wire on some terminal
Set up
Actually
Trailer
Stole the analyser
Maybe it's working soon
First thing no satellite use the ground
Hair salon destroy my remote table
Can you see that no scam
I'm amplifying and completely correct I don't think this is going to work
White
I have never let ridiculous ads200 between me and
Hoops learning some things
That's that one right now it's also monitor
The two charge pumpkins
And
Smarter
Are the ones on the way on the way out
Remember what the maximum voltage are
Yes ban
That's actually a really good point I could have gotten around all of this in just plug the stupid thing into a car
Where's the flying on from there
Believable way to do it
I've already started down this path now
That and I normally don't have the same lie so it was just by like that
How long will be the same this time
Ben are you a hardware engineer or a software engineer
Blog
Oh I missed the software engineer who is about 10-years further down the same path you're on
Call
I actually got my degree in computer engineering and then I went back to get my
In computer science
I realized I didn't like computer science but I was stuck in it
So I do hardware on the weekends
Accepting light survive which how I am getting stuck with because that's all software inside
Hope to my friends are smart enough to
Help out with any of the higher level Maths stuff cos I am not not Savvy
Turn alarm in bed work in lots of crazy projects yeah
I hope to Sunday
Get to the point where my project if I even get started it will be a feed to get started
Aldi
Something unbelievably difficult
Hey so f****** the ground had a huge loop that is so bad
Leeds 0BH phase 1
Pcs2
You
Hand
Add sound using I've never even
And I guess it's necessary for high-frequency start but
Ok ask me what is this thing look like
That is interesting
This one
Is the charge pump in the intended
Negative
Capture fast right click start
Oh yeah I know I know I know I just turned off all the digital
Turn all of the unused one but I don't really very quickly right now
Dislike all of this is happening
Exit
It's probably fine
Switch a roo lyrics
Brand new ones have 0 black and I have one of them
Euro is ground and Zeros black
I wish I could afford one of these but like if people sold them on eBay used I will probably buy them by
I have not found any on eBay
Go for
Interesting so wow this is real
Ok then I'll buy that I will buy the way tune
The noises in the
Ok anyway
Stoneleigh
0.7 volt
Switching it wrong should be spiking down
Clear 13
Set 13
Very nice
Play clean of Dance and Theatre
Singer on folder
Are Tommy and I wish I was following this chat thread
Off
Ok I'll see what is going on now
Hey buddy
9.23 V
That looks pretty sweet
That's terrible
Interesting that looks like the Beacons wonder why that would make me sober
Why would there be
I'm 2926 huge voltage difference
Have you any tomorrow at 3.30 Rail
See what about look like
Oh yeah that is what's going on
What's 8 drop in the VCC of light rays in the
Charge pump
Ok charge pump long-term knock in the world for right now let's just see what happens
So with that now we know the charge pump works
There's no one that's gone
Disappeared
Oh hey
We check that out slowly Reading
10.3 a
Nice salad 10.3 8
Has golden what did that
Hahaha crazy
Increasingly charge pump frequency cleans up the rail that match
Right now
Killarney
Meaning of the problem maybe I just need my card from frequency higher
OKC what does that look like
First starts it is very angry when it first starts
ESP is like wanting to cause face off
Why is it gets moving now
Pigs
That's a long time for s kids up to
1.38 but this is really nice
That's very hard
Split up by factor of
Cialis must be going on this
Cars in the snot excuse fast as I would like
Grade that has to be wild
Then I could totally believe that if I would stick like a little ld-001 bit downstream
Off another ball
That would probably clean the sub Ally
Pumping down what did I do damn
Switch off right now
Gorgeous
Simply gorgeous
Play scala 10.3 a 12
Ok
What does see what voltages
Is the totally open right now on voltages are coming out
3.6 cos that has a limiter on it
No I didn't check should have made sure
The photodiodes and Times news
Don't have a maximum voltage Reading
32 V
Ok I think we're fine
Turn off the
Lighthouses that are called
Turn on
What's the news
It's ok yay
I hear you're terrible I ever
I will admit aar has done some things and assembly that I have
I would never kick the Buddy
Turn time on
Everything else surrounding it is gonna be off from it
Kyle I don't know
Ben I'm really curious what do you think about straight up
GCC GCC is my go-to Elan commercial systems now
For a long time I was kind of stuck in the world of proprietary compilers but eventually
Gave off
Does anyone else here
Turn off the light on my radio does anybody else here actually really prefer any of the other environment
Like more than GCC on
I have I've met people who used to feel that way and
I have never used fly
I don't laugh with avr-gcc
Trouble with it recently really needs the dash fl20 flag to do anything
And I don't know I've had a hard time with Dash fl20
I see you do anything useful when used Ash flt use up much
Lights last for
Match match last
Codebase
LBC
I'm really choose to hate then so when you say climb what what
What is systems this clang run on because I have heard nothing but good things that climb
Do I have heard limited things about climb
And and white screen clang
Now write about all of the charge pump circuit
Volume to connect
I think the TL Dr from that is yes you can
Charge pumps on the esp8266 yes they work no they're not clean or
Liable
Settle
The mileage may vary
GoPro
The probe input minus
Going to probe input - as it goes into the chip
Going to probe
Output
That's not gonna come off
Into the streets
Turn off now
Play me some Spotify for ldm
Does Aldi on actually support 80 hours in actually second question
How old I am support in Celica if it does I will be really tempted
Go fourth on his name
TVR sorry his jslinux towards the
The esp8266 so I will be able to have a browser that could
Compile the code to take c code and compile it in the browser for the processor I think that
Really cool
So I want to reverse by
Estate agents
What side into the minor and hope it doesn't blow up
Straight on
Cd236 girls it's just take them
6455 is the
Yes
Power Force
That's just a complete mess
I'm saying
This is a new girl
Should be there too
How do I why have you
Vue
How do I view the
Show us me and hair 120
In between
Mirrors this absolute terrifying
Charge pump
Ok fine
So plans
You and 3
2 and 3
2 - 3 is
Ok the apology of this is not gonna work and definitely need a different topology
Who is the 93.3 v
I was just concerned about mediate not having a higher frequency response
Honestly inside just assumed that would be a bad thing so
I didn't even go for it
Well I'm really curious why this is not
Really confused by channel sixs not
Ok maybe I will just back out and will just use the door
Turn up
A bit more but I have a feeling that we will be switching out to
Sky Radio
The ts460 2
Can you give that a shot
Expensive 60 piece
The perfect frequency response frequency response
Ok that's why I didn't have no idea
Does
Hello if my five nights
Quiet signal
Oh my gosh it's also cooking itself
Discharge from thing which is done
Alan did tweeter Center schematic for Callum sensor schematic on is for it
Rewind it have the enveloping
Which I do not want
What was life like before
That's a good point then if I use a schematic I would still be able to use the RPM in the flying from
Just have to chop off the background
You make entirely too much sense
What am I looking at
I don't know which I'll be able to use this when it goes mind looking up which I thought was
Yes you can look it up right now I'm using a solo
Can you tell me look up the
Add the schematic
Yates get up
Yankee
That really is going to get some sort of colour
Pause
News
I'm thinking it is best to bandon this now because I'm not really sure how we change the architect
I mean I guess I never thought that but now that
I mean
Does not from across the room but
Pretty cleared
2.9 x 2.7
Mask
What is this
How well
The TC whatever needs on
Is the higher voltage
Can you start in Cluedo
Just a comparator
What speed
Propagation delay that long
Put that shorter response
No no I got it I just up here when I look
Anyway I was looking to Reading
Ok anyway
What does the actual response time look like so sad
Fast enough
500 seconds
What is the phase delay or for Just Can't respond that fast
Turn the lights off
Hello hardest with operated that's so long time
The envelope comparator ok that makes more
Anybody gets me what the the office lamp
I'm using at the front and that would be super cool right now though
I will leave me
I don't think there is anyway
There is no way this is going to get cleaned up good enough to use
Misses the signal and that is the noise and this is the signal like a foot
Cell
I wonder how the size of the compared to the size on
Please guys
Currently I was just gonna decouple it and put it into captain
Just take a peek at it
Sexy hair
Oh buddy
Haha I am going to need a different photodiode to
This is downright embarrassing
Why can't I take a picture
Wrong
Camera
Taking more pictures
What did you want to do mt4
What did you want medium out of
Yeah we are the Dion that guy looks way bigger than the online but that's still
Only need about 2 different stuff
By the way are the bump in the signal is definitely from the light now
You can see the the bump here and there
YouTube on from The Sweet
And it's my house is currently in a mode so you can see that somebody in the summer bit further
Definitely from the Lighthouse the box themselves I believe should be Spaced
8.8 Ms or 16.6 between the pair and it's 6
Sex between the pair
What's the noise of the charge pump
That's unfortunate
On
Actually I think about it
You extra components those that there
Spite of common mode so
Resistor between here and 12th
That should bring it back in the common mode
Maybe
10K
Zoom out
Why is such a specific frequency thats not even on the ntsd frequency is it
No it's only the 90s
Not really need this signal anymore
I'm just maybe eutectic
Turn on use business Saturdays you get something if the junction that you don't want very rare
Hilarious
Where is the car
No action playing any response
That's embarrassing
Why is my voltage so low
2.9 volts
Tired
Yeah
Service to voltage drop there
Curious if I drop the charge from frequency of that
Improve music by I'm guessing probably not
7.7 microseconds in hours
Why is it
Now yeah
Lighthouse stuff
Stephanie above and below but I don't see any app
Oh that's really rough on the ESP
DVLA open
Ok
I get a 9-volt battery but I don't think it's going to get any better I'm pretty sure that apology
And I should probably give up on this apology
Maybe another day maybe another day
No I have a resistor between the the apple in the GP I opened it will ya
Actually has a funky bit of protection circuitry on the inputs it's so that you can drive
Portsmouth V even higher won't hurt it but I don't know
We've ever actually come out and said with the maximum voltage you can put on the prince's but no
I do have the resistor there I have a resistor right here that goes into the i2s I think
The 10K resistor but there is almost no power being dropped on it because the ESB
Funky like that
Yes almost zero
Turbo battery
Don't try this at home kids
Do you wanna say now
Recompile
Is this coming from
White
What's what's going on
Where is the noise coming from
Play
Tell 019 leaving connected
What they're saying the same noise that everything else is doing
Getting weird
Somewhere
Maybe the ESP is causing the ear mouth
Look like
Well apparently if you get loud enough you can see the outfit
Sinclair 6 volts
Still that
The words comments on
Askew
Sweet that's 1.8 MHz carrier
Yeah I start driving with charge pump on a wire make sure I stop driving and I'm getting really
Confused
Soap in one is now tied to the pin that the charge pump cos I'm still there is
Play nothing there
It is absolutely
Play Pretty Queen
Slimming by noises coming from somewhere else
Not sure where
Disable the Wi-Fi in the ESP
Is the Wi-Fi engine the spy put the nail in the coffin
Resolving
Why is the Wi-Fi engine in the ESP so noisy
No no it's still happening this
It doesn't call for now so you don't know this it's ok nevermind
What's the
Definitely did not go the way I was playing
Nothing I had a plan b
Expected more than just how the charge pump works perfectly and nothing else works
Yes the charge pump is about the simplest part though
This guy looks like
Pretty big difference
Yeah you can be the 1.8 MHz signal at first but
What in the world is that
That was
Now there is definitely a maths somewhere else right now the esp8266 is off
The world is going on in my house be causing this
Maybe actually you know you can find out what's causing this
Gpio0 is now disconnected
Look at that glorious noise that it is exactly the frequency of the terrible
Ok where in the world is that coming from
Tell me the laptop
That changed much
Probably close down song
Disconnect everything else now because at least we can figure out where this noises coming from help me tomorrow
Everything on Ford
Play The Noise goes away just just like that
OK how am I supposed to divide this seriously
Instagram backup
So I'm going to go take me there and their
Here here
I'm in Harriet as a huge ground there's no way this would work
Stupid
No the problem is that the sailor is grounded to my desktop
As is the power for this thing
Now if I unplug
No
Something else is still going on here
Still the same
Stupid
What is the theory on Earth
9.6 microseconds
What in the world happened at 9.6 microseconds
Ok white
I get the Oscars
Amplitude
Hello
Bigger
No way
I'm jumping to conclusions here
But I'm thinking I spent a little bit too little money on the power supply in my computer
Because
This little black here is what I touched the shell of the power supply with my finger
The syllable is filled
With that same
Period of awful noise
No it's ok nevermind
I jump to conclusions
That is
I know it's 9.1 microseconds
Alan plug everything
Unplug this
Actually I can test my theory really fast what I can do is I can switch off recurring my laptop
Add xsh cam
Hi
Ok and you guys still get taxed
Unplug the sale a
Plug-in here
I got bad news guys I don't think it's a laptop
Cars
That's my touch the computer ok next step is turn off the desktop
How I said shut down
Does anything
Please
Updown
My desktop is now off
It's just a normal 60hz for my house now
Ok
I bought a Chinese power supply that was too cheap
And
It is nothing everything off
I've have mine just joking my my desktop up to jumpers to my
Track right now
Sounds like the radiator though is to be honest apple in a bit the charge pump is possible
I don't think it would have that much noise actually
We can find out
Send speed now saying with spy laptop here
Get Paul
I forgot the name
My PSU is a funky Chinese 12-volt
Power supply
Strip
Name
Which was not intended for use in a computer
Go on the computer just doesn't work really well for everybody else around me
On 5-years
Plugging everything else backyard
I use a pico PSU for all the 99 12:00 trails
I didn't really start thinking as DVR
Other supply would be
Undone
This one you - which is this one
I want to probe
I want a pro but going into the SP
Oh my gosh
Also way too loud but
Oh my god
So crystal Clear I'm taking a reasonable thing to do if we we are
Use this to help clear that is oh wow
That is interesting that
What daily dose response time isn't actually is good is it
Pause
I guess I have to increase the resistance of the pull-up
Actually I really should have a ground loop
Cheap ones are USB 3.0
Man oh ok so the answer is there's really no
Problem with the charge pump system
It is rock solid
Queen
Plus 3
What's going on there
6-months
True that
Going into the SP
So clear
Something's just her
The wrong turn
That's the charge pumpkin
Crystal clear so clean you just don't
What's going into the ESPC
Weird
Might 141 into the home voltage
Sure why
Not really care at this point I think it's just the wrong
Wake me up in the wrong solution
Thank you everybody for sticking around
Yeah this is just
Ok sure what's crank it
Play The One That Really Care
Free that has the power come
The charge pump
Cos that's the one that's going off the main system and I can do that at 50 so
Trousers mess of wires in
Yeah I am I'm looking hearing I don't see anything
Any sign of that charge pump being sad gold
Well that was fun
Definitely going to have to play with us some more though
Thanks for tuning in everyone this was fun
Yeah
So
How long till we hackaday worthy but it definitely looks like you can
Can definitely get a charge pump running on an EST
And ESP doesn't seem to care if you shave 6 volt input so that's kind me too
Thank you everyone for coming out it was a lot of fun